<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Latest Posts Onfashion | JunkJam | Fashion! LifeStyle! Market! Travel!]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/categories/fashion/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2018-11-22T16:55:55+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethnic Fashion Trends for Navratri and Where to Shop Them]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/16/ethnic-fashion-trends-for-navratri-and-where-to-shop-them/"/>
    <updated>2018-09-16T13:38:06+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/16/ethnic-fashion-trends-for-navratri-and-where-to-shop-them</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>{% img left <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594290-e3fc9300-b9b5-11e8-9251-1c6747e7d9d2.JPG">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594290-e3fc9300-b9b5-11e8-9251-1c6747e7d9d2.JPG</a> 400 500 %}
Among all the various celebrations that exist everywhere throughout the nation, Navratri far surpasses the rest as far as sheer spectacle and speculate. The 9-day celebration is one of the greatest in the nation alongside Dussera and Diwali. On the event of Navratri, a considerable measure of you will want to dress your best, have a good time and participating in all the different dances that occur, for example, the garba and dandiya. However, for those of you who have no clue how to dress up during Navratri, you need to keep reading thoroughly below, where we&rsquo;ve compiled the best Ethnic Fashion Trends for Navratri and also given you tips on the best way to look your finest in every department of your Navratri style.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>1.  Long kurtas with palazzo suits for Navratri</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594289-e3fc9300-b9b5-11e8-92f7-2a34b8a0afe3.JPG">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594289-e3fc9300-b9b5-11e8-92f7-2a34b8a0afe3.JPG</a> 500 600 %}
Even though traditional outfits are usually favored for Navratri, you can simply try something new and go the in a trendy way by matching voguish outfits that go well together. One such mix that truly functions admirably is the pairing of long kurtas with palazzo suits which will truly enable you in breaking out each one of those elegant dance moves you have in store for the dance floor. Since Navratri is a sensory overload of colors, a interesting method to spice things up is to pick colorful dupattas.
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594288-e363fc80-b9b5-11e8-955b-d0cfe3b8e9bc.JPG">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594288-e363fc80-b9b5-11e8-955b-d0cfe3b8e9bc.JPG</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<h4>2.  Anarkalis for Navratri</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594285-e232cf80-b9b5-11e8-8100-b544f8bbd8ae.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594285-e232cf80-b9b5-11e8-8100-b544f8bbd8ae.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
There are no two different opinions about Anarkalis being truly excellent. The silhouette and styling of this ethnic outfit are very complementing for most body types and renders a fantastic and magnificent appeal. Despite the fact that it&rsquo;s basically traditional in style, Anarkali Suits still keep on being amazing in current times. That is primarily one of the principle reasons why Anarkali Suits are most favored for special and traditional occasions, for example, Navratri celebrations.
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594284-e232cf80-b9b5-11e8-9dc1-ff18582d593c.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594284-e232cf80-b9b5-11e8-9dc1-ff18582d593c.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<h4>3.  Festive Lehenga Choli</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594287-e2cb6600-b9b5-11e8-81a0-456a60119452.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594287-e2cb6600-b9b5-11e8-81a0-456a60119452.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
Navratri is one such Indian celebration where individuals incline toward a traditional Indian outfit. Navratri is synonymous with Lehenga Choli, the reason being it is celebrated largely in Gujarat and Rajasthan where Lehenga Cholis are mostly worn by the ladies. Today, there&rsquo;s a plenty of Lehenga Choli Designs available in the market to suit your taste.
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594286-e2cb6600-b9b5-11e8-9476-9c5538364354.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594286-e2cb6600-b9b5-11e8-9476-9c5538364354.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<h4>4.  Silk Sarees for Navratri</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594291-e4952980-b9b5-11e8-8436-0ce0313b3240.JPG">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594291-e4952980-b9b5-11e8-8436-0ce0313b3240.JPG</a> 500 600 %}
Amid celebrations like Navratri, individuals favor only ethnic traditional Indian outfits. Silk Sarees, maybe, best speak to ethnic Indian Fashion. In this manner, Silk Sarees with their unmatched brilliance are a perfect Indian outfit for Navratri. India has an extensive assortment of Silk Sarees to offer, for example, Kanjeevaram Silk Sarees, Mysore Silk saree, Benarasi Silk Zareez, Poochampalli Silk Sareez, Sambalpuri Silk Zarees, and so forth.
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594290-e3fc9300-b9b5-11e8-9251-1c6747e7d9d2.JPG">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594290-e3fc9300-b9b5-11e8-9251-1c6747e7d9d2.JPG</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<p>Buying wonderful Navratri Fashion Online</p>

<p>In the event that you have decided to purchase Navratri outfits, then the best game-plan for you would be to online shop from a reputed online ethnic fashion site which is notable for having the best collection of Navratri dresses online that incorporate an assortment of Indian ethnic styles, all available at amazingly reasonable costs with huge rebates, deals and offers as well.</p>

<h4>Best Websites to Shop Navratri Outfits Online</h4>

<ul>
<li>Jabong.com</li>
<li>Ajio.com</li>
<li>Myntra.com</li>
<li>Craftsvilla.com</li>
<li>Lifestylestores.com</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Websites Giving the Best Deals on Ethnic Wear for Raksha Bandhan]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/22/5-websites-giving-the-best-deals-on-ethnic-wear-for-raksha-bandhan/"/>
    <updated>2018-08-22T20:16:18+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/22/5-websites-giving-the-best-deals-on-ethnic-wear-for-raksha-bandhan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>{% img left <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470760-285f7200-a648-11e8-8d45-cfb969003344.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470760-285f7200-a648-11e8-8d45-cfb969003344.jpg</a> 400 500 %}
Raksha Bandhan is fast approaching and it&rsquo;s the right time for us to buy ethnic wear. Festive occasions like this are special for us because apart from getting a chance to celebrate, we also get to buy and wear different kinds of stunning ethnic wear. Who doesn&rsquo;t love to pamper themselves every once in a while by dressing up in ethnic royalty?</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>More and more people are starting to use websites, mobile apps, etc. to find the best deals and not make the trip to the closest bricks-and-mortar shop. By using the right websites and resources, it can be very easy to find great deals online. Here are 5 of the best websites offering online deals this Raksha Bandhan:</p>

<h4>1.  Myntra</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470764-28f80880-a648-11e8-8009-364df6526750.JPG">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470764-28f80880-a648-11e8-8009-364df6526750.JPG</a> 500 600 %}
Myntra is an e-retailer that is offering exclusive and mega discounts on ethnic wear this Raksha Bandhan. There are more than 1500 Indian brands and 200 brands globally and is certainly one of the topmost style destinations for all ethnic fashion enthusiasts. Must check out their lucrative offers and buy something for yourself and your sibling.</p>

<h4>2.  Amazon</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470760-285f7200-a648-11e8-8d45-cfb969003344.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470760-285f7200-a648-11e8-8d45-cfb969003344.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
Based in the United States and one of the largest online retailers in the world, Amazon offers an amazing ethnic wear collection. Outfits within this category have been categorized according to genders, such as women&rsquo;s and men&rsquo;s clothing; according to brands, such as Manyavar, Biba, etc. or also according to stores, such as of that belonging to a specific designer, and so on. The site offers a 30-day return on its all its products with &lsquo;no questions asked&rsquo;. So, you must check out their amazing offers today.</p>

<h4>3.  Jabong</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470761-285f7200-a648-11e8-9ef8-1f9a19455bed.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470761-285f7200-a648-11e8-9ef8-1f9a19455bed.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
Since essentially Jabong is a fashion portal, it offers a great variety of options for women, men, kids, in ethnic wear. It offers its customers with options that range from local brands and even designers like Rohit Bal to Rohit Gandhi-Rahul Khanna, etc. If you are someone who loves ethnic fashion, their ethnic wear is something you must check out. You Raksha Bandhan outfit worries will be sorted.</p>

<h4>4.  Lifestyle India</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470762-28f80880-a648-11e8-845a-8b96d905016d.JPG">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470762-28f80880-a648-11e8-845a-8b96d905016d.JPG</a> 500 600 %}
Lifestyle India is a fashion retailer that offers menswear, women&rsquo;s wear, jewelry, cosmetics, and so on. They also have brick and mortar stores across India. It provides its customers with exclusive deals with new discounts on ethnic wear and also offers affordable fashion.</p>

<h4>5.  Ajio</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470759-27c6db80-a648-11e8-960e-1dd5f28d9798.JPG">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470759-27c6db80-a648-11e8-960e-1dd5f28d9798.JPG</a> 500 600 %}
Within the fashion category, their products are categorized into men&rsquo;s, women&rsquo;s, and kid&rsquo;s fashion, which are further categorized according to the type of fashion product and type of clothing. Ajio offers an assortment of options within each fashion section for both women and men, such as Ethnic wear, which consists of sarees, anarkalis, palazzos, dress material, semi stitched and stitched kurtas, salwars and churidars, and so on.</p>

<p>All you need to do is find something that you love and then compare the offers you are getting, which are offered at these amazing websites and then buy the one that meets your budget along with your requirements.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Shoes Every Girl Must Own]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/12/7-shoes-every-girl-must-own/"/>
    <updated>2018-08-12T16:28:12+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/12/7-shoes-every-girl-must-own</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>{% img left <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001289-9f8b3b7e-9e4c-11e8-8c47-4330971ed49c.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001289-9f8b3b7e-9e4c-11e8-8c47-4330971ed49c.jpg</a> 400 500 %}
If you are a shoe lover and always have an urge to buy a pair of shoes, then you probably can’t have enough pairs to satiate your love for shoes. While you might not have all the shoes you would like to have, here are the essential 7 pairs that every girl should have in their collection:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>1.  Pumps</h4>

<p>When it comes to style, pumps never go out of style. These shoes are good for all ages and are very versatile when it comes to mixing and matching your overall outfit. Pumps are becoming more abundant on the shoe racks at the stores and they are commonly seen as fashionable for everyday wear.  You can get them in just about any color and they match up effortlessly with anything from a skirt and top to a pair of jeans. Its strength lies in its ease of use and its versatility.
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001286-9dce9b32-9e4c-11e8-8837-cccd4a47ade5.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001286-9dce9b32-9e4c-11e8-8837-cccd4a47ade5.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<h4>2.  Sneakers</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001289-9f8b3b7e-9e4c-11e8-8c47-4330971ed49c.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001289-9f8b3b7e-9e4c-11e8-8c47-4330971ed49c.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
We wear shoes almost every day of our lives. That means that we want supportive, comfy shoes for all the different areas of our daily lives. Sneakers are one of the few shoes that you can pick that fit into almost every part of your daily life. Whether you want to go for a walk, play a game, go out dancing or even to work you can certainly find a pair of sneakers that will fit right in. Sneakers are well-known for their comfort and their relaxed style.</p>

<h4>3.  Ankle boots</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001276-99042e8c-9e4c-11e8-928c-23c870e7c398.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001276-99042e8c-9e4c-11e8-928c-23c870e7c398.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
Ankle boots are a wonderful fashion accessory, whether you choose high-heeled, tasseled, fur-lined or flat, a good quality pair of ankle boots can set you apart in the fashion game. One of the trendiest items of footwear available, ankle boots can make an array of style statements.</p>

<h4>4.  Flat Sandals</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001278-9a6da4ce-9e4c-11e8-9600-9fde9c61ee09.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001278-9a6da4ce-9e4c-11e8-9600-9fde9c61ee09.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
Flat sandals are one of the staple accessories of summer and spring fashion. They are comfortable and suitable footwear for a plethora of events from a beach party or an evening outing.</p>

<h4>5.  Knee High Boots</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001282-9c8cd716-9e4c-11e8-9388-a3720bd3dbf7.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001282-9c8cd716-9e4c-11e8-9388-a3720bd3dbf7.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
Knee high boots come in a huge number of designs and colors so you are certain to find at least one pair that you love. Knee high boots can be worn with almost anything in your wardrobe so you can go formal to casual to sensual with these boots in a jiffy.</p>

<h4>6.  Heels</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001279-9b38bf7e-9e4c-11e8-8163-ed2696abc38e.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001279-9b38bf7e-9e4c-11e8-8163-ed2696abc38e.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
Women love to complete their look with heels. Heels are a trendy accessory in their closet and they have been highly popular among girls for a long time. These are the most classic type of shoes that women love to wear to accentuate their look.</p>

<h4>7.  Wedge Sandals</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001290-a7337daa-9e4c-11e8-8923-6496e9dbd43c.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001290-a7337daa-9e4c-11e8-8923-6496e9dbd43c.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
If you are looking for something comfy and easy to walk in, step into wedge sandals. Wedges are such a versatile shoe that they can be paired with virtually any outfit, from formal to informal.</p>

<p>These are the top 7 types of must-have shoes in a typical women&rsquo;s closet. With all the fresh style coming out every season, you will certainly find that perfect pair for you.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Must Have Bottom Wears for Every Fashionista]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/11/8-must-have-bottom-wears-for-every-fashionista/"/>
    <updated>2018-08-11T21:05:44+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/11/8-must-have-bottom-wears-for-every-fashionista</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>{% img left <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993469-a5502dcc-9dab-11e8-972b-e0f36a656bf6.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993469-a5502dcc-9dab-11e8-972b-e0f36a656bf6.jpg</a> 400 500 %}
A couple of years ago, there weren&rsquo;t a whole lot of choices available for bottom wears. But as fashion got trendier, the world has become your oyster! Palazzos, cigarette pants, dhoti pants, culottes - the silhouettes are endless! So, whatever your shape and preference, here are 8 must-have bottom-wears for you.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>1.  Palazzos</h4>

<p>The key to looking stylish in palazzos is to feel comfy wearing them, which is exactly what palazzos are all about - comfortable and fashionable. Palazzos are stylish and cool summer-wear and give women a much-needed break from the dull blue jeans, dresses, normal work pants and salwar kameez. Palazzos have become a rage in India; it is the most loved Indo-western trend adopted from the flared silhouettes of the 60s and 70s.
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993400-4abde742-9daa-11e8-9b08-98d23f2143d7.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993400-4abde742-9daa-11e8-9b08-98d23f2143d7.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<h4>2.  Culottes</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993397-4a1a79e0-9daa-11e8-8fc2-7da07cd78de1.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993397-4a1a79e0-9daa-11e8-8fc2-7da07cd78de1.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
Culottes were unquestionably one of the most sought-after fashions of the 60s and 70s. Not only could you go to an exercise class in them but also run errands, without having to change your clothes. Now culottes can be one of the most versatile clothing items in your closet. Simply pair culottes with a t-shirt for casual gatherings or wear a dressier top and shoes for special occasions. You certainly need to give the culottes a chance this season.</p>

<h4>3.  Ethnic skirts</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993399-4a8847c2-9daa-11e8-96d1-11f5bc0e69bf.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993399-4a8847c2-9daa-11e8-96d1-11f5bc0e69bf.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
Pass up the pencil skirts this season and buy yourself a stunning long ethnic skirt. And you are sure to look like a diva! These skirts paired with crop top are the perfect party wear for women attending any small function.</p>

<h4>4.  Cigarette pants</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993396-49e5a9a4-9daa-11e8-9333-9386bcf4a461.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993396-49e5a9a4-9daa-11e8-9333-9386bcf4a461.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
No girl’s closet can ever be complete without a pair of 4.  Cigarette pants! It is one Indian outfit that can be worn to the office or even lunch dates. They are loved for their flattering fit and have the power to make you feel oh-so-chic.</p>

<h4>5.  Dhoti pants</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993398-4a52d8bc-9daa-11e8-924a-f1f0a89fe4b0.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993398-4a52d8bc-9daa-11e8-924a-f1f0a89fe4b0.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
The dhoti pants are back in style, giving women some incredible designs to pick from. It&rsquo;s truly a great item for anyone looking for an appealing bottom-wear to add to their closet.</p>

<h4>6.  Ripped jeans</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993402-4af89798-9daa-11e8-8566-5c480773eef6.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993402-4af89798-9daa-11e8-8566-5c480773eef6.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
The ripped jeans are now very much in fashion. It has done well in the majority of countries and is fast catching up in other places too. Especially, teenagers are crazy about this ripped style and they sure know how to look cool without getting influenced by the latest trends.</p>

<h4>7.  Boyfriend jeans</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993395-49b117de-9daa-11e8-94d2-fea55c6c1403.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993395-49b117de-9daa-11e8-94d2-fea55c6c1403.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
When summer comes, can boyfriend jeans be far behind? One of the great products of the boyfriend fashion trend is the boyfriend jeans. These jeans are the latest rage amongst the comfortable fashion lovers. The best part is that you can steal it from your partner&rsquo;s closet!</p>

<h4>8.  Shorts/ hot pants</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993403-4b2fc43e-9daa-11e8-8168-4985f284b249.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993403-4b2fc43e-9daa-11e8-8168-4985f284b249.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
There is nothing comfier than wearing shorts or hot pants in summer day. They are not only worn during vacation but also anytime since they offer minimalism and hot look!</p>

<p>Now that you know what bottom war items to have in your closet, it&rsquo;s time to go online and start shopping for the perfect bottom wear available for girls out there.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Bags Every Girl Must Own]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/04/7-bags-every-girl-must-own/"/>
    <updated>2018-08-04T14:30:42+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/04/7-bags-every-girl-must-own</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>{% img left <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674620-ae309c68-97f4-11e8-8be5-2aeaeaaa74a8.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674620-ae309c68-97f4-11e8-8be5-2aeaeaaa74a8.jpg</a> 400 500 %}
Bags are an essential part of a lady’s life. A lady needs to ensure she has the best and right bags to suit every single outfit in her closet. Luckily, it’s less demanding than it sounds. Here is a list of the must-have bags for all kinds of ladies.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674534-166f4164-97f3-11e8-8ce2-d614651fd8f6.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674534-166f4164-97f3-11e8-8ce2-d614651fd8f6.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<h4>1.  Satchel:</h4>

<p>There&rsquo;s one fundamental rule with regards to picking bags, and that is to buy them in neutral hues so that they will work everywhere - from the workplace to parties. Black, brown, grey, navy and camel are the best hues that will match well with every outfit. Pick a satchel for active lifestyles and for desk jobs and the like. Structured styles are more sophisticated and professional.</p>

<h4>2.  Backpack:</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674530-15a001b0-97f3-11e8-9432-bd5e5cfb5e86.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674530-15a001b0-97f3-11e8-9432-bd5e5cfb5e86.jpg</a>  500 600 %}
It&rsquo;s an ideal opportunity to rediscover this school-time favorite, as there are many &ldquo;grown-up&rdquo; backpacks that are smart and practical even for a working professional. Purchase a stylish backpack; it&rsquo;s astonishing how these bags have transformed in the course the last couple of years. They look fashionable and are sufficiently big to hold a lot of stuff. Just get yourself one!</p>

<h4>3.  Tote Bag:</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674535-16a373d0-97f3-11e8-9aa5-12de63ec3446.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674535-16a373d0-97f3-11e8-9aa5-12de63ec3446.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
The tote is everyone’s favorite. Every woman needs a tote bag in her closet. A sophisticated tote is ideal for a road trip or in the event that one has a couple of additional things more than usual. They add to the overall look and are also very stylish and trendy.  Made in quality leather they will never go out of style.</p>

<h4>4.  Classy Clutch:</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674531-15d368ca-97f3-11e8-8a85-f21bdda2a207.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674531-15d368ca-97f3-11e8-8a85-f21bdda2a207.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
Ladies can show off their elegant style when they decide to add a statement clutch to their collection of bags. These look perfect with just a casual jeans and t-shirt day or for a night out on the town. Blow people&rsquo;s minds with this new favorite that can be grabbed to go along with pretty much anything when you just cannot decide what bag to carry.</p>

<h4>5.  Cross Body:</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674532-160552ea-97f3-11e8-9a77-be2d6a458053.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674532-160552ea-97f3-11e8-9a77-be2d6a458053.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
Whatever the event, each lady ought to have a cross-body in her bags collection. They function admirably for a date or a night out with friends. They are just the correct size to carry just what one needs to touch up or get into the clubs. Utilize the strap to make it super easy to move around and pick something that is fun with little stylish details that turn heads.</p>

<h4>6.  Evening Bag:</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674533-163bd0b8-97f3-11e8-868d-37bf1afe50ff.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674533-163bd0b8-97f3-11e8-868d-37bf1afe50ff.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
Regardless of whether a mini strap bag or clutch, each young lady ought to have a beautiful evening bag that will be ideal for the most upscale of gatherings. While black is reliably the best choice, the most imperative thought is to discover a style that has subtle appeal, similar to a quilted style or satin finish bag.</p>

<h4>7.  The Bucket Bag:</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674588-0a0a610a-97f4-11e8-98cd-717a62e2bb77.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674588-0a0a610a-97f4-11e8-98cd-717a62e2bb77.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
These bags are exquisite and modern in one solid color and without a lot of detail. Ideal for working ladies who need big bags to carry lots of stuff and who have to attend corporate parties all the time.</p>

<p>Each of the above-mentioned bags is exclusive in their own way and is a must-have for the closet of a fashionable woman.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
