<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[JunkJam Blog]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2016-09-20T07:45:00+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Shop From Streets]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/19/why-shop-from-streets/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-19T22:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/19/why-shop-from-streets</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641943/62d0d65a-7ebc-11e6-8e60-9e56dd3ac1bd.jpg" width="450" height="600" title="Bargaining" >
With advent of many e-commerce sites and recent emergence of mall culture in india, here are top 7 reasons why street shopping is still a hit.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641945/62e48c2c-7ebc-11e6-9beb-387444617a2c.jpg"></p>

<h2>1. Bargaining is fun - every girl&rsquo;s right</h2>

<p>A bargain is something you don&rsquo;t need at a price you can&rsquo;t resist. - Franklin Jones
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641944/62d14356-7ebc-11e6-83a4-141257d22e5e.jpg"></p>

<h2>2. Street food - The only thing I like better than talking about food is eating : John Walters</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641950/636edf3a-7ebc-11e6-8d15-9086fe5841ab.jpg">
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641949/636b5928-7ebc-11e6-89bf-28aa02e085db.jpg"></p>

<h2>3. No need of cards -&ldquo;Na credit card bada na debit, sabse bada rupaiya!!&rdquo;</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641946/6320e73a-7ebc-11e6-9928-56e494cabd75.jpg">
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641948/6340981e-7ebc-11e6-8a68-fdc9d2aa4502.jpg"></p>

<h2>4. Worth every penny - value for money</h2>

<p>It is not the money that matters, it&rsquo;s how you use it that determines its true value.
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641956/63f894c8-7ebc-11e6-97f9-a8671888260f.jpg">
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641957/6403da04-7ebc-11e6-82d1-8b5ab7a252bb.jpg"></p>

<h2>5. Verify your goods - goods are tangible</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641960/6489419e-7ebc-11e6-8879-fc1586f2d9a7.jpg">
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641962/64aeb42e-7ebc-11e6-99b1-2ffcedeeedad.jpg">
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641963/64c10cb4-7ebc-11e6-9f42-6c8746127e7b.jpg">
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641959/642e4b04-7ebc-11e6-80ff-8ab40b5ecc3a.jpg"></p>

<h2>6. No hidden costs - no shipping, packages, delievery charges</h2>

<p>The price you see is the price you pay !!
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641954/63e39e92-7ebc-11e6-999b-7502c54105cc.jpg">
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641955/63f61284-7ebc-11e6-9f8d-4205a1779b11.jpg"></p>

<h2>7. Friendly staff - To help you choose</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641952/63b8b1be-7ebc-11e6-90a6-4fbbb7c9a7a7.jpg"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Honeymoon Dresses to Wow Him]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/15/5-honeymoon-dresses-to-wow-him/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-15T12:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/15/5-honeymoon-dresses-to-wow-him</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550457/95725a82-7b71-11e6-9e6b-2924f7b15b7e.jpg" width="400" height="500">
After the wedding ceremonies are done, the newly wedded couple is all ready to get set and go for their honeymoon. You want everything to be the best, be it the honeymoon destination, the venue where you’ll b staying, the places that you are going to visit, the activities you are going to do, the places you are going to eat or shop. Everything is planned in advance and you just can’t wait to do it all. Your excitement level is simply unstoppable!</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Honeymoon! The dreamy phase of every girl’s life, where everything seems to be perfect and the way it had to be. So, you are in your dreamy phase and can’t keep your hands off each other. You just can’t wait to reach your honeymoon spot, but before you set out for it, do not forget to do your homework. Yes, we are talking about a few pretty and hot outfits that would simply make him go nuts over your beauty! Also, a dress chosen wisely can make it an amazing as well as a never forgetting honeymoon for you. Here are a few suggestions as to what dresses can you take along on your honeymoon and have those picture perfect memories:</p>

<h1>Evening dress</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550455/9558ed54-7b71-11e6-83a2-fb4d7c6986ed.jpg" width="600" height="700">
Nothing can make you look classier than an elegant yet sexy evening dress. They say red is the color of love so why not put on a red evening dress and have a candle light dinner beneath a sky lit with stars. Pair it with pencil heels and a beige or gold clutch and slay him!</p>

<h1>Floral tunic</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550456/956e0658-7b71-11e6-8438-a619ff6f4cc4.jpg" width="600" height="700">
A tiny tunic makes every girl look pretty and hot at the same time. So, wearing a cute floral dress while going out for shopping would not let him take his eyes off you. Putting on a light and natural makeup would add to the glow on your face and give you that perfect look that would make him love you more and more.</p>

<h1>Boho piece</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550453/951f542c-7b71-11e6-9634-8e3c1f603e84.jpg">
A boho one piece is all you need to have that attractive look for your honeymoon. Moreover, it would make your better half go completely crazy after you.</p>

<h1>Hot pants</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550454/954add72-7b71-11e6-95c6-97a8c9d5d202.jpg" width="600" height="700">
Hot pants give every girl a sexy chic look. So a denim hot pant wore with a sexy top or a cool tee accompanied by a pair of shades and  wedges would get you a look that would make his eyes glued to you.</p>

<h1>Barely there</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550457/95725a82-7b71-11e6-9e6b-2924f7b15b7e.jpg">
A beaded net top or dress in nude in color will leave a little to his imagination. The beaded threadwork on the outfit would make you look sexy and he would not be able to resist you anymore and you will be all set for a hot and amazing night.</p>

<p>Hope you like our suggestions on the kind of dresses that would make your honeymoon an extra special and extra hot one! Do not forget to click amazing pictures and make a beautiful collection of your beautiful memories.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Best Indian Wedding Songs for the Grand Bridal Entry]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/11/8-best-Indian-wedding-songs-for-the-grand-bridal-entry/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-11T12:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/11/8-best-Indian-wedding-songs-for-the-grand-bridal-entry</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417590/530a3f42-7852-11e6-9294-5bc2cd9fc9f9.jpg" width="400" height="500">
Wedding! The most auspicious and important day of every girl’s life! On this so very special day, everything ought to be perfect. From a beautiful bridal dress to the perfect background song during the entry, there needs to be sublimity in everything and every girl wants that these dreams come true.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Picture yourself on your wedding day walking down the alley with your favorite people by your side. The marvelous attire and a soft romantic song being played in the background, while you move towards your prince charming. Doesn’t it seem like a fairy tale where you are the princess and the evening belongs to you! So, to help you with this fairy tale turning into reality, we have a list of songs to make your bridal entry an epic one:</p>

<h1>Raabta</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417601/8875089c-7852-11e6-9126-72595dcd31f9.jpg">
Raabta song from the movie Agent Vinod can be an excellent choice to make the bridal entry a decent yet a grand one! The lyrics of the song, “Kehte Hai Khuda Ne…” perfectly fit the moment, addressing the bride’s and bridegroom’s emotions to each other.</p>

<h1>Din Shagna Da</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417608/ab9a5494-7852-11e6-86e9-a37cd6077c95.jpg">
I think Din Shagna Da is played at almost every Indian wedding when the beautiful maiden enters. There is hardly any wedding where we won’t hear “din shagna da chadheya” playing in the background, as the bride is stepping towards her to be husband.</p>

<h1>Sajde kiye hai laakhon</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417664/e7174404-7853-11e6-85f8-5e7d181c2eb8.jpg">
From the legend Akshay Kumar’s movie Khatta Meetha, Sajde kiye hai laakhon is also an ideal and lovely song that can be played at the time of bridal entry. The song is soothing to the ears and would perfectly convey the heart-tendering feelings going on in the hearts of the bridegroom as well as the bride.</p>

<h1>Tum se hi</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417668/0d05ea80-7854-11e6-9f8f-8fb2a24d8fd0.jpg">
Another amazing song for a bride’s entry is the song “Tum se hi” from the movie Jab we met. It describes how important both of them feel about each other.</p>

<h1>Teri Ore</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417590/530a3f42-7852-11e6-9294-5bc2cd9fc9f9.jpg">
I think there cannot be a better song that would best describe the moment. As the bride moves towards her better half, the lyrics of the song match every step she takes or each moment she does, while moving forward.</p>

<h1>O Re piya</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18617466/3d618402-7ded-11e6-94e6-4fc865e880cc.jpg">
The song “o re piya” sung by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan is good enough to grab people’s attention as and when you enter the venue on your big day.</p>

<h1>Kabira Encore</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417691/a6a4f28a-7854-11e6-9b88-444fff453698.jpg">
Kabira encore version is another wonderful song that can be played well when the bride enters the wedding hall. It makes the atmosphere so senti-menti that the people around start shedding tears looking at the bride.</p>

<h1>Latika’s theme song</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18617465/3d123bfe-7ded-11e6-9119-a3d8d6c156ce.jpg">
Sung by A.R. Rehman, from the movie Slum Dog Millionaire, this theme song is just a feeling that would definitely bring goose bumps on the skin of the listeners. The more you listen to this, the more you will feel it and love it.</p>

<p>So girls , on your big day, don’t let the DJs ruin your eye-catching entry by playing some cheap beats. Choose your own jingle for your special day!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Ways to Re-use Your Bridal Lehenga]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/05/7-ways-to-re-use-your-bridal-lehenga/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-05T21:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/05/7-ways-to-re-use-your-bridal-lehenga</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250508/6ecce898-73a1-11e6-918f-451afab578b6.jpg" width="400" height="500">
When it comes to choosing the Bridal Lehenga, we just never mind the thousands of rupees as well as the long hours spent in finalizing the same. We take extra initiative to customize it according to our preference and make it more attractive in every way possible. But what happens of that precious piece of clothing, the bridal lehenga , after the wedding. Well if I am not wrong, then half of my readers will raise their hand if I say its wrapped up in a malmal ka kapda safely in the wardrobe. Well here are some great ideas to re use your bridal lehenga in a classy fashion again and again.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Lessen the volume and Cut it along.</h1>

<p>Though it may sound very harsh and painful but one can surely lessen down the motifs and heavy embellishments by simply cutting it off and toning it down in its look. With the extra kalis removed which was forcefully inserted at that time or event with the net out it will look more subtle and wearable.
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250132/b938d0c4-739f-11e6-8ae8-f779a4d6da8a.jpg"></p>

<h1>Switch the style to Anarkali</h1>

<p>With the help of a good tailor, its quite easy to transform your wedding attire to an embellished anarkali which looks less bridal in comparison to a bridal lehenga. The skirt and the blouse can be stitched together with a waist belt or the same can be stitched with a separate simpler blouse to get the desired effect.
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250242/46f88c24-73a0-11e6-878e-0abb97a8dcf3.jpg"></p>

<h1>Long Kurtis with Lehengas</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250412/d8b718b0-73a0-11e6-847d-7d36d95ba8ab.jpg" width="500" height="600">
This is one of the most preferred styles that have hit the fashion world with a bang. And it is also a great way to reuse the bridal lehenga with a toned kurti and set the look. Even jackets with thin borders are also a good option to try along.</p>

<h1>Combining the bridal set with other attires</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250339/aaba739e-73a0-11e6-8b2f-a31b13861729.jpg">
Usually the bridal lehenga teamed up with designer blouses and embellished dupatta forms the bridal set and altogether they provide the bridal feel. So the best way is to team the lehenga with a toned top, wear the blouse with a plain skirt and use the dupatta with a neutral shaded salwar kameez.</p>

<h1>Color Blocks</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250285/73bdf9e2-73a0-11e6-8379-7be272a1b291.jpg">
It is not always necessary to team up bridal lehenga with same colored blouses. Color blocking is quite in the fashion so if the idea is to attend some wedding function then pair up the embellished lehenga with a no work blouse of different color and just set the elegant look for the occasion.</p>

<h1>Drape it as a saree</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250339/aaba739e-73a0-11e6-8b2f-a31b13861729.jpg">
There are many cases when the lehenga sets have a long flowing dupatta with loads of zari work on it. The best way to tone the dress down and still keep the charm is to drape the dupatta as a saree pallu and use a toned down blouse to maintain the classy look</p>

<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250508/6ecce898-73a1-11e6-918f-451afab578b6.jpg"></p>

<h1>Use as it is</h1>

<p>We all love our lehengas and honestly there are many who just don’t want to alter it. For them the best way to use it is by wearing it just as it is but with a simpler accessories, toned make up, and by letting the hair fall casually.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Destinations for Your Last Single Girls Trip]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/05/10-destinations-for-your-last-single-girls-trip/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-05T19:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/05/10-destinations-for-your-last-single-girls-trip</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239264/c88e218e-7361-11e6-8e2b-a9ef93478244.jpg" width="500" height="600">
Ever been on an ‘only girls’ trip? If you haven’t done it or thought about it yet then go girl, do it now! Yes, here we are referring to an all-girls trip before you step in to your married life. When it comes to your last ‘single girls’ trip, it has to be something unique and epic! Here are 10 destinations for you that would let you have the time of your life.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Udaipur</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18238964/74dbdab0-735f-11e6-9a66-a01849176716.jpg">
Do forts, lakes and palaces are something that interests you? If so, here is the perfect destination for you and your girlies and that’s none other than Udaipur. This place is situated to the south of Rajasthan and coming here would make you feel as if you are here to take pleasure of the rich and cultural heritage of your motherland.</p>

<h1>Amboli</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239048/325a3c6c-7360-11e6-99a8-785bb37b40dc.jpg">
If you are a nature lover, you are definitely going to get mesmerized with the eye-catching beauty of Amboli, a beautiful hill station in South Maharashtra. The panoramic view of Amboli Falls and Shirgaonkar Point will make you fall in love with this place. Added to the fun, spicy Malvani food would provide you the remaining satisfaction.</p>

<h1>Rishikesh</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239104/8969b64a-7360-11e6-8184-1917d5516b77.jpg">
Bring out the adrenaline junkie in you and be as adventurous as you can! Plan a road trip to Rishikesh and attend the Ganga aarti, taking place at Triven Ghat. Going Rishikesh and not doing river rafting would be regretful. Splash through the white waters of the place and give yourself a wave of thrilling fun. The treehouse café Little Buddha near Laxman Jhula is also worth a visit.</p>

<h1>Ladakh</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239194/2ad549f4-7361-11e6-8b14-d927e16ca65d.jpg">
Snow lovers would simply not resist going to Ladhakh. It is usually found that girls love snow all around, crystal clear lakes, all of it presenting nature at its best.</p>

<h1>Alleppey</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239198/33fdf26a-7361-11e6-90df-fc8c286f3ab1.jpg">
Taking your best friends along and staying in a boathouse would be so much fun! The backwaters of Alleppey would let you have this fun with all the best girls of your life. Also, don’t forget to pay a visit to the Alleppey Beach.</p>

<h1>Nainital</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239229/7ce9e6be-7361-11e6-81de-534f8447f499.jpg">
Well, being a mini hill station of Uttarakhand, Nainital is not at all a bad option an all girls trip. The alluring Naini Lake and the mountains make this place a big hit among the travelers. The Kumaoni cuisine can also be tasted at its best when you visit this place.</p>

<h1>Ziro Valley, Arunachal Pradesh</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239113/968b815a-7360-11e6-8642-90103c7637f2.jpg">
Ziro Valley is counted amongst the most ‘worth watching’ places of Arunachal Pradesh. The Apatani Tribe and their rich and prosperous heritage can be a great source of knowledge about this place.</p>

<h1>Shimla</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239186/14a91f34-7361-11e6-93a3-f43aa76755a9.JPG">
For the ladies, here is the safest hill station Shimla and along with its breathtaking beauty, don’t miss out the Toy Train.</p>

<h1>Varanasi</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239104/8969b64a-7360-11e6-8184-1917d5516b77.jpg">
This divine city would arise the goddess in you and the morning boat ride is one of a kind.</p>

<h1>Sikkim</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239198/33fdf26a-7361-11e6-90df-fc8c286f3ab1.jpg">
The gorgeous valleys and the sky touching mountains accompanied by hot water springs are best of the combo that can be found in Sikkim, presenting the wow factor of north eastern India.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Do if You’re on Your Period on Your Wedding Day?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/03/period-on-your-wedding-day/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-03T19:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/03/period-on-your-wedding-day</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18057833/388b1bfa-6e2f-11e6-909b-e36c5d673d28.jpg" width="500" height="600">
Wedding Day is the most special day of every girl’s life. So, the special day of your life is about to arrive. Everything is planned, the perfect dress, the most romantic venue of the city, honeymoon destination, and what not? But oops! What’s happening? You suddenly realize your chums are here and you definitely did not invite them to your wedding. Well, the best way to avoid such a situation is to try and fit it into your marriage plans much before the time. If you happen to experience your period on wedding day, a few things can be done to avoid any kind of mishaps.
The first thing to be done is stay calm and composed. Keep a smile pasted to your face and enjoy the day. Here are some tips for you in case you happen to experience period on the most auspicious day of your life:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Rush to the doctor</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18058016/14777b54-6e30-11e6-872f-34f4ccc3da38.jpg" width="600" height="500">
In any case of uneasiness or a disease, all of us look for the doctor. Similarly, if you have these uninvited guests suddenly interrupting the special occasion of your life, doctor’s clinic is not far away! Start taking the pills two weeks before your period is due, it may delay your next period for your day. This might not be a foolproof solution though, but help’s for sure.</p>

<h1>Use a menstrual cup</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18058048/3c0b9786-6e30-11e6-96d6-e95ba80dca33.jpg">
They really do help: The menstrual cups can prove to be great help for the ‘aunt flo’ blunder that just took place. These cups can easily be inserted into the vagina and help cover the opening to the cervix. Tampons can also be used as a backup, otherwise pads are always your best friend during your menstrual cycle. These help prevent leakage. If you want to keep things tidy on your wedding night, the cup can also be inserted prior to sex.</p>

<h1>Make love on your wedding night anyways</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18057878/6d0618ee-6e2f-11e6-960c-e9cdb6fae890.jpg">
Due to extra sensitivity as well as lubrication, some women enjoy being intimate during their menstrual flow whereas, on the other hand, some find it more painful. Well, the whole thing entirely depends upon you and your better half. If your partner is ok with it, just go ahead and have an intercourse. Just make sure to take tiny precautions in order to avoid untidiness, like bring a towel along so that you can place it down to protect the bed.</p>

<p>In short, any of the brides can experience this mishap on the very special day of her life, but not to worry girls! There is always a solution to everything. Just don’t panic too much! Keep calm and tranquil, it’s your day girl! Enjoy it to the fullest and don’t forget to wear a smile all day long. This smile will add on to your glow on the wedding day. Discuss this with your friends and know each other’s experience in case such a thing ever happened to anyone of you.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Momos Point in Delhi]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/03/best-momos-point-in-delhi/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-03T19:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/03/best-momos-point-in-delhi</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17994563/5944851c-6b77-11e6-9c2c-0f5d9d67d482.jpg" width="500" height="600">
Who doesn’t love momos? I think there is hardly any food lover who could say a no to momos. Delhi is a city that offers a wide range of delicious and irresistible momos. While one wonders where to eat best vegetarian momos or best non-vegetarian momos or best fried momos or best tandoori or wheat momos in Delhi, one ought to try following places and give their taste buds a wave of happiness and satisfaction, making it crave for more. Moreover, you will find plenty of street momos in the city of Delhi, a few being:</p>

<!-- more -->


<p><br/>
<br/></p>

<h1>Dilli Haat</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17994566/594f2710-6b77-11e6-9a0f-4bcb608ed319.jpg">
Dilli Haat can be said to be heaven for the momos lovers. Ranging from vegetarian momos in paneer to non-vegetarian momos in pork, there is something for everyone. The Sikkim and Nagaland stall is the best place where you can grab tastiest ever street momos.
Momo’s Point, Kamla Nagar
Momo’s Point in Kamla Nagar serves usual momos with a great taste. In addition to these, they also have Masala Momos, with a desi, spicy touch.</p>

<h1>Brown Sugar, M Block Market,Greater Kailash</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17994563/5944851c-6b77-11e6-9c2c-0f5d9d67d482.jpg">
Located in the M block market of Greater Kailash, New Delhi, Brown Sugar serves some of the taste bud tingling momos of the city. The momos are popular by the name of wheat steamos and are served in different vegetarian as well as non-vegetarian varieties like Chicken, Mushroom, Spinach, and Paneer. Chicken Momos of this little café are a must try.</p>

<h1>Crazy Bruno, Anand Lok Market</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17994564/59461274-6b77-11e6-8f56-90e622620313.jpg">
When it comes to best momos of the city, how can one not remember the one and only name Crazy Bruno. Placed in Anand Lok Market, opposite Gargi College, this place serves a complete assortment of momos you just can’t deny. From Afghani Momos to Makhni Gravy Momos, Tandoori Momos, Malai Momos, Spicy Cheese Momos, and Crispy Chilly Momos, you may fall short of time but you can definitely not fall short of the different kinds of momos platted at this place.</p>

<h1>Dolma Aunty Momos, Lajpat Nagar</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17994568/597910b6-6b77-11e6-963e-4b93d5c1bfd8.jpg">
Dolma Aunty Momos of Central Market, Lajpat Nagar has been selling momos since last 20 years. Aunty’s chicken and paneer momos served with spicy chutney would invoke the foodie in you.</p>

<h1>Chalte Firte, Near DU</h1>

<p><img class="ceneter" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17994565/5946cfac-6b77-11e6-959e-f73fe58ecbb9.jpg">
Situated in Kamala Nagar, covering the vicinity of Delhi University, Chalte Firte serves items like Steamed Butter Masala Momos, Afghani Momos, and Fried Gravy Momos. Being another best momos point of the city, this place does a justice to the delicate dumplings called momos.</p>

<h1>Hawkers, Vasant Kunj</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17994569/597c5302-6b77-11e6-9640-922904481c16.jpg">
‘Hawkers’ is yet another classic food joint in Vasant Kunj area of New Delhi where you can find the most amazingly tasty fried moms. Only a glimpse would water your mouth.</p>

<h1>Tee Dee</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17994570/5984a124-6b77-11e6-8395-0167dfea82ee.jpg">
Perhaps, the best place for momos in Majnu Ka Tilla is Tee Dee, as you will find varieties like soupy momos in vegetarian, steamed, fried in Chicken and beef variants.</p>

<h1>Noodle Bowl, Dwarka</h1>

<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17994561/593cfc7a-6b77-11e6-9037-f117fe5a94be.jpg" width="300" height="400">
Noodle Bowl is your place if you are looking for juiciest pork momos in Dwarka. High on flavor, they offer quantities that are generous enough to satisfy your stomach. Also, they offer a home a delivery.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Just Educators but Role Models: Make Them Feel Special This Teachers Day!]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/03/teachers-day/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-03T13:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/03/teachers-day</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/18225112/167eff1c-7209-11e6-99cf-c6beb0d2bec8.jpg" width="500" height="600">
During our school days we had so many friends that we had to cut short the names of who to call on our birthdays and family
functions but when we grow up, after college and come into the corporate world, people get busy in their respective lives.
There are just a few friends left who remain close to our heart but our educators, our teachers are the ones who have thousands of people who remember them for ages.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/18225115/16879b40-7209-11e6-85f4-38703cabe40d.jpg" title="" >
Teachers moud us into respectable human beings and give us such life lessons that help us in our lives.
Isn’t it our moral duty to remember our teachers on their special day and make them feel special?
Teachers are the inspirational figures who give us the courage to constantly keep moving.
However, take out time from your corporate lives and make them feel special this teacher’s day.</p>

<h1>Token of appreciation</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/18225113/1680c78e-7209-11e6-8655-86c4fd6adbad.jpg">
Teachers deserve appreciation as they remember thousands of names, they know what we are best at and our weakness as well.
Take out time and order a gift of gratitude for them like a basket full of their favorite things (if at all, you remember what they like), you can also draw and make a special card for them or a scrapbook (if you have images with your teacher).
This gesture of appreciation will make the teachers feel it down their spine and will be a wonderful sign of gratification.</p>

<h1>Think creatively</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/18225111/15fff71c-7209-11e6-844a-887ddeb977b8.gif">
This is the era where people are not able to spare time for their families, they are so busy and engrossed in the daily chores that maintaining relations becomes a complicated task.
You don’t have to go out of the way but you can simply make your teachers feel special by making a creative picture and sending it on their Facebook with a heartwarming wish or a heartfelt message for them, make it certain that your teachers acknowledge the message and wishes.</p>

<h1>Celebrate together</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/18225119/364b684e-7209-11e6-9d82-5aa61b44ad9c.jpg">
Teachers are more than just our mentors, they are our role models. And if we can surprise them by going out of the way to meet them, nothing like it. Celebrate their special day and make them feel that they are important for you.
These are small-small things that make a huge difference.</p>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/18225114/1682527a-7209-11e6-9fe5-d168a5769271.jpg">
We might consider these things as trivial but for our teachers, it makes a huge difference for them when their pass-out students remember them and make them feel on the seventh heaven. This is just an act of reverence to make them feel wanted and upright. If you think about the school and college days; don’t you remember how your teachers molded into what you are today?
How they took pains to help you in growing up? On this teacher’s day, make them feel special and watch a beam appear across their faces.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cheap & Best Hangout Points for College Students]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/26/cheap-and-best-hangout-points-for-college-students/"/>
    <updated>2016-08-26T19:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/26/cheap-and-best-hangout-points-for-college-students</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17888542/0f3eca66-6949-11e6-8f18-06eaa8d79017.jpg" width="500" height="600">
Every college group has its own hangout point, which is special to them. In every college memory, each rind of gossip takes place in food joint or a café. While we converse about any big or small topic, the snacks and fast food are present as our companion. Their pep is not less than the college where the students study. To continue their vivacity, here we bring to you some of the cheapest and the best hangout points for college students in Delhi.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Rico’s</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17888539/0d9e1770-6949-11e6-97b2-0863ca823b02.jpg">
Great food accompanied with super fast service and what not? Perky interiors, amazing aura further add to the charisma of the place. Although the café is little expensive than other cafés, but the delicious food served here does full justice to whatever amount one spends here. The must try of this place is chicken stroganoff and the black forest waffle, which you could definitely not resist.</p>

<h1>Keventer’s</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17888714/e15930ae-6949-11e6-8dc5-314e44f37b70.jpg">
Well, milk shakes are our all time comrades. To cheer up your mood nothing can be better than a chilled glass of milk shake topped with your favorite ice cream. Keventer’s situated in Connaught Place is the favorite milk shake hub of the college students. Even though the infrastructure of this place is not too well organized but it still stands strong and serves the best in all the aspects.</p>

<h1>Amar Colony Market</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17888792/434abe2c-694a-11e6-998a-8e4bd76987b5.jpg">
Known for its aunty ke fries and Lebanese shawarma, amar colony market offers such scrumptious and pocket-friendly food items that you just can’t move away without trying at least one dish. This place offers a variety of eatables having something for anyone and everyone.</p>

<h1>Crazy Bruno</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17888814/5cf108f4-694a-11e6-8612-cf5506b2636e.jpg">
The momos lovers just can’t afford to miss this eatery located in Anand Lok Market, opposite Gargi college. They serve different varieties of momos including Malai Momos, Afghani Momos, Crispy Chilly Momos, Makhni Gravy Momos, Tandoori Momos, and not to miss Spicy Cheese Momos. Other than a complete assortment of momos, the menu also includes sandwiches, noodles, authentic Muglai food, as well as salads.</p>

<h1>QD’s</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17888826/77b48cba-694a-11e6-82ab-ddca9634cce2.jpg">
Perhaps the first place in Delhi to have given momos a tandoori flavor and twist, QD’s serves lip smacking chicken as well as vegetarian momos. One can relish their delicious taste at its outlets in North Campus and Satyaniketan.</p>

<h1>Dilli Haat</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17888873/c1dca106-694a-11e6-98c3-cedb8cf92f7f.jpg">
A place that offers unique flavors of India, Dilli Haat has various food stalls offering delicacies to taste. At the same time, you can shop exciting things from different state stalls. Being one of the most lively places of Delhi, this place is the center to many events and performances that can be a good past time.</p>

<h1>India Gate</h1>

<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17888984/7c4a4926-694b-11e6-9e4e-9d2e627eba83.jpg" width="500" height="200">
While talking of the hangout destinations in Delhi, how can anyone forget about the famous India Gate. The alluring atmosphere and strolling the art galleries and museums around feels amazing. The place offers an amazing fusion of patriotic and romantic feelings. The cheap street food around is worth giving a try. All in all, this place deserves a hangout while in Delhi.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best & Budget-free Pubs and Night-out Restaurants in Delhi]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/26/best-and-budget-free-pubs-and-night-out-restaurants-near-north-campus-and-south-campus/"/>
    <updated>2016-08-26T19:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/26/best-and-budget-free-pubs-and-night-out-restaurants-near-north-campus-and-south-campus</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18011846/78bc2424-6bd4-11e6-81ce-d64c0a77f0b9.jpg" width="500" height="600">
Going out for night outs and partying is such a cool thing to do in the coolest city of Delhi. This is the reason why most of the youngsters love coming to this city for their higher education. Yet another thing that just can’t be ignored is the very little money in the pocket during the college time. At one point, you might feel as if you are in complete recession. But not to worry! For the collegians, there are many cool places where boozing and partying can totally be pocket friendly. Here is a list of some of the best as well as the budget free pubs and night out restaurants near North Campus and South Campus in Delhi.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>My Bar Lounge and Restaurant</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18011845/78b5bf08-6bd4-11e6-80f5-0fe5203a15fb.jpg">
Located in Connaught Place, My Bar is filled with so many college students that it can be called as their second home. The reason why this place never falls short of customers is the fact that it is actually reasonable and the collegians can easily have the best time boozing here by spending little amount of money.</p>

<h1>Sam’s Café</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18012087/94c1b444-6bd5-11e6-9cd4-414c3314b07e.jpg">
This place sits in the main bazaar of Paharganj and probably the best place to chill and relax. Accompanied by voyagers as well as foreign nationals, this is a cool place, where after having your drinks and stuff, you can go up to the rooftop and relish the alluring view of Daryaganj.</p>

<h1>Pocket Bar</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18012167/f4ff609a-6bd5-11e6-8118-93d176b92422.jpg" width="700" height="450">
A part of the Vasant Square Mall, Vasant Kunj, Pocket Bar sounds so much like friendly to your pocket. The dark red hue of the place gives it a classy retro look, the ones that could be seen in old movies. This place offers ‘happy hours’ that go up to 12 hours. This happy hour can fetch you amazing deals on your drinks and snacks, letting you have the time of your life.</p>

<h1>Big Banana</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18011847/78bdb532-6bd4-11e6-9fc8-627d35685f45.jpg">
The moment we think of night clubs in Delhi, how can Saket not click our minds? Big Banana is an amazing place if you want to visit a lounge that has a spacious bar and is tranquil, at the same time.</p>

<h1>Skooter</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18012877/0595c2b6-6bd9-11e6-858e-0044cb6d871b.jpg">
A nightclub inside Hotel Samrat, New Delhi, this place is popular for Delhi’s premiere crowd. Themed with black and pink décor, Skooter has two floors. The ground floor is for normal entry whereas the first floor is meant for VIPs.</p>

<h1>Garage Inc.</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18012752/7bdd7a0a-6bd8-11e6-97b1-629fd25a5c42.jpg" width="700" height="450">
A budget-philic, all day breakfast menu that is 24x7 ‘happy hours’ can be found nowhere but in Hauz Khas Village. Smoking and chilling at the Garage Inc. can be less costly as compared to other pubs in Hauz Khas Village. The indoor, outdoor, as well as the balcony seats promise to provide you amazing boozing experience.</p>

<h1>Urban Hub</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18012471/38bf9e84-6bd7-11e6-9925-ae5dc3e4e0aa.jpg" width="700" height="450">
Trending in North Campus, Urban Hub is filled with college students. It is a fancy place that offers drinks and snacks at affordable rates. They provide flavored hookah as well.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ragged Jeans Trend to Follow, This Fall!]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/19/the-ragged-jeans-trend-to-follow-this-fall/"/>
    <updated>2016-08-19T09:45:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/19/the-ragged-jeans-trend-to-follow-this-fall</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798197/d92b4bb6-65ec-11e6-9268-e8c738640615.jpg" width="500" height="400" title="High neck blouse" >
Distressed denim has never truly left style and tore pants are the simplest approach to accomplish the look. Infusing a component of road wear edge into your easygoing day wear has never been simpler. The tore jean is likely more flexible than you might suspect.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Tore pants are a definitive gesture to summer and with first look at hotter climate to come, now is the ideal time to consider redesigning your closet. Whether you decide on the inconspicuous choice of essentially distressing your denim or totally drench yourself in the pattern and tear and torque your pants into something taking after bothered shorts, it is a promise that can make the tore jean work for you.</p>

<ol>
<li><p>All alone, tore pants and a straightforward sweater are super easygoing. Be that as it may, include a statement neckband and heels. You will hence have a marvelous outfit.
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798198/d92fe8d8-65ec-11e6-87f3-a01d7455a81c.jpg"></p></li>
<li><p>Front-tuck an old-fashioned shirt into thin pulverized pants and put on booties – moment chic outfit.</p></li>
<li><p>You can simply keep things super easygoing with a cardigan, and tennis shoes. The way to make this look less bumpy is to wear perfectly sized pants and include some charming frill.
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798199/d934f788-65ec-11e6-80c9-4c48a3e771fd.jpg"></p></li>
<li><p>Wear high-waist torn denim with a sparkly crop top for some genuine marvelousness.</p></li>
<li><p>In hotter climate, include level shoes and a flowy kimono top for the easygoing look.</p></li>
<li><p>Include glitz top and beautiful heels for a basic watch that still emerges and makes you the center of attraction.
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798201/d93d81dc-65ec-11e6-8b81-e21668c88b4a.jpg"></p></li>
<li><p>Pair your torn pants with oxford shoes for an adorable outfit.</p></li>
<li><p>Tuck in front, a designed sweater into your torn denim and include heels for the ideal spring outfit.
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798200/d936d454-65ec-11e6-99c9-193ec6f9a221.jpg"></p></li>
<li><p>Some way or another, you must learn to style those much loved shoes, tore pants, and a sweatshirt to look ludicrously cool.</p></li>
</ol>


<p>In the event that you were still in any uncertainty regarding how flexible the tore pants drift truly is, look to any semblance of these road style trends and styling options. They demonstrate to us that ripped pants are easy to pull off and work with a scope of styles. Whether you&rsquo;re deciding on a keen look and dress your tore pants up with a jacket, dress down for a more easygoing look with a plain bit of knitwear. You can also tear your pants directly down into shorts for an even comfortable and a never ending trendy style, the conceivable outcomes are inestimable.</p>

<p>In this manner, on that note, in case you&rsquo;re in any uncertainty that the tore jean is a short lived pattern, you&rsquo;d not be right. Distressed denim has been around for some time and it&rsquo;s not going anyplace in a rush. It&rsquo;s a look that&rsquo;ll take you through each season from spring into summer and once more into winter. Prepare your tweezers and have scrounged in your tool kit for some great quality sandpaper. Torn pants are enormous for Spring/Summer and on the off chance that you don&rsquo;t take after this recommendation, then let it  be an all alone head.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Denim Brigade that You Cannot Miss, This Fall!]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/19/denim-brigade-that-you-cannot-miss-this-fall/"/>
    <updated>2016-08-19T09:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/19/denim-brigade-that-you-cannot-miss-this-fall</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798143/745a2a54-65ec-11e6-90c2-0acac849f0e1.jpg" width="500" height="400" title="High neck blouse" >
Denim is a kind of cotton material known for its utilization in pants and other garments. It utilizes a solid twill weave with a trademark corner to corner ribbing. Initially utilized for laborers' garments, denim is presently pervasive and has even entered the universe of high form. About everybody has no less than one article of clothing made of this fabric in the storage room nowadays.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Style today is deficient without denim. Denim comes in all structures, looks and washes to coordinate with each dress. It is hard to trust that the same denim was initially utilized in dress for the jeans and overalls worn by mineworkers on the west coast (US).</p>

<h2>1.  Dry Denim</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798142/744c4498-65ec-11e6-92c4-ee368d33df10.jpg">
Dry or crude denim, rather than washed denim, is a denim fabric that is not washed in the wake of being colored amid its creation. Most denim is washed subsequent to being made into a piece of attire. It is done so keeping in mind the end goal to make it milder and to wipe out any shrinkage which could bring about a thing to not fit after the proprietor washes it. Notwithstanding being washed, non-dry denim is some of the time falsely distressed to accomplish a well-used in look.</p>

<h2>2.  Selvage Denim</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798143/745a2a54-65ec-11e6-90c2-0acac849f0e1.jpg">
Selvage denim is a sort of denim which frames a spotless normal edge that does not unwind. It is ordinarily introduced in the unwashed or crude state. Normally, the selvage edges will be situated along the out crease of the jeans, making it unmistakable when sleeves are worn. Despite the fact that selvage denim is not totally synonymous with unwashed denim, the nearness of selvage commonly suggests that the denim utilized is of a higher quality.</p>

<h2>3.  Stretch Denim</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798146/7460792c-65ec-11e6-879d-08611058cb2f.jpg">
It is more often around 98% cotton and 2% Spandex for a touch of that easy-going stretch that we as a whole love. This mix gives you awesome simplicity and in the meantime some backing for those inconvenient spots you aren&rsquo;t so partial to like around the hips or thighs. Stretch denim pants are one of the quickest developing sections of the ladies' business sector for pants makers.</p>

<h2>4.  Poly Denim</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798145/746041f0-65ec-11e6-9136-e3a3d652c623.jpg">
These mixes engage the individuals who like the look of denim yet favor polyester mixes that wash and dry rapidly and are lighter in weight and somewhat dressier. These for the most part speak to a somewhat more established business sector, but on the other hand are discovering support as pant suits when the look is intended to be dressy yet easygoing.</p>

<h2>5.  Ramie Cotton Denim</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798144/745e09c6-65ec-11e6-8d06-cb290d9bf091.jpg">
Ramie cotton denims are found in an assortment of mixes, with a wide value fluctuation. Ramie is a plant fiber more often than not included in light of the fact that it decreases wrinkling and adds a smooth radiance to the fabric. It isn&rsquo;t as solid as cotton and this is the main reason that it must be mixed with this more grounded material so as to stand up as a denim material.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stunningly Sensual Full Sleeve Blouses to Make a Fashion Statement at a Wedding]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/18/blouses-to-make-a-fashion-statement-at-a-wedding/"/>
    <updated>2016-08-18T18:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/18/blouses-to-make-a-fashion-statement-at-a-wedding</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17774637/223b482c-6572-11e6-98f8-609c71fadaa8.jpg" width="500" height="400" title="High neck blouse" >
The wedding season is here once more. Sprucing up and staying aware of the most recent pattern is the close-by errand for the women. There are such a variety of blouse plans and patterns out there in the business sector, yet there&rsquo;s something about full-sleve blouses or cholis that make them look so rich and tasteful. Here are some full-sleeve choli outlines to help you put forth an agreeable style expression.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p><br />
<br />
<br />
<br /></p>

<h2>1.   Brocade blouse</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17774633/2222c900-6572-11e6-9623-ccdadca7df61.jpg" width="600" height="500">
It is surmised that brocades will be the pattern this wedding season. The brocade silk material is immaculate to make a full-sleeve choli and to make you look classy. It can run well with a lehenga or an excellent silk saree.</p>

<h2>2.   Net with weaving</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17774634/2228ebbe-6572-11e6-87c8-46efcbe6d8da.jpg" width="600" height="400">
Need to demonstrate some skin, yet need to go for a full-sleeve? Settle on a net blouse that has weaving on it. This looks tasteful and rich in each sense.</p>

<h2>3.  Princess cut</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17774635/2230c0e6-6572-11e6-996c-8f65d880810f.jpg" width="600" height="400">
When you are wearing a full-sleeve choli, the best outline you can have is a princess cut neck. It is flexible and sophisticated. It gives a feminine touch to the outfit and shows off your slim neck.</p>

<h2>4.    High neck with heavy weaving</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17774637/223b482c-6572-11e6-98f8-609c71fadaa8.jpg" width="600" height="600">
These plans are the ideal mates for the individuals who need to go light on their gems. The choli itself gets to be an adornment for this situation. While whatever is left of the blouse can be embellished with weaving, the neck is given the fundamental consideration with vast weaving and stone work. Al this makes it look like a choker neckpiece.</p>

<h2>5.   Boat Necks</h2>

<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17774636/223a3220-6572-11e6-89ae-777e380ebd70.jpg" width="370" height="260">
These necks are assuming control over the weddings since last season. Boat neck cholis are the most ideal approach to flaunt your thin neck. Simply go ahead and get yourself a choli with this outline to continue through to the end of the gathering.</p>

<p><br />
<br /></p>

<h2>6.   Jacket style and cropped top style cholis</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17774638/22683620-6572-11e6-8225-d4492937df5f.jpg">
Need to style up that super heavy and sarkling weaved saree or lehenga? Experiment with the coat style choli that is certain to make you snappy and diverse. The youthful and energetic women can decide on a better time alternative with regards to choli plans. Select to wear a slick crop top. Observe these picks and you may experience passionate feelings for them.</p>

<h2>7.   Full adorned choli</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17774639/226efc62-6572-11e6-85ea-cbefd6998ae1.jpg">
A full-sleeve plan gives an imperial princess look. Furthermore, when it is a full-decorated choli with string and stone work, nothing can beat the look.</p>

<h2>8.   Vintage and pastel cholis</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17774640/227592e8-6572-11e6-9e23-45ccb347fd3b.jpg">
Take a trek back in time and attempt these vintage roused cholis this season. You surely will cherish the modest effortlessness it offers. Do you get a kick out of the chance to keep it unobtrusive at the wedding? Select powder pastels that are in pattern.</p>

<p>Full-sleeve cholis and blouses when worn in the correct way can highlight your excellence and class. With such a large number of staggering decisions, you surely will now be prepared with the right patterns for the weddings lined up this season.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Subtle white Top Trend You Can’t Get Enough Of!]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/18/the-subtle-white-top-trend-you-cannot-get-enough-of/"/>
    <updated>2016-08-18T10:00:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/18/the-subtle-white-top-trend-you-cannot-get-enough-of</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798251/48160516-65ed-11e6-9828-7351be57173e.jpg" width="500" height="400" title="High neck blouse" >
Why do a reversal to the rudiments? This season, it&rsquo;s about unobtrusive overhauls, similar to a wrapped abdomen, a cut set pattern, or a topsy-turvy hemline to liven up the exemplary shirt we once acquired from the young men. Obviously shirts are the things you presumably own the greater part of. Also, white is the color of the time, the most wanted and the best of all. So given below are the five essential classifications of white tops. This will give you a reasonable thought of what shirts will be the most adaptable and practical, and afterward from that point you can pick pieces that fit your own style.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>1. Button Ups</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798250/480fd196-65ed-11e6-9d17-b0f5c21c22b0.jpg">
I used to think button ups were excessively proficient search for a general mother like me, yet they&rsquo;re truly a staple that each lady needs in her wardrobe. They come in a wide range of hues and materials; however a great white button up top and lightweight denim is truly the main thing that you require. They are awesome for layering under a sweater, wearing open over a dress, tied at the midsection, tucked into a skirt, or just without anyone else&rsquo;s input with a couple of pants.</p>

<h2>2. Shirts</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798251/48160516-65ed-11e6-9828-7351be57173e.jpg">
In spite of the fact that button ups are additionally considered shirts, there are also different sorts of dressier tops. They&rsquo;re certainly their very own classification. These are the shirts that claim a large portion of your wardrobe. They can arrive in a million distinct assortments and styles, so this is the place you can have a great time and pick pieces that fit your identity. These are the best pieces for dressing down with a couple of shoes and pants, or sprucing up with a couple of thin pants and heels for a night out in the town.</p>

<h2>3. T shirts and crop tops</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798252/4818dfde-65ed-11e6-94e7-d9c7b1a5c0f1.jpg">
Who can live without T-shirts? They are staples for easygoing wear, yet can likewise be spruced up with a coat and heels or matched with a pencil skirt. Also, the crop tops are the latest in trend to flaunt your way to a party. Ensure your storeroom has some realistic tees and crop tops in white color.</p>

<h2>4. Sweaters</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798254/481f6a20-65ed-11e6-9a4d-283d15b43171.jpg">
Larger than usual, trimmed, long sleeved, short-sleeved; sweaters come in all varieties. A white sweater looks cool with any dress you wear and that is why it is in vogue today. Pick your most loved styles. They are incredible for layering over a dress and wearing with a skirt or pants etc.</p>

<h2>5. Layering Pieces</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798253/481ec084-65ed-11e6-93ef-ea4937829b7c.jpg">
These are the complete pieces that each lady additionally needs in her storage room. Cardigans and coats are the top two decisions to decide upon when going out. I cherish the look of an overcoat tossed over a tee dressed over a flowy shirt. Cardigans and coats have a great deal of variety, so make sure you pick the ones which you feel can go with maximum number of your dresses.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[#TrendAlert: Dare to Dungaree?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/13/dungaree-outfit/"/>
    <updated>2016-08-13T19:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/13/dungaree-outfit</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17643124/c4a69736-617d-11e6-9281-0fc81faa40ee.jpg" width="600" height="500">
Dress ‘em up, or dress ‘em down, dungarees are the new wardrobe staple. Frequently
spotted on celebrities and bloggers alike, dungarees make for a fun, chic addition to your
style. Why? They instantly amp up swag quotient, and are utterly easy to carry. With the
chills setting in slowly, now is the perfect time to lend a brand new spin to your style with
this hot fashion pick.
To help you ease into the trend, here go four stunning variants of the dungaree that you can
opt for. Buckle up, and soak in all the inspiration you can:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>The classic distressed dungaree</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17643050/571a8b52-617b-11e6-88e2-0577a08b960e.jpg" width="500" height="400">
Love distressed denims? Take them a notch higher with distressed dungarees that are the
perfect pick for a fun day out with your gal pals. Team them up with this season’s hottest
fashion favourite – cropped tees, and slip into a pair of white oxfords or sneakers to
complete the casual chic look.</p>

<h1>Dungaree shorts</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17643049/56ee73dc-617b-11e6-9e46-3e9486348c04.jpg" width="500" height="400">
Showcase your fun side (and, those toned gams) with dungaree shorts that look playfully
flirty! Couple them with a graphic tank top and sneakers to lend just the finishing touch your
look needs. If not denim, pick a printed pair to add a dash of feminine, and swap the
sneakers for strappy sandals!</p>

<h1>Formal black dungaree</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17643048/56a87468-617b-11e6-8103-d34b1c3eb0b7.jpg" width="600" height="600">
On your next evening out, ditch the classic cocktail dress and grab a pair of formal black
dungarees to make for some serious power dressing. Wear them over a crisp white shirt,
and a pair of pointy stiletto heels to maintain the perfect balance between formal and</p>

<h1>Layered up</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17643051/571b479a-617b-11e6-85e5-5679b30287a0.jpg" width="500" height="400">
Scarves, jackets, shrugs and even overcoats – dungarees go well with each of the layers,
thereby, giving your look an all new edge. For a casual event, wrap a statement contrast
scarf around your neck and style your hair into a high-rise messy bun. For a formal event, on
the other hand, simply rest your jacket or overcoat on your shoulders and opt for pointy
heels to complete the look.</p>

<p>No longer tricky, are they? Rush now, flaunt your love for dungarees by incorporating trendy
accessories to team them up with, and leave a long-lasting impression on your onlookers.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delhi College Fashion Trends]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/28/delhi-college-fashion-trends/"/>
    <updated>2016-07-28T19:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/28/delhi-college-fashion-trends</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17203889/be07ffac-54bf-11e6-8377-80ef1dffe9ba.jpg" width="600" height="600" title="Delhi College Fashion Trends" >
Along with the monsoons comes the new session of colleges which simply means a whole new life. All the new friendships, heart aches, class notes, mass bunk etc are waiting for you. Apart from all these things, one major thing that is gonna change is that you no longer have to wear the same uniform daily, college gives you the freedom to wear the trendiest outfits and break the code of regular uniform. As the college new session starts, here I am suggesting you 10 styles which are trending this season.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Palazzos</h1>

<p><img class="right" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17203914/de738874-54bf-11e6-8d23-19ca5e2eb94a.jpg" title="Palazzos" >
Palazzos are really trending and seems like everyone from women to young gals are in love with them. For summers, Palazzos are the best choice as they are flowy wide legged pants. You can wear plain palazzos or printed ones with any kind of top like long and short kurtas, halter neck, tuck in tops etc.</p>

<h5>Where to get: In Delhi you can easily get a palazzo from any street market like Sarojini Nagar, Janpath, Kamla Nagar Market</h5>

<h5>Price Range: Rs. 200 to Rs. 500</h5>

<h1>Scarves</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17204009/8829fb28-54c0-11e6-827d-4738e167d1f5.jpg" width="650" height="500" title="Scarves" >
Whether you are wearing a kurti, ethnic skirt or a top, you can easily accessorize it with a patterned scarf. There are various ways of carrying a scarf, if you don’t know how to tie a scarf then you can easily find many video tutorials online.  You can buy scarfs in different patterns like polka dots, striped ones, zig zag ones etc and create a new style every day to your college.</p>

<h5>Where to get: All the street markets of Delhi</h5>

<h5>Price Range: Rs. 35 to Rs. 150</h5>

<h1>Ripped Jeans</h1>

<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17203963/38b1959c-54c0-11e6-889b-32a56a9ff937.jpg" width="500" height="350" title="Ripped Jeans" >
Yeah and this one is really being loved by the college going gals as it gives them a rockstar like feel. No longer that boring normal jeans, make an exciting entry to your college on the first day wearing these highly fashionable ripped jeans. You can DIY any normal jeans into a rockstar ripped jeans.</p>

<h5>Where to get: Janpath</h5>

<h5>Price Range: Rs. 250 to Rs. 500</h5>

<h1>Kurtis</h1>

<p><img class="right" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17204139/5d921a5c-54c1-11e6-8d9e-674cf4aaf007.jpg" width="500" height="700" title="Kurtis" >
Wear it with palazzos, leggings, ethnic skirts, jeans or anything else, Kurti is certainly the best choice for Summers. It’s light and comfortable to wear. And yeah you can also style it up with trendy scarves, Rajasthani jhola bags, cute little jhumkis and juttis or Kohlapuri chappals.</p>

<h5>Where to get: Janpath, Kamla Nagar Market, Palika Bazaar</h5>

<h5>Price Range: Rs. 250 to Rs. 500</h5>

<p><img src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17204152/70d46232-54c1-11e6-9540-a7d752da9c9a.jpg" title="Fashion Accessories" ></p>

<h1>Fashion Accessories</h1>

<p>Yes, now you are in college and you can definitely flaunt your accessories without being called as “ye dekho school me jyda style mar rahi hai ladki”, rather you would be labeled as a fashionista. In Delhi you can have so many accessories like beaded neck pieces, scarves, sunglasses, metallic bangles etc at low price from various street markets.</p>

<h5>Where to get: All the Street Markets of Delhi</h5>

<h5>Price Range: Rs. 10 to Rs. 250</h5>

<p>So, follow these few Delhi college fashion trends and become a rockstar in your group.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Famous Street Shops in Bangalore]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/26/5-famous-street-shops-in-banglore/"/>
    <updated>2016-07-26T19:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/26/5-famous-street-shops-in-banglore</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136045/b69cb962-5350-11e6-98c0-ec12e3b8df76.jpg" width="600" height="700">
Bangalore is a city that has n number of options for the perceptive bargain street shoppers. Be it colorful flower markets or the crowded second hand stores, there is something for everyone. The local street market of a city is something that can never be compared to anything else in the world. The joy of shopping gives an amazing shopping experience. The lively sounds, smells, and the wonderful sights of the city further make these shopping streets different from others. From clothes, accessories, to books, street food, medicines, flowers, and what not, Bangalore has a separate street market for everything that one would like to buy. Here is a list of 5 famous street shops in Bangalore where the shopaholics would love to go:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Commercial Street</h1>

<p><img class="right" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136023/8bad626a-5350-11e6-94d4-303c018aa217.jpg" width="500" height="500">
Commercial Street is one of the most popular shopping areas that has stores selling every style of clothing, accessories, jewellery, shoes, and much more. Every time you pay a visit to this street, you will find something new to shop for. All you need to do is bargain to your heart’s content. The more you bargain here, the less amount you will have to pay for the items that you purchase.</p>

<h1>Avenue Road</h1>

<p>The avenue road is an eternally crowded one way street that is famous for food carts, stationary shops, shops selling jewellery, and textiles. It is the home to such interesting things that no one can find anywhere else in the city. Here, second hand books are available at cheap rates and the ones who want to sell unused books are also welcomed. This makes it an ideal place for students as well as the book lovers due to the buying and selling of second hand books.
<img src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136130/3b64417e-5351-11e6-9df7-f47ac1f48628.jpg"></p>

<h1>Chickpet</h1>

<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136297/2593edc6-5352-11e6-847d-ed75721a53b7.jpg">
<img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136301/2836b3d8-5352-11e6-920c-bba3b91475b9.jpg">
Chickpet is counted among the city’s oldest commercial districts and is famous for a wide variety of saris as well as wholesale dress materials that are available at reasonable prices. Also, you don’t need to compromise with the quality. Bangles at Balepet, jewellery at Raja market, and locally made musical instruments at Nagarthapet are also worth a purchase when you visit this place.
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136308/2cc06c78-5352-11e6-8cd2-d2f02494d065.jpg"></p>

<h1>Gandhi Bazaar</h1>

<p>Being city’s most vibrant streets, this market is known for trinkets, traditional religious items, textiles, silk saris, and local medicines. The best form of this shopping place can best be seen in the evenings and at the time of festivals. Offering lip smacking street food, a large number of people are gathered at the popular eateries, the most famous being Vidyarthi Bhavan.
<img src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136480/40b20cd6-5353-11e6-9f81-2d7755273e49.jpg"></p>

<h1>City Market</h1>

<p><img class="right" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136582/e2cf79c2-5353-11e6-81a6-9f2df47fb356.jpg" width="500" height="500">
The city market is famous for colorful flowers, vegetables, and fresh fruits and several kilos of flowers are sold here every day. Vendors all over the city buy their stock from this market. The quality of flora, vegetables, and fruits make this place a must visit. If you get here early in the morning, you will be able to buy the best produce. The condition of the place is little messy but the fresh stock available here is a must to see and buy.
<img src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136611/0af7b400-5354-11e6-98ab-de4a6d9144f3.jpeg"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Fashion Accessories for Men]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/24/top-fashion-accessories-for-men/"/>
    <updated>2016-07-24T23:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/24/top-fashion-accessories-for-men</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17110837/7c7bebc0-52bc-11e6-881d-6f39d8bbc336.jpg" width="450" height="600" title="Fashion Accessories for Men" >
Most of the people will concur with the epigram &ldquo;women&rsquo;s fashion is much more diverse than men!!&rdquo;. But who says accessories are for women only? Here are top 10 accessories that can add flavour and color to any outfit to fit the preferences of any men out there.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>1. Watch</h2>

<p><img class="right" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17089993/b960e928-5249-11e6-8d5b-81279774db38.jpg" width="250" height="200">
A wrist watch is the most conventional accessory a man can invest in. It exudes simplicity while adding style to your personality. it is one of the most acceptable men&rsquo;s accessory. Mechanical, chronograph, leather strap watches are the latest trends this season.</p>

<h2>2. Tie</h2>

<p>A tie is one accessory that adds life to any men&rsquo;s attire. Various mutants include bow-tie, necktie, ascots. A tie radiates class and confidence. Pair up your suit with multicolor, printed , textured, silk ties this summer.
<img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17089994/bb5c44d4-5249-11e6-933b-584c8de947e3.jpg" width="400" height="400"></p>

<h2>3. Pocket Squares</h2>

<p>Regardless of this recently added fashion statement pocket squares have become a perfect addition to men&rsquo;s wardrobe. How to pair them up?? well chose a totally contrast pocket square. no matchy-matchy!!GO for a colorful choice that isn&rsquo;t too in-your-face.
<img class="right" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17090004/ca3d60d2-5249-11e6-8a99-5aa692b481b3.jpg" width="300" height="200"></p>

<h2>4. Wallet</h2>

<p>Black and brown leather wallets for men are perennial. The Hobo Millie Clutch and Elephant wallets are gaining popularity these days. Totally cool isnt it?
<img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17090007/cde62ce6-5249-11e6-9f52-04feb9ea4fa2.jpg"></p>

<h2>5. Money clip</h2>

<p>This accessory offers a simple and convenient approach to handle your cash. Its graceful and elegant style makes it a great alternative to carry your money. While other men are still confused as to what is better, a wallet or a money clip, you grab your painted m-clip, chrome or silver plated money clip to earn brownie points in impressing ladies out there!
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17089995/bdeff6f0-5249-11e6-9058-4ef2de814599.jpg" width="500" height="200"></p>

<h2>6. Card Holders</h2>

<p>Card holders can be a superb approach to speak to a level of professional skill. They also serve as a great way to gift a business associate. Stainless steel and custom fabric card holders are go-go this season.
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17090000/c29821dc-5249-11e6-87ac-53a347664d83.jpg" width="600" height="500"></p>

<h2>7. Jewellery for men</h2>

<p><img class="right" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17089998/c068dbfe-5249-11e6-843b-8982834315f5.jpg">
Yes unsual it seems,, but jewellery for men is gaining popularity now-a-days. Common jewellery for men is the wedding ring. THe most effective way for a man to carry jewellery is to be comfortable about it. Ear studs, copper bracelets, lapel pins, beaded necklace are some well executed jewellery intended for men.</p>

<h2>8. Belt</h2>

<p>Belt is a safe and easy pick accessory for men. It no longer serves as a tool for holding mens trouser but a great style statement. Wide buckles and a webbed, fabric version with a double-D buckle fastening works well for this summer.
<img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17090002/c430ffbe-5249-11e6-826f-77f4fee2771a.jpg" width="750" height="400"></p>

<h2>9. Sunglasses</h2>

<p>Sunglasses, aviators, shades are one of the accessory men wear on their face. They are a must have for glamorous, High Fashion look. Tortoiseshell frames and sleek metal are latest fashion trends..
<img class="right" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17090005/cbff5c18-5249-11e6-9fdb-d111dd013d44.jpg"></p>

<h2>10. Cuff links</h2>

<p>Well you must first know what are cufflinks?? Cufflinks are tools for fastening shirt cuffs closed. They add variety and shape to men&rsquo;s outfit. Chain link and stud cufflinks are perfect for all your wedding functions and other formal occasions.
<img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17090003/c5e23d82-5249-11e6-8d98-5ec4b1c25279.jpg" width="700" height="500"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tibetan Market for Budget Shopping in Delhi]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/20/tibetan-market-for-budget-shopping-in-delhi/"/>
    <updated>2016-07-20T23:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/20/tibetan-market-for-budget-shopping-in-delhi</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16996255/1f8f8d00-4ece-11e6-94f0-30b4cb3b5cc8.jpeg" width="500" height="650" title="Tibetan Market New Delhi" >
What is the greatest highlight of Delhi shopping? Many may answer, that shopping in the cosmopolitan Delhi malls has revolutionized the shopping experience. But the hidden truth is different. Though the city malls are quite attractive but in comparison to the charm and attraction of the Delhi street markets, it’s nothing. The most convenient proof of the statement is the overcrowded; jam packed areas of the age old traditional markets of Delhi throughout the year.
One of such a traditional market is the Tibetan Market located on the western side of Janpath.  From designer clothing to stylish accessories, home décor to Tibetan artifacts, footwear to woolen clothes get it all in best quality and that too in throw back prices. Seems unbelievable? Well not, the market is one of the most preferred shopping destinations in the capital city.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Historical Truths</h1>

<p><img class="right" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16996521/57465494-4ecf-11e6-9755-343d25be65a8.jpg">
Originally the place was designed to house in Tibetan refugees in 1960. But what initiated as a small locality dedicated to the fugitives soon got transferred into one of the popular shopping locations of the city. It is the rising fame of the market with its cheap price and quality products that it soon became a tourist spot in Delhi and became christened with the name, the Monastery market.
<img src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16996295/4349bcb6-4ece-11e6-834e-701f23c28cec.jpg"></p>

<h1>What remains in Offer for you?</h1>

<p>Though Tibetan market has a host of products to offer, it is known a lot for its resplendent collection of woolen garments. Mostly these are homemade winter wears and they are sold at unbelievable low prices. Shawls, jackets and designer cloaks all remain available here. Apart from winter wears, the next best thing available here is the Tibetan artifacts which includes paintings, antiques, statues, incense , wooden lamps and classical jewellery. Leather products and footwear are also quite cheap here. The small Tibetan world also holds a wide collection of exquisite Lucky charms, Tibetan bric-a-brac , Om danglers, Tibetan souvenirs and many other exclusive products. In a nutshell, it’s Little Tibet away from Tibet.
<img src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16996570/7db09720-4ecf-11e6-8e89-96f858d2deba.jpg"></p>

<h1>Food to Savor in Tibetan Market</h1>

<p>Shoppers usually are great foodies too. And even if they are not, shopping for stretched hours calls for re energizing with delicious food which gets fulfilled in the market with a wide collection of flavors from Tibet. Visit Wongdhen House or Zomsa and enjoy the wide variety of Tibetan foods like chowmein, momo, thupkas etc in its authentic flavor.
So what are you waiting for, get set go to explore the traditionally rich authentic Monastery market. The place is quite close to ISBT flyover and the nearest metro station is Kashmiri Gate. Even the Old Delhi Railway station is based closeby at a distance of 3kms with regular public buses plying towards the market area. The market usually remains open from 11 in the morning and stays buzzing till 8:30 to 9 in the evening. It is functional on all days of the week except Monday.
Undoubtedly, it is one of the cheapest and the best markets in the city and the must visit for all.
<img src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16996600/9ee50246-4ecf-11e6-888a-a90d2332f200.jpg"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2 Best Places to Go Street Shopping in Mumbai]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/19/2-best-places-to-go-street-shopping-in-mumbai/"/>
    <updated>2016-07-19T23:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/19/2-best-places-to-go-street-shopping-in-mumbai</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16958979/837dee66-4e00-11e6-970a-fda168654bf9.jpg" width="500" height="650" title="Street Market Mumbai" >
Mumbai is the City of Dreams for many and certainly a shopper’s delight. Where there are hub of designer shops ranging from Gucci, Louis Vuitton, Burberry to Versache , there are also lot of street markets in Mumbai where you can shop at the cheapest rates. These street markets are very crowded as one can find variety of items here, ranging from first copy of branded clothes, vintage items, Chinese gadgets, books and finger licking street food. Mumbai Street markets are a blessing for all the college going girls as well as the struggling actresses who don’t have much money to buy branded dresses for their photo shoots or celebrity parties. Here I am listing 2 Best Places to Go Street Shopping in Mumbai</p>

<!-- more -->


<p><img src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16959160/458c7db0-4e01-11e6-88ae-27ad32a0b177.jpg"></p>

<h1>Colaba Causeway</h1>

<p>Located in the area of Southern Mumbai, Colaba Causeway is one of the best street markets in Mumbai. This market is a huge one which stretches over several meters and offers all kind of items. You name the item and you can find it here in this market, from artificial jewellery, handicrafts, leather items, sunglasses, stoles and scarves, antique items, books , fashionable clothes, books, bags, bangles to juttis. If you are looking for any personalized gift for a friend then you can also find vendors who can write messages on a single rice grain and engrave it into a locket or key chain. Even if the prices seem to be very reasonable but still you can bargain to a great extent and save your valuable money. Here you will not only find the local people of Mumbai but also foreigners shopping, as this market is only a few kilometers away from Taj Hotel and other iconic landmarks like Gateway of India. If you want to watch a movie then you can also go to one of the oldest Theatre, Regal Cinema, which is located near the market.
<img src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16958980/840beffe-4e00-11e6-9476-f153a98d8c1d.jpg">
<img class="right" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16958978/836996aa-4e00-11e6-9c7d-0592edcaa868.jpg"></p>

<h1>Fashion Street</h1>

<p>Another amazing shopping area in Mumbai is the famous Fashion Street, which perfectly fits its name. Here, you will find all the latest fashion clothes, accessories, cosmetics, and much more at affordable prices. These also include first copies of popular brands. Situated in South Mumbai, this street is a cluster of about 385 street side clothing shops placed on MG Road near Azad Maidan, opposite to Bombay Gymkhana. Along with being a favorite shopping street of the locals as well as the visitors, it is also a popular tourist destination located opposite to VSNL office building at MG Road. As we know, the more you bargain, the better price you fetch for particular apparel, so another advantage of shopping here is that it is well known for bargaining. Not only this, but in order to show concern for environment, in January 2011, as a part of green drive of BMC in collaboration with Fashion Street Shop Owners’ Association, the market at Fashion Street banned the use of plastic bags and polybags, and started using paper bags, made by the training workshop of the National Association of the Blind.
<img src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16959165/4bab41f4-4e01-11e6-9d83-407c45e521c5.jpg">
<img src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16959161/47682a26-4e01-11e6-8515-23d94f37e41f.jpg"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
