<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[JunkJam Blog - Street Market! Fashion! LifeStyle!]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2017-02-08T05:16:29+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Must Haves if Applying for a Foreign College]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2017/02/07/6-must-haves-if-applying-for-a-foreign-college/"/>
    <updated>2017-02-07T19:36:03+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2017/02/07/6-must-haves-if-applying-for-a-foreign-college</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22694596/da270524-ed6d-11e6-816a-b32e9d91c746.jpg" width="470" height="600">
If a study abroad programme seems appealing to you and you’ve applied or been selected and you are now super-duper excited about the abroad adventure. Well, congratulations! The next step is to prepare yourself for the trip. So make a probable questionnaire and kick start your preparation. Here we have complied 6 must have points in your to-do list while planning your trip.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Passport and Visa</h2>

<p>Without a passport, your abroad trip is impossible. If you already owned one, make sure that it’s not expired or won’t expire within 6 months of your intended return to the place you have opted for study. Also, check with other credentials related to the passport.</p>

<p>For newbies, it’s always advisable to apply for it before you plan a trip because the process may take a little time and also cuts the end-time hassle. One can also apply online, make payment and fix a schedule. It’s the easiest way to apply for a passport these days.</p>

<p>In addition to a passport, a traveller may need a visa to visit his/her dream country. Different countries have different visa requirements. In this regards, you will have to do some research and find out the required list. Or you can approach the nearest embassy as well. Like a passport, visa applications also takes several months to process so delay is non-advisable.</p>

<p>Apart from this, there are few countries, which allow the students to enter without a visa for 90 days. So, if your dream country comes under this umbrella than it’ll be an icing on the cake.</p>

<h2>Ensure You Have a Travel Insurance Plan</h2>

<p>While traveling abroad it is a must that you are covered by an accidental insurance plan.</p>

<p>What are Things that a Travel Insurance Covers?</p>

<ul>
<li>Coverage at the time of flight is delayed/cancelled</li>
<li>Lost luggage</li>
<li>Stolen personal belongings</li>
<li>Evacuation in the case of a health emergency or natural disaster</li>
</ul>


<p>Moreover, you can avail health insurance too from the Council of International Educational Exchange.</p>

<h2>Find a Plane Ticket at Cheapest Price: You’re Lucky</h2>

<p>Finding a plane ticket as per your budget and criteria is like an art of timing and luck. The fares are always unexpected and may vary depending on when you want to fly and to where you want to buy your tickets. There are various agencies though, you can compare the fares as well. Additionally, there are student travel agencies too who offer inexpensive tickets for students travelling abroad. You can approach them too.</p>

<h2>Research Your Destination</h2>

<p>Do some homework before flying to your destination. By knowing briefly about your soon-to-be home’s culture, language, history, economy, geography, you can ease your stay there.</p>

<h2>Settle with the Money</h2>

<p>Get an online account of you don’t have. It will be easier for you to use ATM/debit or credit cards to get cash in the local currency.</p>

<p>Moreover, never forget to inform your current bank that you are flying. Otherwise, you risk getting locked out of your account or they might flag it as a fraud.</p>

<p>Also, get some cash with you and don’t forget it the convert to the required currency. You can find the moneychangers at airport or metro stations.</p>

<h2>Finally Start Packing</h2>

<p>Now come to the last stage when you are done with all the documentations and financial requirements, start packing up. Kindly double check with your airlines to learn their luggage allowances to avoid fees. The less baggage you carry, the lesser are the chances of getting charged.</p>

<p>Finally, prepare yourself mentally, cross check everything that you have packed, especially the documents. Though you can never expect to be fully prepared upon arrival, we hope these tips will help you to plan your trip to your dream destination. Happy flight!!!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer 2017 Outfits]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2017/02/05/summer-2017-outfits/"/>
    <updated>2017-02-05T22:08:42+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2017/02/05/summer-2017-outfits</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627708/b1a3f6a6-ebed-11e6-93f4-1eb05a5e5078.jpg" width="500" height="600"></p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Hola Girls!!!</p>

<p>Wohooo!! Its New Year, New Season. So it’s time to reshuffle your wardrobe with new trending outfit.
It is time to take off your coats and heavy jackets to leave them at your wardrobe and start wearing those shorts and miniskirts you have.
The sun begins to gradually appear after being hidden by clouds for months. The weather becomes hotter which forces you to leave those heavy outfits and wear lighter ones.
Spring and summer outfits are completely different from those fall and winter outfits in terms of both colors and materials.
Pastel shades, white shoes/sandals start dominating what we wear in the hot seasons and light materials are used to allow us feel comfortable while walking and moving outside our homes.</p>

<p>To increase your beauty and look fashionable, you have to keep checking out the latest fashion trends that are presented every year and are changed from one season to another.</p>

<p>So here are some of the latest spring – Summer 2017 outfits you must copy right now:</p>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627814/271b37a4-ebef-11e6-9855-52c6499e3952.jpg" width="500" height="700">
<img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627707/b0bb5db0-ebed-11e6-9443-e574894781c1.jpg">
<img class="right lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627704/aec58058-ebed-11e6-9a37-8f3476e39b83.jpg">
<img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627725/c7f4621a-ebed-11e6-9fc9-c1d60b29c4c5.jpg"></p>

<p><img class="right lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627705/af371614-ebed-11e6-92f6-bd42cf5981ab.jpg">
<img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627706/b00955e8-ebed-11e6-9321-1bda3e21f4ed.jpg"></p>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627726/c8eefa72-ebed-11e6-9677-e84b6fab658a.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627815/275d0ea4-ebef-11e6-9b7e-38c2ea739a86.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627712/bfa00a06-ebed-11e6-90e2-978c157088dc.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627713/c15958ac-ebed-11e6-943c-9ca09efcbca7.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627714/c192774a-ebed-11e6-9428-16e1f1b22335.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627715/c1e50186-ebed-11e6-95d4-82260beb2738.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627716/c26c9d8a-ebed-11e6-9d33-0854f20d5850.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627717/c2f39880-ebed-11e6-9268-c70beb62645d.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627718/c426eaea-ebed-11e6-8af0-edaa49a0be94.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627719/c4c6e7fc-ebed-11e6-918f-1c40bc71b686.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627720/c4e2528a-ebed-11e6-84ea-9ff94b42c772.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627721/c5393618-ebed-11e6-859b-ec4712719448.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627722/c54aaf4c-ebed-11e6-91c1-e546ee6bd3be.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627723/c5683a08-ebed-11e6-9c3c-92d81248e374.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627724/c6025d2c-ebed-11e6-85fb-d351067034d5.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627892/7052be32-ebf0-11e6-8006-95fc61153b27.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22627893/706cc52a-ebf0-11e6-97ac-c734c77e6a18.jpg" width="700" height="600"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Places for Skydiving in India]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2017/01/29/places-for-skydiving-in-india/"/>
    <updated>2017-01-29T12:55:53+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2017/01/29/places-for-skydiving-in-india</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22402598/dadbb1f6-e622-11e6-8d88-80d5e48cc661.jpg" width="450" height="340">
Hello friends!!</p>

<p>If you are looking for craziest lifetime experience that will break you free from the prison bars of your daily routine, there is nothing best on this Globe than flying on your own in the sky.. well!! you must be excited as well as feeling scary when you think to do skydiving. But do not worry! it’s quite natural and its absolutely okay.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Skydiving is a sport in which participants jump or fall from aircraft at altitude. They can perform an assortment of aerial manoeuvres before deploying a parachute to slow their descent, allowing them to come gently to rest on the Earth below. The sport is also known as parachuting, in a reference to that vital piece of safety equipment. People at different levels of physical fitness can participate in skydiving, as long as they are ready for an adrenalin-packed sport which can be both terrifying and exhilarating.</p>

<h1>Types of Sky Dives</h1>

<h2>1. Tandem Jump</h2>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22402596/dacd0606-e622-11e6-9a52-e5ac1ba43726.gif"></p>

<p>The simplest form of skydiving in India, here you are connected to an instructor via a harness. Both of you jump together using the same parachute and the instructor pulls the cord.</p>

<p>Note: You need only minimal instruction before this jump.</p>

<h2>2. Static Line Jump</h2>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22402739/af6167f0-e627-11e6-8db1-ca74fe281fbb.png"></p>

<p>In this skydive you are connected with a cord to the aircraft. And the parachute opens automatically after around 3 seconds of freefall with no action required by the passenger.</p>

<p>Note: The jump is made from only 3000 feet and requires upto 6 hours of training.</p>

<h2>3. Accelerated Free Fall</h2>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22402737/af517976-e627-11e6-8048-245cec4fc43d.png"></p>

<p>Not for the faint hearted – this one is the real deal, where you jump without any attachments and free fall. It is one of the most challenging experiences of skydiving in India.</p>

<p>Note: Obviously given the serious nature of this skydive, it requires both classroom instructions and practical training and is done from at least 13000 feet.
So, which one is your pick? Hold on your breath daredevils ’cause you could go skydiving in India now!</p>

<h1>Places For Skydiving in India</h1>

<h2>1. Mysore, Karnataka</h2>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22402736/af357730-e627-11e6-87e0-3f110121e39f.png"></p>

<p>Nestled at the base of the Chamundi Hills, Mysore is one of the best places to have the ultimate skydiving experiences in India. Is that a bird, a plane, no it’s you!</p>

<h3>Cost:</h3>

<ul>
<li>Tandem – INR 35,000 (3 hours)</li>
<li>Accelerated Free Fall – INR 2,50,00 (5-7 days, 10 jumps)</li>
<li>Timings: 7 AM to 9 AM</li>
</ul>


<h2>2. Deesa, Gujarat</h2>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22402599/daf66cda-e622-11e6-86b8-d0d5943cf2b7.jpg"></p>

<p>Indulge into the thrill of soaring in the blue sky at this beautiful lakeside city. It is one of the best destinations for skydiving in India providing all three types of jumps. The Sports Authority of Gujarat and Indian Parachuting Federation hosts several skydiving camps here.</p>

<h3>Cost:</h3>

<ul>
<li>Static Line Jumps – INR 16,500</li>
<li>Tandem Jumps – INR 33,500</li>
<li>AFF – INR 37,500</li>
<li>Timings: 7 AM</li>
</ul>


<h2>3. Pondicherry, Tamil Nadu</h2>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22402734/af2c02cc-e627-11e6-9c0c-be9de0879681.png"></p>

<p>One of the most beautiful towns in the country, enjoy the spectacular landscape here as you free fall from the sky. The camps here offer static line and tandem jumps.</p>

<h3>Cost:</h3>

<ul>
<li>Static Jumps – INR 18,000 (1 jump) to 62,000 (5 jumps)</li>
<li>Tandem Jump – INR 27,000</li>
<li>Timings: 7 AM or 9 AM</li>
</ul>


<h2>4. Aamby Valley, Maharashtra</h2>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22402733/af25ae90-e627-11e6-95e0-41c843cbd864.png"></p>

<p>One of the best skydiving places in India, Aamby Valley has to be on every Mumbaikar or Punites list if they wish to indulge in the daring sport. Gaze the stunning landscapes beneath as you freefall in the beautiful valley to enjoy the most thrilling experience of your lifetime.</p>

<h3>Cost:</h3>

<ul>
<li>Tandem Jumps</li>
<li>Mon – Thurs – INR 20, 000</li>
<li>Fri – Sun – INR 25,000</li>
<li>Timings: 8:00 AM to 10:00 PM</li>
</ul>


<h2>5. Dhana, Madhya Pradesh</h2>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22402732/af22e336-e627-11e6-9268-291cb127f505.png"></p>

<p>Home to an air strip, Dhana hosts many skydiving camps for adventure enthusiasts. Enjoy a freefall from 4000 feet above, gazing the breathtaking landscape beneath.</p>

<h3>Cost:</h3>

<ul>
<li>Tandem Jump</li>
<li>Weekday: INR 35,000</li>
<li>Weekend: INR 37,500</li>
<li>Static Jumps – INR 24,000</li>
<li>Timings: 8:30 AM</li>
</ul>


<h3>Some Simple facts; You must be aware of before you go for it :-</h3>

<ul>
<li>Skydiving is sensitive to weather. If the conditions are not perfect, your experience may take a little longer.</li>
<li>You Must be atleast 18yrs of age,Please go with a valid ID.Tandem medical Statement for over 60.</li>
<li>Wear Athletic and comfortable clothes , sneakers / sport shoes.No Sandals , booths or High Heels . No Sleeveless Shirts , only T Shirts with</li>
<li>Short and Long Sleeves.</li>
<li>You MUST be within weight limit of 95kgs (with Clothes and Shoes ) or you may not be permitted to Skydive.</li>
<li>There is  a Zero Tolerance Policy for Alcohol and / or Drugs in 24 Hours Before Making  Skydive for your Safety.</li>
<li>Please do not Scuba Dive , 24 hours before Tandem Skydive.</li>
<li>Take your courage with you.. don’t forget it at your home.. ;)</li>
</ul>


<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22402731/af1a9744-e627-11e6-8400-9a83bc69900e.png"></p>

<p>Hope you will enjoy the adventure :)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[OMG: 10 Insane Things Your Favourite Celebrities Believe!!!]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2017/01/15/omg-10-insane-things-your-favourite-celebrities-believe/"/>
    <updated>2017-01-15T12:47:35+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2017/01/15/omg-10-insane-things-your-favourite-celebrities-believe</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21961000/61034542-db23-11e6-9134-d49d9277a01c.jpg">
Well we all love Bollywood’s Thumkas and jhatkas without NO doubts but we hear about their insane believes, it will straight forwardly put all us into persist snigger! Superstition is a senseless fear of God that NOT only show our much loved stars into disgust situations but also proof that Everyone is NOT perfect though as it sees..</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>So guys coming back to the track, let’s make your heart little more giggles and request our superstars to be little sensible in this approach.</p>

<h1>10 Shilpa Shetty</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960991/60b112ae-db23-11e6-9836-f02fa61cf7ea.jpg" title="Shilpa Shetty" ></p>

<p>Our number 10 celebrity is our favourite dhumkas girl. This superstar, super model and modern Entrepreneur that each girl want to be like has lot s more to stay herself practical to keep out of her laughing list.</p>

<p>As confessed by this beautiful diva herself, Shetty always wear “TWO” watches during cricket matches of IPL.  It is NOT all, the way she cross her legs when oppositions team bats is ACTUALLY insane.</p>

<p>Shilpa we love you and millions of your fans don’t want you to have such senseless fear or FAITH.</p>

<h1>9 Bipasha Basu</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960992/60b958ce-db23-11e6-96ce-5e3b06078e11.jpg" title="Bipasha Basu" ></p>

<p>Always on the news for her fitness and over sensuous body, now this bollywood queen caught in our list with her over senseless thinking on the FEAR or faith over devil in particular. This Bengali sexy diva is always seen in horror movie but our reader will be chuckle after knowing her INSANE flicks for keeping lemon and green chillies in car every Saturday to keep her safe from evil eye.</p>

<p>Well bips, fearing from BHOOOOOOOT is not a cool idea.</p>

<h1>8 Katrina Kaif</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960993/60c3640e-db23-11e6-8cec-ed662be5242f.jpg" title="Katrina Kaif" ></p>

<p>Our bollywood Barbie doll is always in the mind for her sexy face and controversial love relationships. But this time she is stuck with our list for her superstitious belief of dargah of Sufi saint Khwaja Moinuddin Chisti in Ajmer before of movie release date.</p>

<p>Devotion is good kat but making it little pernickety and obligatory each time surely make you look insane.</p>

<h1>7 Deepika Padukone</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960994/60c5ee68-db23-11e6-8636-b73c68db6b88.jpg" title="Deepika Padukone" ></p>

<p>After Katrina, Deepika is our next number to have insensible faith that sure said to be insane.  Going with the flow as Kat, she visits Siddhivinayak Temple in Prabhadevi.
Well visiting temple is NOT weird, but making it OBLIGATERY is INSANE.</p>

<h1>6 Ajay Devgn</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960995/60c97baa-db23-11e6-831a-226f32d33843.jpg" title="Ajay Devgn" ></p>

<p>Well guys DONT blame me if you ACTUALLY do the Dublicheaked with th google for this as it is 100% TRUE  or NOT that out KJos hubby has REMOVED “a” from his surname to have successful career!</p>

<p>I mean REALLY????</p>

<p>Mummy told us that hard work ke liye there is NO short “CUTS&hellip; “</p>

<p>This kind of INSANE things is NOT expected with you Mr. devgAn.. as you seems to be sensible in beginning.</p>

<h1>5 Sanjay Dutt</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960996/60ce3b22-db23-11e6-9962-da20209b3697.jpg" title="Sanjay Dutt" ></p>

<p>Well I am sure that all of my readers must have watched Munna bhai Mbbs? Yes?
Have you remember our favourite Munna have do heart touching gandhigiri to remove that Pandit taboo for mangalic vivah..</p>

<p>Yes yes yes ..</p>

<p>So taking our number 5, our Munna Bhai has ACTUALLY broken our heart with his INSANE thing for choosing Number 45 45 each time and called as its good luck charm.</p>

<p>We loved you for what you done in the movie and NOW you are making us regret with this 4545 drama Munna..</p>

<p>Grow up Munna!!!</p>

<h1>4 Aamir Khan</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960997/60f10792-db23-11e6-8f8a-371a2acf3392.jpg" title="Aamir Khan" ></p>

<p>oOops Aamir is  ACTUALLY a heart breaking name to see in this list for sure. Having famous to be called as Mr. Perfectionist in Bollywood industry and looked up by millions of young minds, this INSANE thing is NOT so cool.</p>

<p>Our readers will be thrill to know that such a contemporary minded actor and liberated person who was recently loved for his PK movie who actually a slap for melo drama for superstitions is all just a reel play!</p>

<p>Our Mr. Perfectionist have a COMPULTION to release his movies on Christmas. List is quite long Taare Zameen Par, Ghajini, 3 Idiots, Dhoom 3 and PK.</p>

<p>Poor thing!!! PK was REEL not REAL.</p>

<h1>3 Kareena Kapoor Khan</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960998/60f63708-db23-11e6-8f28-43402f375d41.jpg" title="Kareena Kapoor Khan" ></p>

<p>Our bebo has taken 3rd positions in the race for her insane things in this list. You want to know how? She being the hottest and most followed on the bollywood theme lines, she is now in the laughing stalks for her obsession for NUMBER 3 on the car plates.</p>

<p>Bebo you have to be trend setters for all your co actors for NOT doing this INSANE harkate. We love you and these things are NOT #3</p>

<h1>2 Salman Khan</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960999/61003d5c-db23-11e6-88c9-ded759e37232.jpg" title="Salman Khan" ></p>

<p>He is hot and handsome, BUT surely this time he is NOT so COOL!</p>

<p>Our being human hero and Bigg boss super star, is also INSANE for trending up with superstition tradition with his sexy looking though, blue sapphire bracelet.</p>

<p>Change it salu, we know You Can!!!</p>

<h1>1 Shah Rukh Khan</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21961000/61034542-db23-11e6-9134-d49d9277a01c.jpg" title="Shah Rukh Khan" >
KING Khan with NOT much doubt takes our TOP position in our list with his number 555 superstitious trend.</p>

<p>It is INSANE. IT is ILLOGICAL!!!</p>

<p>I hope you all love this INSANE list. DONT follow it and make a change!!!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Your Child Picking the Right Career Option?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/12/21/is-your-child-picking-the-right-career-option/"/>
    <updated>2016-12-21T07:45:27+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/12/21/is-your-child-picking-the-right-career-option</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375268/56872186-c752-11e6-8ceb-2216eee23654.jpg" width="400" height="500">
A simple effort of yours can make great change in terms of selecting the right career for your child!</p>

<p>Being a parent, has this question ever strike on your mind? Have you ever observed, towards what your little one is inclining more? In the daily hustle, parents often forget to notice those silly but important deeds of their child, which in a long run can be a big problem to tackle with. The skill of being a good parent Is not a rocket science. Yes, it can be obtained over the time. In today’s world, where academics, extra-curricular activities and distractions in the term of electronic gadgets, acquire children’s priority time, it is tough to communicate with them. However, a simple effort in this regard can make a great change.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>How to choose a right career is quite a common question floating in every students’ mind after completing the schooling. Since this is the peak time to find the right path and follow it enthusiastically, a student must be aware of his aptitude and preferences. One wrong decision might lead you to regret for lifetime. A well- structured career is an essential element to chase a successful life and here, parents can set the example as epitome of success, as they have already experienced the same phase.</p>

<p>In this article, we will give you an idea about how to help your child in choosing the right career path. Moreover, the DO’s and DON’T given here will help you in evaluate your parental role.</p>

<h2>Keep an Eye on these Imperatives:</h2>

<p>There are a few factors, which make the career selection process like a cakewalk. While determining a career for their children, parents should understand and ponder these factors. They include:</p>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375267/567c545e-c752-11e6-8c10-76e9c5ac7c9f.jpg"></p>

<h3>Interest:</h3>

<p>Whatever you are doing, it should be of your interest. Without having an interest in a particular field, one can’t be successful in making this as his/her passion. Same goes to your child too. It is your duty as a parent to keep a frequent check of your child’s interest and choose a career accordingly.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375266/567b37d6-c752-11e6-890d-bb5b43811011.jpg"></p>

<h3>Ability:</h3>

<p>One’s ability determines his/her capabilities of doing something. It acts like a mirror of your child personality as well. By noting their ability of doing something, you can select a career exactly meant for your child.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375265/567972e8-c752-11e6-9c3b-1d05801ffc63.jpg"></p>

<h3>Research on the availability of course:</h3>

<p>The course related to a particular career should be available easily and it is, therefore, parents’ duty to do a thorough research on that before advising their child to opt it.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375264/56789c2e-c752-11e6-9ced-32b230c57a39.jpg"></p>

<h3>Scope:</h3>

<p>Pay attention to the scope of a particular course, which tells us about what type of opportunities, will open up after doing that particular course or going for a career.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375263/5675b1da-c752-11e6-83e4-cc55d58f47b7.jpg"></p>

<h3>Remuneration:</h3>

<p>Though, all the time it’s not necessary, but in today’s scenario, remuneration or salary plays an important role. Remuneration should meet the child’s aspirations, so that they can excel a satisfied and comfortable life ahead.</p>

<h2>Do’s and Don’t</h2>

<h3>Do&rsquo;s</h3>

<ul>
<li>Evaluate your child’s aptitude, strengths and weaknesses.</li>
<li>Help your child in discovering his/her own passion.</li>
<li>Motivate your child in pursuing his/her passion.</li>
<li>Inform your child regarding all aspects of the career.</li>
<li>Help the child understand the work life in the chosen career by associating with professionals in the field.</li>
<li>Stop your child from falling prey to peer-pressure and herd mentality.</li>
<li>Gain your child’s confidence and motivate them to discuss their queries with you.</li>
<li>Seek professional help whenever required.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Dont&rsquo;s</h3>

<ul>
<li>Do not impose your wish on them</li>
<li>Do not burden the child with unreal expectations</li>
<li>Don’t be impatient when dealing with children</li>
<li>Career scope changes with time; do not try to impose the ideas or views that existed during your days</li>
<li>Do not misguide the child into choosing a career of your choice</li>
<li>Do not be on rush to answer a child’s question without the knowledge. It’s ok to take time, research or seek professional help</li>
<li>Protect your child from being influenced by others in the career selection process</li>
</ul>


<p>This way you can be an active partner of your child while selecting a career. Identify your child’s interest, skills and value and start playing your role.</p>

<p>Happy Parenting</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Navigate the Traps of Online Dating to Save Your Relationship?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/12/20/how-to-navigate-the-traps-of-online-dating-to-save-your-relationship/"/>
    <updated>2016-12-20T00:07:32+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/12/20/how-to-navigate-the-traps-of-online-dating-to-save-your-relationship</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324391/870c3a8c-c647-11e6-9118-abe61a3cd600.jpg" width="500" height="600"></p>

<!-- more -->


<p>This surely is a tech savvy age and the rise of smartphones are all the rage. It has transformed our society wherein online dating has been ticking all the wrong boxes.
Men who are in relationships might be loyal to their women but nowadays, with this emerging trend of various online dating sites gaining popularity; men are drifting towards infidelity. These online dating sites provide a gamut of attractive facilities to woo men along with hundreds and thousands of eye-catching women waiting to get ticked. Men look for excitement in their lives and what better way than online dating sites? While being in a relationship, there are times when men look for other prospects for simply flirting and passing their time, these online dating sites are a boon for these men to talk with women they have never met or spoken with.</p>

<h2>How to deal with it -</h2>

<p>Do not turn a blind eye to it, if you get acquainted with the fact that your man is getting indulged in online dating sites and is showing his interest in it. It can act like a dagger piercing through the heart but do not ignore.</p>

<h2>Educate yourself and research about his interest –</h2>

<p>If he sends across messages that are steamy and passion then he surely seeks or attention just like an egoistic man would want to do and if he is sending intimate and comforting messages then he is craving for affection emotionally.</p>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324389/86f13aac-c647-11e6-9d6b-94a3f9fef1a1.jpg"></p>

<p>You don’t need to feel that you are not of value for him because online dating is considered as a sign of infidelity and such men at times lack the ability of communicating their needs or it might even be the reason of his self-image. You need to reach out to him and talk it out instead of thinking about anything else.</p>

<h2>Set your limits –</h2>

<p>When you get to know that your man is cheating on you, you need to set your limits there and then. Stop acting like an emotional freak and if you are serious for him; make it certain that he needs to make a choice. Don’t feel the pain of his entertainment and cut all ties of physical intimacy till the time he doesn’t get back to his senses.</p>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324390/86fe7244-c647-11e6-989f-b3c925bc419d.jpg"></p>

<p>Don’t burst like a volcano over him and try to be calm. Because he might take offence despite being wrong at his part. Also, don’t blame or argue, put out your heart on your sleeve and refrain from having any physical contact with him. He might comprehend the blunder he has made to his relationship.</p>

<h2>Focus back on your life –</h2>

<p>Your happiness is equally important and if you cannot control his infidelity, be kind to yourself. Do not indulge in sleepless nights and swollen eyes. Pamper yourself and ignore his behavior. There are times when your self-esteem gets broken when your man does such things.</p>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324388/86e47ef2-c647-11e6-87fe-e9e744e0fe2a.jpg"></p>

<p>Bubble-up and make sure you date yourself and spend as much time with yourself that it makes you feel happy. Take your life back and maintain the respect and self-esteem in the ego, no matter what. Everything else will fall back into place and if he is meant to be, he will come back to you.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s How You Can Check Your Boyfriend’s Loyalty?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/12/19/heres-how-you-can-check-your-boyfriends-loyalty/"/>
    <updated>2016-12-19T07:50:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/12/19/heres-how-you-can-check-your-boyfriends-loyalty</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21299213/73ec5474-c5bf-11e6-8840-1807723aa1df.jpg"></p>

<!-- more -->


<p>It sends shivers down your spine when you acknowledge or even think about your beau cheating on you. Trust and faith are the base of any relationship. There are a few tests and ways through which you can check the loyalty of your boyfriend. There are times when you might be apprehensive of his behavior like phone number on waiting, replying late or reluctant to meet but it does not mean that he is cheating on you. Suspecting him for false reasons might be a disastrous feeling for your relationship so try to test him through the below mentioned ways.</p>

<h2>Steer clear from infidelity</h2>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21299210/73e10b6e-c5bf-11e6-8ccd-77cfac469d6a.jpg">
You don’t have to hire a company to do the loyalty test for you. Start small and conduct loyalty tests all by yourself. You don’t have to involve scores of people to do this for you when some simple tricks can do the work for you.</p>

<h2>The Social Media Test</h2>

<p>You need to develop a fake social media profile with a believable name along with photographs and friends so that it doesn’t look unreliable. The pictures that you post, make sure that those pictures are attractive and might woo your guy. Try to flirt and trifle with him. Try to judge his reply and check, if he is interested in that fake profile. Slowly and steadily ask for his number and check whether he reverts or not. If he is interested in that fake profile and shares the phone number then, he is certainly not trustworthy and you have proof to support the infidelity.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21299209/73dd5a96-c5bf-11e6-9828-fd802570b6a0.jpg"></p>

<h2>Friends with Benefits</h2>

<p>Take help from your friends and make them meet your guy. Try to observe his behavior and attributes while he communicates with your friends. Ask one of your friend to become overfriendly and informal with your guy and check his response. You don’t have to exaggerate the situation, ask your friend to call and flirt with him. Just in case if he is positive towards the entire philandering then he is surely not loyal.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21299212/73e5773a-c5bf-11e6-9723-8f05fa70c8d1.jpg"></p>

<h2>Sudden change in attitude</h2>

<p>Try to observe his behavior, way of dressing, talking and meeting you. Is he ignoring you while giving you a reason of work overload or does he spend a lot of time surfing social media? These are some of the things which might be of concern for you. Does he not share his messages with you or he doesn’t like if you check his cell phone or Facebook account?
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21299211/73e1d198-c5bf-11e6-8ae4-0421f8ff1b80.jpg"></p>

<p>These are some of the ways through which you can confront your boyfriend and check whether he is loyal to you or not. You never know if he is a two-timing man or he has been cheating on you since a long time. You have to be frank and do not allow him to twist the things. If you are serious for him, try to confront it and work on your relationship. This would take time to heal because it can develop grudges between the two of you but time heals every wound. Give him a last chance but always remember that once bitten, twice shy; stay cautious and guarded.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diwali Shopping in Sector 31 Market Gurgaon]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/30/diwali-shopping-in-sector-31-market-gurgaon/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-30T15:18:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/30/diwali-shopping-in-sector-31-market-gurgaon</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="/images/posts/DSC09823.JPG"></p>

<!--more-->


<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="/images/posts/DSC09815.JPG"></p>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="/images/posts/DSC09818.JPG"></p>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="/images/posts/DSC09821.JPG"></p>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="/images/posts/DSC09825.JPG"></p>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="/images/posts/DSC09826.JPG"></p>

<p>Huda market sector 31, Gurgaon is a perfect destination for a great time with your dear ones.
With so much to lure your senses and offer you recreation at its best, get drenched in the spirit of adventure that you get to explore at huda market sector 31, Gurgaon.
Enjoy together all the points of popular interests and bring back several memorable moments.</p>

<p>Huda market sector 31, Gurgaon is not just the place for sightseeing, but it also enables you to steal a self-indulgent moment for yourself as well.
So, check out the huda market sector 31 tourist spot for all the attractions that is on offer and visit this spot on weekends for a rejuvenating time.
World standards, extraordinary architecture, innovative layouts, and well-thought execution make place a highly coveted point of tourist interest.
Huda market sector 31, Gurgaon is the sure way to refresh and relax after a busy weekday.</p>

<p>Explore interesting themes, fabulous designs, colorful landscapes, amusing characters,
ambient music, props and merchandise available in nearby stores- all at one place.</p>

<p>Huda market sector 31, Gurgaon is the best way to have a memorable time with kids and family.
So, enjoy a fulfilling outing at huda market sector 31 in Gurgaon. Check it out!</p>

<h2>Happy Diwali</h2>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Super Gorgeous Woman Fashion Trends Not to Miss in This Diwali]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/24/woman-fashion-trends-in-diwali-2016/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-24T15:18:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/24/woman-fashion-trends-in-diwali-2016</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651466/8a8718ce-9a2a-11e6-8cd7-eb9674c2f9e2.jpg" width="400" height="600">
Well, it’s an open secret that all women’s are fashion savvy in some way or other. Some like to uniform themselves with the latest fashion and others trying to keep up with the trends at the festival season.
Whatever the occasion and whichever the place, fashion is always on the mind. So, as we all know the happy days of Diwali are here to come and I am going to discover some crazy fashion trends for this Diwali
– after all this is the best opportunity to show your bit-off fashion sense, if you are so inclined.</p>

<!--more-->


<h1>Go Indo-Western:</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19656458/b39238b2-9a3d-11e6-8c42-92740f186c51.jpg" width="400" height="500">
Whether you are collage going girl or working woman fusion dressing can give interesting twist to your Diwali fashion. You can try some hit fusions like choli with palazzo pants, traditional saree with off shoulder or sleeveless blouse.
All these apparels can be emphasized with delicate elements like zardosi work or you can try beads, stones and pearls as well.</p>

<h1>Jewelry time:</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651463/8a74cf0c-9a2a-11e6-92cc-7cc67e408913.jpg" width="500" height="600">
The most important thing which can make or break your look is jewelry. So, leave some good budget aside to invest in beautiful jewelry.
Huge ranges of exclusive jewelries are available in market to suit every budget and every taste. Furthermore, culture jewelry is in revival on the festive occasions, so this is an ideal time to add some traditional jewelry in your collection.</p>

<h1>Digital print:</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651459/89df5b16-9a2a-11e6-81ab-1e9a8519a764.jpg">
Nowadays, digital prints hammered huge market and now you can find these prints for anarkali suits, kurties, party gown and in sarees also.
Floor length anarkali suit with digital print can give you contemporary look this Diwali.</p>

<h1>Go with Polka dots</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651467/8aa6cfa2-9a2a-11e6-932b-2336226e9d17.jpg">
Gone are the days when people were hesitant to try something different with their clothing especially on traditional festival like Diwali.
However, if you are bored with traditional sari or salwar kamiz then better you go with polka dot. It’s an innovative outfit that gives perfect model look.</p>

<h1>Footwear:</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651461/8a61e69e-9a2a-11e6-8285-7e0be452b3e4.jpg">
Well, your footwear is a mirror of your style sense. So, I suggest pair your outfit and jewelry with nice traditional footwear like kolhapuri chapples,
jodhpuri or mojadi. You can also go with nice pair of flipflops with designs and glittery stones.</p>

<h1>Get trendy with long skirts:</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651460/8a2c1fbe-9a2a-11e6-83dd-c79aefb93842.jpg">
Do you have collection of ethnic tops and jackets? Then team up those with any vibrant colored long skirt. But make sure not to go with
very flowy or dramatic skirts as it can mess with diyas or rangoli.</p>

<h1>Stylish nose ring:</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651466/8a8718ce-9a2a-11e6-8cd7-eb9674c2f9e2.jpg">
Though it’s very less considered armament in jewelry, Stylish nose ring can gives you elegant look for this Diwali. You can find various kinds of nose ring or studs with different material like metal,
stone, gold etc.</p>

<p>So, these are some fashion trends that can surely help you to make right choice for yourself to rock this Diwali festival. Enjoy your Diwali to the fullest!!!</p>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651462/8a6e4fe2-9a2a-11e6-9106-f7ccc795fc9d.gif">
Happy Diwali ☺</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Questions Every Girl Wants to Ask Her Guy?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/15/questions-every-girl-wants-to-ask-her-guy/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-15T13:18:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/15/questions-every-girl-wants-to-ask-her-guy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif" width="500" height="600">
Well, it is not as if the number of questions we often bombard you with is a low figure. Nevertheless, we have a few more.
There are certain questions, which are not so easy to ask, or are better avoided. However, in alignment with our traits,
we cannot feel at peace unless these questions are answered.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>No matter how cool we might seem as girlfriends, we remain troubled by these questions.
Therefore, boys, if you are reading this, please do help us clear away the clouds of curiosity hovering over our heads by answering these questions!</p>

<h1>1.Do you love me? Like, you really do?’</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378810/4b5135d4-920c-11e6-9819-b7f47d541d5c.gif">
You might have been very clear about your serious intentions. Yet, we feel the need to re-confirm if the answer has changed, is still the same, or is modified.
And of course, we love listening to the way you express your love.</p>

<h1>2.How much do you love me?’</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378794/4b17ec2a-920c-11e6-8e48-76543db03aea.gif">
We aren’t expecting a very clichéd answer for this one, but rather an honest answer that quantitatively describes your love for us.
Then you can probably just add on those historic lines proclaiming how you can even fetch us stars from Heaven. :P</p>

<h1>3.‘Do you ever stalk me the way I stalk you?’</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif">
Umm, maybe not as diligently as we do, but at least partially in the same manner that we do?
That’s really something we girls would want to know. We love knowing how much a person is curious about us.</p>

<h1>4.Does your best friend really like us?’</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378797/4b195eca-920c-11e6-8d2a-09695430c5d2.gif">
If this question has not yet come up, be assured that it soon will. Although your best friend might be very nice to us,
we cannot help but contemplate on the question if she genuinely likes us or is being pretentious and doing it for the sake of friendship.</p>

<h1>5.‘How serious were you in your previous relationship?’</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378798/4b1af94c-920c-11e6-8787-0feccfb25de8.gif">
This kind of a question may lead to an awkward silence. It is similar to the awkwardness we face when we contemplate asking you this.
The answer would not really affect our relationship, but we are curious. We would want to be a bit more knowledgeable about this.</p>

<h1>6.‘Did you ever imagine getting married to your ex?’</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378796/4b18c352-920c-11e6-8118-fd9083e9c858.gif">
If it were a straight forward NO, we definitely would want to know the answer. However, if it’s a yes, then maybe we should just go to the next question.</p>

<h1>7. ‘What do your friends think about me?’</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378811/4b51c6b6-920c-11e6-9198-180e93ff30d0.gif">
Whether the answer is negative or positive, we are ready to face anything and everything.
We just want to know about the kind of conversation you have with your friends while discussing us.</p>

<h1>8.‘Do you still miss something special about your past relationship?’</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378799/4b1fccc4-920c-11e6-8dd9-f1519d838bbb.gif">
At some point, we do accept your past and stay cool with it. Yet, we do love keeping ourselves informed about such things.</p>

<h1>9.What if your parents do not accept me?’</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378814/4b52a34c-920c-11e6-88c1-1175cd81b92b.gif">
We reassure you that we will try our best to make them like us.
However, suppose they don’t, what do we do then? Where does our relationship go from here?</p>

<h1>10.Why me at all?’</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378795/4b1756b6-920c-11e6-8677-5966d4dc2bf0.gif">
Now this one calls for a super romantic reply. We girls would love hearing about your feelings during the initial meeting, and what prompted you to choose us.
It might be the hundredth time but it is hard to explain how it feels to hear the answer every single time!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Best Budget Free Honeymoon Destinations in the World]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/08/10-best-budget-free-honeymoon-destinations-in-the-world/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-08T13:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/08/10-best-budget-free-honeymoon-destinations-in-the-world</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19268423/146a7350-8fd2-11e6-9e03-c15f544fd9f0.jpg" width="400" height="500">
Honeymoon, another amazing time associated with your wedding! It ought to be amazingly perfect, ain’t it? But the other side of story reveals something different. When it comes to wedding expenses, not everyone has a loose budget to spend money like water. But that does not even imply that you cannot have a fabulous honeymoon. We have a list of budget friendly destinations where you can enjoy to the fullest without stretching your dollars much.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Ireland</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19268219/cbebcd1e-8fd0-11e6-944a-2b99843a7f60.jpg">
Ireland is one of the best ravel places for the ones who want a honeymoon in Western Europe. The picturesque views, castles, charming villages, as well as the vibrant green stretches are enough to make you fall in love with the place.</p>

<h1>Mexico</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19268221/cc209d14-8fd0-11e6-8627-701d865e846c.jpg">
With a tropical climate and n number of beautiful sandy beaches, a very affordable honeymoon trip to Mexico can easily be planned. It has a variety of accommodations that would fit anyone’s budget. The leisure time spent in jungles or relaxing on the beach with a cocktail is something that incuses you, then Mexico is the place where your honeymoon is meant to be.</p>

<h1>Thailand</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19268224/cc580c7c-8fd0-11e6-861e-87c066991b43.jpg">
Thailand is one of the most popular destinations of Southeast Asia that is known for being wallet-friendly. This place boosts of having a plenty of picture-perfect beaches having clearest of waters. The adventure lovers have their call in the place as it does offer activities like trekking and wildlife safari. Moreover, the food and accommodations are very affordable.</p>

<h1>Croatia</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19268227/cc8b0ca8-8fd0-11e6-9863-95022be3217d.jpg">
Gifted with beautiful medieval architecture and gorgeous beaches, Croatia is one of the best option for honeymooners. Also, there are plenty of things worth doing. You can go boating, sightseeing as well as relish the scenic views of Europe.</p>

<h1>Jamaica</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19268220/cc0a13d2-8fd0-11e6-8a22-ee43f0fc35b5.jpg">
Jamaica is one of the most affordable destinations in the Caribbean area. Home to laidback mountains, pristine beaches and, waterfalls, this place has affordable resorts to make it an amazing honeymoon for you. Other than this, there are affordable boutique hotels as well. Jamaica brings a cheap tropical honeymoon for you.</p>

<h1>Turkey</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19268228/cc96da92-8fd0-11e6-8493-a120d6716497.jpg">
Turkey is another fantastic affordable honeymoon destination if you crave for amazing food, ancient ruins, and postcard-worthy villages. The rich culture of the place decorated with mosques and palaces is something that must not be missed while here.</p>

<h1>Canada</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19268226/cc75a52a-8fd0-11e6-93b9-fc3d568107b9.jpg">
A package of Vancouver, Montreal, and Whistler, Canada can give you a taste of amazing honeymoon experience. Or you can even visit a part of Canada and celebrate your honeymoon.</p>

<h1>Portugal</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19268223/cc4d6376-8fd0-11e6-86e3-fd0361792073.jpg">
The most affordable country to visit in Western part of Europe is Portugal and this place is also blessed with immense cultural and historical heritage, which includes ancient castles, river cruises, olive groves, seaside fishing villages, and much more.</p>

<h1>Nicaragua</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19268222/cc38e7fc-8fd0-11e6-9ac3-9b9843c150af.jpg">
For the adventure lovers of the world, Nicaragua is the best pocket-friendly destination. There are plenty of outdoor activities that one can do and these include lakes, beaches, volcanoes, mountains, and so on. To mention a few by name, volcano boarding, hiking, and Ziplining are something you’re surely going to enjoy.</p>

<h1>Greece</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19268225/cc660ec6-8fd0-11e6-8720-b1e426b73785.jpg">
Romantic Resorts, calm climate, clear waters, and sandy beaches it is the perfect package to have an amazing honeymoon and Greece offers you this gateway to make your honeymoon affordable as well as enjoying.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Checklist for Your Wedding Vanity Box]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/08/checklist-for-your-wedding-vanity-box/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-08T12:29:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/08/checklist-for-your-wedding-vanity-box</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19268109/08a047c2-8fd0-11e6-9f5a-a0f67ae52f96.jpg" width="500" height="500">
A girl’s wedding is the most important day of her life and everything related to wedding needs to be absolutely amazing. Moreover, the tiny minis associated that give immense happiness and one such happiness is the fun of doing your own wedding shopping.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>It is that time of your life when you can buy anything and nobody can stop you. Just imagine how exciting would be the shopping for wedding makeup. But a wise thing to do would be that you buy only those products that you will actually use as cosmetics expire after a certain period of time. Nonetheless, we have some essentials that would make a perfect wedding vanity box for you.</p>

<h1>Compact</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/19210349/486f457c-8d3e-11e6-94b4-0273f349e085.jpg" width="500" height="600">
A compact or what is commonly known as face powder is the most common thing that a girl must have in her makeup kit. This is essential as the normal Indian skin is oily. Therefore, putting on a loose or translucent powder on, the skin would not look too oily after a couple of years.</p>

<h1>Primer</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19268109/08a047c2-8fd0-11e6-9f5a-a0f67ae52f96.jpg" width="600" height="500">
A primer is a must have in your wedding vanity checklist if you love to put on makeup often. This primer acts as a barrier between the foundation and your skin.</p>

<h1>Foundation</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/19210351/4872c0a8-8d3e-11e6-8c6a-68347ca22be5.jpg">
Foundation is another essential item that is meant for a makeup girl. When applied, it acts as a base glow for your skin.</p>

<h1>Eye-liner</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/19210347/48692e76-8d3e-11e6-83ab-9223729bf307.jpg">
This is another makeup thing that you must carry in your kit. It outlines your eyes.</p>

<h1>Brush</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/19210352/48a7f9d0-8d3e-11e6-89ae-f92b24c904c2.jpg">
A brush is required to put makeup on. Hence, you can include different brushes according to the purpose they are meant for.</p>

<h1>Eye-shadow</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/19210348/486e09f0-8d3e-11e6-92d5-8d5f2fc78e05.jpg">
Putting a light shade of shadow on your eyes would make them look attractive and ‘eye-catchy.’</p>

<h1>Mascara</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19268125/229ec05e-8fd0-11e6-975d-6ce9f4d5bc0d.png" width="500" height="600">
This serves as a magical equipment in your makeup box and makes your eye lashes look simply amazing.</p>

<h1>Lipstick and Lip liner</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/19210353/48ab9914-8d3e-11e6-8d6a-20fbf7713e16.jpg">
Although a lipstick or a lip-gloss is more or less the same thing but the choice entirely depends upon you. In fact, you can go for both of them but do not forget to assist them with a lip liner as it outlines your lips, with lipstick or gloss filled in. You can have as many shades and colors of lipsticks or glosses you want to.</p>

<h1>Kajal Pencil</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/19210350/4871b654-8d3e-11e6-8924-5b61b2236530.jpg">
When you have already equipped your kit with an eyeliner, how can you forget a kajal pencil. Kajal is something that is being used since ages by the women folk and it is believed to give your eyes a magical look. They say kajal is the most basic makeup that a girl can put on.</p>

<h1>Eyebrow Pencil</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/19210346/4866ca00-8d3e-11e6-9fba-8e0df2f38a40.jpg" width="500" height="600">
You are definitely going to need an eyebrow pencil to magnify your looks. It is the perfect makeup accessory to groom your brows.</p>

<h1>Concealer</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/19210355/48b306cc-8d3e-11e6-8a85-72850d857d43.jpg" width="500" height="600">
Think you have to rush to a party on a very short notice but you realize that there are a few irritating spots on your skin, well, a concealer can work wonders at such time. It can help you hide those spots for a time being.</p>

<h1>Makeup Remover</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/19210354/48af8c22-8d3e-11e6-91af-dfe666d1e47b.jpg">
When you have so much of makeup to put on, certainly you would be needing something to remove it as well. A makeup remover is something that you must not forget to keep in your wedding vanity box.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Overcome a BAD Breakup]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/04/how-to-overcome-from-breakup/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-04T13:18:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/04/how-to-overcome-from-breakup</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif">
Break ups can be very difficult to deal with and looking at how fast paced our lives are, it is difficult to make time for you and cope up with all the depression phase.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Needless to talk about how you have to deal with all the people around who if know about the break up, keep asking how you feeling and those who don’t know keep wondering
if there is something wrong you are going through mentally. However, we have got a few ways in which you can handle a break up without going through much of self- disappointment or depression.
Hope this tips help you and do the best for you</p>

<h1>Block him or unfriend him from all social media platforms.</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104511/8a2b50b4-8afa-11e6-9cc1-5252742b2490.gif">
You might feel like a grownup that does not need to do all this but trust us, this helps BIG time! Off course you do not what his name popping up in your notifications. This might keep reminding you of him and plus getting updates about what he is up to while are trying to move on can worsen things up for you.</p>

<h1>Do not jump into the ‘let us just be friends’ stage too soon.</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104513/8a3137f4-8afa-11e6-95b4-262e04c3a847.gif">
It is advisable to give yourself sometime to figure things out and realize what needs to be changed and what does not. If he suggests this then tell him that you need some time to think about it. Usually one wish to be just friends while the other expects more out of it, and at such you a state, you might want to have things clear and no confusions involved.</p>

<h1>If you are ever tempted to drink, take a friend along.</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104510/8a288564-8afa-11e6-9ee7-b4d811ee0964.gif">
Drinking while you are alone and sad after a break up is very common.Although some find it a convenient way to deal with such traumatic situations, it is not really a solution to it. If you are tempted to go for a drink, take a trusted friend along who would make sure you don’t up making regrettable choices when you are drunk.</p>

<h1>Start up an intense work out regime.</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104512/8a2c681e-8afa-11e6-8e6c-81d934bc15db.gif">
You might have come across options like these which people usually choose. The point is to boost your self-confidence and keep you focus on your own well-being. Moreover, doing something such as kickboxing is a great way of getting all the inner frustration out and doing something productive.</p>

<h1>Allow yourself to cry whenever you need to.</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif">
This one can be a bit confusing but letting it all go and getting yourself out of the phase should be your motive.</p>

<p>Most importantly give time to do things that you like doing and being around people who love and care for you.
Before loving others, it is important to love ourselves, beginnings could be little difficult but once you start initiating things, you feel good about it. Remember the solution is always live up in the present than recalling the past. Your life is important.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Sweetest Ways to Tell Your Partner About Your Pregnancy]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/03/how-to-tell-him-about-your-pregnancy/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-03T13:18:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/03/how-to-tell-him-about-your-pregnancy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103253/6908ad66-8af3-11e6-91d1-6fff11b6948d.jpg" width="500" height="600">
Being in a long distance relationship it took us long time to plan a kid. Finally the good news arrived and I was pregnant by 2 month. The joy was to the cloud and back.
Even if you are sure and going to be new parents to be., here are some sweetest way to tell your partner the same, the tips are as follows:-</p>

<!--more-->


<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103252/69043c4a-8af3-11e6-9f8b-94abc6787cd6.jpg" width="500" height="600"></p>

<h1>Cupcake delight</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103265/74fef99a-8af3-11e6-920c-a7f23ce2d3b2.gif">
The customized cup cakes could do all that wonders. A romantic and surprise cup cake for soon to be daddy will be a perfect one.</p>

<h1>Sweeter box of chocolates</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103324/d22f1b0e-8af3-11e6-8cf9-af577009b9c1.gif">
They are most easy thing to bake and spelling daddy on every piece of chocolate could be an good option to break the news.</p>

<h1>Jigsaw puzzle</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103487/b9ff3702-8af4-11e6-980d-58f1642709a3.gif">
When you wish to give him that nail bitting moment and keep that fun of surprise on then jigsaw puzzle could be a perfect option for you.</p>

<h1>Coffee mug hidden message</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103527/fa6adfee-8af4-11e6-91bb-eb0400a56351.jpg">
Imagine that he has entered home after long time, in order to break the ice and start conversations coffee would be an ideal option. The best way to express your feelings is that the message in the interiors of the mug could express it better. Planning a coffee together could be the best one.</p>

<h1>Baby lottery</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103528/fa6c06b2-8af4-11e6-9acd-715e023c210e.jpg">
Times have gone where people only used scratch cards to win lottery or recharge, you can even use scratch card to announce your pregnancy.</p>

<h1>Announcing on customized t-shirt</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103530/faa56cea-8af4-11e6-9f18-f4146c0cfb84.jpg">
Hip hurray we are going to be new parents to be, trust us fun will be different when he will wear a t-shirt. You could choose from variants of colors.</p>

<h1>Baby cake pops</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103529/fa912dd4-8af4-11e6-8ec1-6d45336494be.gif">
This time is right  to express your creativity to loved ones. You could order for baby cake pops and when he arrives surprise him with that.</p>

<h1>Small cute plate on dining table</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103526/fa6a651e-8af4-11e6-983c-830bcc351508.jpg">
A little spoon, dish and bowl with handwritten message will bring that big blushing smile.</p>

<h1>Baby photos everywhere</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103528/fa6c06b2-8af4-11e6-9acd-715e023c210e.jpg">
Before he gets up from the bed, fill your bedroom with lot of photos. We are sure that cute baby photos will also melt his heart. Doing your own photoshoot with some cute dolls to surprise him will also work wonders.</p>

<h1>Take him for garden stroll</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19120993/84af3fcc-8b42-11e6-851b-63fbc6f8b7ae.jpg">
There is nothing pure like nature and revealing heart out. Breaking the news of baby may require some peaceful environment; taking him to toddlers play area will give him that different joy all together.</p>

<p>Relationship grows better with a new arrival of new kid. Motherhood is all together different joy. We insist all of you to eat right and fresh.
Enjoy the present with all good moments. We are sure that these tips will surely bring in more joy than anything else. You could go boundless with creativity even if you are planning to do DIY.
“I love you” is always worth to say for giving him that perfect good feeling.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deal It Right for Perfect Dream Date!]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/03/first-date-tips/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-03T13:16:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/03/first-date-tips</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19019990/4b9ea3b6-88b9-11e6-818a-201fac58cebd.gif">
Dating online is no more a taboo. It has become a pretty normal way of finding dating partners. Not to miss out some relationships that turned into having a bright future.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Online dating can be a very tricky business. While it can work wonders for a few, it can even become troublesome for others. Under such circumstances, one must be self-informed about everything that goes around.
Not all online experiences turn out to be good ones and thus, here are a few tips which will help you connect to a partner suitable for you and also help you avoid making silly mistakes:</p>

<h1>Select a good site.</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19020016/39b50720-88ba-11e6-8e6a-7a36570515e0.jpg">
Even before you start dreaming about your to-be date; it is necessary to give enough time to select an appropriate site for online dating. While there are sites which allow you to make choice for yourself from a number of members using the same website, there are also sites that suggest dates to you based on your compatibility.
If you wish to have the freedom of choice and are ready to go through hundreds of accounts, then the prior one is what you should be looking for.</p>

<h1>Choose someone with similar interests.</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19020012/25cb172c-88ba-11e6-8221-7356013943f9.jpg">
If you are specific about what you are looking for, for example, of a particular community or work place or a defined age group or even in terms of preferred sexuality, there exist sites which work wholly based on that particular category.
This way it will be much more sorted, easier and faster. Also while choosing a partner; people like to usual go for someone with whom they share similar interest. This helps you to start a good conversation.</p>

<h1>Not being too choosy is the key.</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19020014/31813178-88ba-11e6-8acb-5611f4cd88d4.jpg">
It is a human tendency to make a list of have’s and have not’s when you start talking to each other or meet on the first date. You might have thoughts like ‘he doesn’t dress well’ or ‘she does not have good eyes’ or ‘he does not earn enough’.
However, when you are going for online dating, it is very important to have an open mind and not to be too much judgmental about everything. Letting your inner voice stay at peace and seeing what’s kept on the plate for you is a wise choice. You might as well turn out to like the person.</p>

<h1>Be honest.</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19019984/1b259cf8-88b9-11e6-88ad-4a78b058f81a.gif">
The truth can’t be denied that it is very tempting to exaggerate or stretch things while writing your bio. Nevertheless, lying can lead to a number of disappointments in the future. It is best to stay honest since the start and have nothing to hide about.
False revealing can make you lose a potential partner. Not pretending or trying to be someone or something you are not is the best option to go for.</p>

<p>Online dating has become a fade lately because of which it has become very important to beware aboutpeople who use these sites for their selfish needs or to trick people. One ‘must’ stand by rule is to keep it low at the start. Do not give too many details.
Rest is all that your personality and charms needs to manage.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Movies Related to Womens Issues Everyone Should Watch at Least Once]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/26/top-10-movies-related-to-womens-issues-everyone-should-watch-at-least-once/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-26T12:29:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/26/top-10-movies-related-to-womens-issues-everyone-should-watch-at-least-once</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015068/5707e8d8-881a-11e6-9af6-6ca86c160dd6.jpg" width="600" height="500">
It all began with eve teasing, slowly took the form of molestation, and finally turned into brutal rape. There is no denying the fact that the issues related to women have increased to great extent now days.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Even though, there have arrived various laws and norms for the safety of females in our country but still the number of such issues has not gone down, in fact, these have increased in the past few years.
No matter, how much this menace keeps on rising, there are still such people in the society who will keep on attempting to do things that create awareness in the minds of people regarding the safety of women. One such awareness is created in the minds of public through empowering movies related to women’s issues. So, we picked some great ones and brought a list for you:</p>

<h1>Arth</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015062/5699e590-881a-11e6-953a-b870094f3719.jpg">
This movie is based on the internal struggle of two women who make a man pivot of their existence. One women rejects every male in order to lead a single and independent life and the other one ditches the man after self-introspection. At the end, women are portrayed as winners.</p>

<h1>Aastha: In the prison of spring</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015061/565c2d68-881a-11e6-9ba7-af8d36328d6f.jpg">
This movie pictured the female protagonist to another realm where a bored house wife turns into a prostitute at night and fulfills the chasm of materialistic needs of life. It was directed by Basu Bhattacharya in 1997.</p>

<h1>Lajja</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015065/56d46206-881a-11e6-9977-531ffcba500c.jpg">
Filmed in the year 2001, Lajja is another female centric movie that depicts a land where women worshipped as shakti are humiliated and killed just because they are females. Directed by Rajkumar Santoshi, it highlights societal malpractices.</p>

<h1>The Dirty Picture</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015070/57376f2c-881a-11e6-8100-a44d2e945470.jpg">
This movie characterizes Vidya as southern siren Silk Smitha, a woman who was not ashamed of her physique, instead, she flaunts it, without caring about the repressed sexuality. She shone like a star and was hailed as a female hero.</p>

<h1>Kahaani</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015148/3a1cb3dc-881c-11e6-95dd-d06eb627cbff.jpg">
Cinematographed in 2012, Kahaani shows another amazing performance by Vidya Balan. The plot of the movie showcased the inner reserves of a woman’s power. Despite of being pregnant, she goes on her mission and completes it with vigor and zeal.</p>

<h1>Jazbaa</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015063/56c29828-881a-11e6-966f-f6578f858a55.jpg">
Jazbaa is another women centric movie that stars Aishwarya Rai Bacchan, an attorney forced to defend a criminal after her daughter was kidnapped.</p>

<h1>Sarabjit</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015069/5712efbc-881a-11e6-9f4b-7ff5a440d54d.jpg">
This movie also pictures Aishwarya Rai Bacchan in the role of Dalbir Kaur who falls a prey to an abusive husband. She leaves him and starts living with her brother’s family, working as an independent woman.</p>

<h1>Neerja</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015149/3a5a415c-881c-11e6-83af-3cd9e6fc478e.jpg">
In Neerja, Sonam Kapoor played the role of the courageous flight attendant who had to lose her life in order to save the highjacked plane from terrorists.</p>

<h1>Piku</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015067/56fd8ece-881a-11e6-9695-2f7342e143b2.jpg">
Piku is a light and humorous film showing Deepika Padukone as an independent single lady who has to give up on her dreams and desires in order to take care of her old father.</p>

<h1>Pink</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015068/5707e8d8-881a-11e6-9af6-6ca86c160dd6.jpg">
It is an Indian Courtroom Drama that conveys that women should have the liberty to walk and speak freely at night.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Questions Every Guy Wants to Ask His Girl]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/25/7-questions-every-guy-wants-to-ask-his-girl/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-25T12:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/25/7-questions-every-guy-wants-to-ask-his-girl</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813009/3000fbb2-8306-11e6-873d-4fdec1d7d180.jpg" width="400" height="500">
Every guy is curious about his girl. Apart from the fact, that he loves her so much, there still some ‘questions that he certainly thinks of asking to her. Here we have a list of interrogations that a guy would like to have with his girl:</p>

<!-- more -->


<p><br/><br/><br/><br/></p>

<h1>Why do you spend so much time on makeup?</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813011/300899ee-8306-11e6-88a2-16ea09db0b3e.jpg" width="600" height="500">
Often, most of the girls are seen with little or too much makeup on. There is hardly any girl who does not likes to put on makeup in order to look good. So, this can be one of the questions that a guy would probably want to ask her girl that why does she spend so much time on doing makeup. And the answer would be because the girls like the way they look in it. Also, it is fun to wear makeup.</p>

<h1>How frequently do you talk bad about your friends?</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813008/2fee873e-8306-11e6-8ee1-2aa132311b0a.jpg">
There is a difference between gossiping about someone and talking bad about them. Gossip can be harmless but talking bad can be something serious. So, another question that a guy would like to ask his girl is that does she talk bad about her friends. To be frank, the ones whom one calls her friend, she can never talk bad about him or her.</p>

<h1>Do you watch porn? If yes, how often?</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813009/3000fbb2-8306-11e6-873d-4fdec1d7d180.jpg">
This one got to be another question that would interest a guy. He might want to ask this to her girlfriend if she also enjoys watching porn and how often does she watches them. well, the answer can be most of them don’t even like to think of doing this. This is because girls are more of mental than visual. They believe in imagination and storyline, so watching such poorly acted video might not be their thing.</p>

<h1>Why do you take so much time while taking a shower?</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813012/300bd708-8306-11e6-8ce2-593994244b55.jpg">
It is found that many girls take a lot of time in bathing. So, the guy is always inquisitive to know that what makes his girl also spend so much time in bathing.</p>

<h1>What would you say about No shave November?</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19012722/24349d3c-87db-11e6-8feb-199618ef89e7.jpg">
There is no denying the fact that girls also need to shave certain areas of their body, where it is inevitable. But like the boys it is very common that girls feel lazy about this too. So, this one would definitely make a guy pose a question on her girly.</p>

<h1>What habit/habits do you hate in your guy?</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813010/30039124-8306-11e6-8adc-0859f99f37ae.jpg">
Well, this one would be a beneficial question for every guy. If they dare to ask the bad habits in them that their girl hates and wants them to change, it would somewhere do good to them as well as their relationship, provided that the girl answers honestly.</p>

<h1>Do you like to check out other guys just for an eye candy?</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19012723/249edd32-87db-11e6-94a2-917ac0edaf9d.jpg">
Yet another question that every guy would rush on is that how often do their girlfriend checks out other guys for providing an eye candy to themselves.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do You Love Her or Just a Crush Find It Out Here]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/25/do-you-love-her-or-just-a-crush-find-it-out-here/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-25T12:29:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/25/do-you-love-her-or-just-a-crush-find-it-out-here</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813044/82b6d6a0-8307-11e6-9a62-386a7c5b5470.jpg" width="400" height="500">
Getting confused between liking someone and loving her is a very normal thing. Most of the guys take years to realize that they love a girl or it is just a cute little crush that they have on them. In fact, many a times it happens so that even after coming into a relationship, they are confused about whether they love her or they just have a crush on her. To clear this confusion a little bit, here is a small attempt that would make you realize the difference between love and crush:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Temporary feeling:</h1>

<p>Crush is temporary feeling. It is nothing but attraction. If you have a crush on a girl, you will only have such a feeling when the girl is around you. When she is not around, you would not feel anything like attraction but in case of love, you will their presence in every moment of your life.</p>

<h1>Priority</h1>

<p>When you love someone, she would be your priority and you would value her more than yourselves. Sometimes, you would even do anything or go anywhere for her, without even giving a second thought to it but in case of crush, you would not have that much of guts to do ‘anything’ for her. Somewhere, you will resist taking the risk.</p>

<h1>On your mind, all the time</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813077/6988c584-8308-11e6-9670-9cf2b13c6603.png">
You will like your life to be filled with her memories, when you love a girl. Perhaps, you would feel her right, even if she is wrong at some point. Her behavior would not change even an inch of your love for her. Also, you would remember each and every moment you spend or spent with her but in case of crush, you would only start to think of her when someone talks about her to you or she appears in front of you.</p>

<h1>Their happiness makes you happy</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813075/69758de8-8308-11e6-857b-d1ca929128da.jpg">
When you love a girl, her happiness would make you happier than yours  but if it is just a mere crush, you would feel happy for them but prioritize your happiness.</p>

<h1>Hard to forget</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813076/697b1420-8308-11e6-8abb-ad4d6b607cbb.jpg" width="500" height="600">
If you truly love her, it would be hard to forget her after she is gone. You might take her out of your life but you can never take her out of your mind as well as heart. You will feel her in everyone you come across but crush fades away with the passage of time and as the person moves away from your life.</p>

<h1>What she feels, bothers you</h1>

<p>When you are in love with a girl, you are affected by what she likes or dislikes, what are her desires, or what interests her the most. All these things would keep on rolling in your mind even if she has left you. On the contrary, when you have a crush on a girl, you would attempt to know her likes and dislikes and what other feelings she has but that would be for a short period of time. The moment you stop receiving a response since long, it would hardly bother you.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Issues Faced by Youth Today]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/24/5-issues-faced-by-youth-today/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-24T12:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/24/5-issues-faced-by-youth-today</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806702/1383d1da-8252-11e6-9496-1494d04dfaf1.jpg" width="400" height="500">
In the modern scenario, the serious issues and concerns related to kids are coming to light slowly and gradually and now that we have entered this new era, the society also has begun to recognize them. not only are they coming to the notice, but also, a need to find solution to these is arising. So, to familiarize a person with these, we are listing a few here:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Obesity</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806695/d139813a-8251-11e6-8b4c-29e68ff9c41f.jpg">
A very common thing to hear but can be a serious concern, if we ponder upon deeply. The kids belonging to today’s generation are gaining weight and getting fatter and fatter day by day and mind it- there is a difference between chubby and obese. It can be said that it is an aftermath of social media and that the modern gadgets have made humans a slave to technology. Kids spend hours and hours sitting in front of television or a computer instead of indulging themselves in outdoor activities. As a result, they are gaining more of weight. The quote- ‘All work no play, makes Jack a dull boy’ fits perfectly to them. Ultimately, this leads to acute disorders like depression, lowered self-esteemed, self-confidence going null, and so on. Also, other maladies like fluctuations in blood pressure and diabetes are two of the consequences.</p>

<h1>Unemployment</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806697/0152688c-8252-11e6-9621-eb42310db0aa.jpg">
It is a well-known fact that a developing country faces too much of employment problem. The present youth is capable enough and also possesses the right qualification but there is a lack of employment opportunities in the country. This renders them jobless, doing nothing, which then leads to catastrophic results like suicide or taking some other dangerous step.</p>

<h1>Relationships</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806702/1383d1da-8252-11e6-9496-1494d04dfaf1.jpg">
One of the major issues faced by 90 percent of youngsters today is failure in love relationships. As per Maslow’s Need Hierarchy Theory, love or belongingness is one of our needs that holds priority in life. But, looking at today’s youth, it seems like there whole world revolves around the person they fall in love with. If they find themselves stuck in a relationship where there is lack of love or respect or due to any other reason, it fails; they end up harming themselves or taking a disastrous action.</p>

<h1>Poverty</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806710/501cb7c4-8252-11e6-8abd-5351e2df9d17.jpg">
Poverty can be considered yet another element that profoundly effects the youth as well as their psychology today. The division of families based on income creates disparity among people and the kids have to live in poverty. Just because their parents cannot earn sufficient amount of money, the little ones are also deprived of government assistance. As a result their childhood goes dingy and their future bleak.</p>

<h1>Alcohol/Drug addiction</h1>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806701/1381cb88-8252-11e6-9bc3-5ea2f381af58.gif">
Drugs and alcohol are being consumed like candies and beverages in today’s world and the most addicted ones to these are the youngsters of today. Not only boys, but also young girls can be found with a cigarette or a packet of cocaine in their hands. In addition, the modern trends like hookah parlors and going out for clubbing are kindling the fire.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Shop From Streets]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/19/why-shop-from-streets/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-19T22:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/19/why-shop-from-streets</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641943/62d0d65a-7ebc-11e6-8e60-9e56dd3ac1bd.jpg" width="450" height="600" title="Bargaining" >
With advent of many e-commerce sites and recent emergence of mall culture in india, here are top 7 reasons why street shopping is still a hit.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641945/62e48c2c-7ebc-11e6-9beb-387444617a2c.jpg"></p>

<h2>1. Bargaining is fun - every girl&rsquo;s right</h2>

<p>A bargain is something you don&rsquo;t need at a price you can&rsquo;t resist. - Franklin Jones
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641944/62d14356-7ebc-11e6-83a4-141257d22e5e.jpg"></p>

<h2>2. Street food - The only thing I like better than talking about food is eating : John Walters</h2>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641950/636edf3a-7ebc-11e6-8d15-9086fe5841ab.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641949/636b5928-7ebc-11e6-89bf-28aa02e085db.jpg"></p>

<h2>3. No need of cards -&ldquo;Na credit card bada na debit, sabse bada rupaiya!!&rdquo;</h2>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641946/6320e73a-7ebc-11e6-9928-56e494cabd75.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641948/6340981e-7ebc-11e6-8a68-fdc9d2aa4502.jpg"></p>

<h2>4. Worth every penny - value for money</h2>

<p>It is not the money that matters, it&rsquo;s how you use it that determines its true value.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641956/63f894c8-7ebc-11e6-97f9-a8671888260f.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641957/6403da04-7ebc-11e6-82d1-8b5ab7a252bb.jpg"></p>

<h2>5. Verify your goods - goods are tangible</h2>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641960/6489419e-7ebc-11e6-8879-fc1586f2d9a7.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641962/64aeb42e-7ebc-11e6-99b1-2ffcedeeedad.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641963/64c10cb4-7ebc-11e6-9f42-6c8746127e7b.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641959/642e4b04-7ebc-11e6-80ff-8ab40b5ecc3a.jpg"></p>

<h2>6. No hidden costs - no shipping, packages, delievery charges</h2>

<p>The price you see is the price you pay !!
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641954/63e39e92-7ebc-11e6-999b-7502c54105cc.jpg">
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641955/63f61284-7ebc-11e6-9f8d-4205a1779b11.jpg"></p>

<h2>7. Friendly staff - To help you choose</h2>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641952/63b8b1be-7ebc-11e6-90a6-4fbbb7c9a7a7.jpg"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
