<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[JunkJam Blog - Street Market! Fashion! LifeStyle!]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2016-10-05T21:36:13+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Overcome a BAD Breakup]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/04/How-to-overcome-from-breakup/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-04T13:18:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/04/How-to-overcome-from-breakup</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif">
Break ups can be very difficult to deal with and looking at how fast paced our lives are, it is difficult to make time for you and cope up with all the depression phase.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Needless to talk about how you have to deal with all the people around who if know about the break up, keep asking how you feeling and those who don’t know keep wondering
if there is something wrong you are going through mentally. However, we have got a few ways in which you can handle a break up without going through much of self- disappointment or depression.
Hope this tips help you and do the best for you</p>

<h1>Block him or unfriend him from all social media platforms.</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104511/8a2b50b4-8afa-11e6-9cc1-5252742b2490.gif">
You might feel like a grownup that does not need to do all this but trust us, this helps BIG time! Off course you do not what his name popping up in your notifications. This might keep reminding you of him and plus getting updates about what he is up to while are trying to move on can worsen things up for you.</p>

<h1>Do not jump into the ‘let us just be friends’ stage too soon.</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104513/8a3137f4-8afa-11e6-95b4-262e04c3a847.gif">
It is advisable to give yourself sometime to figure things out and realize what needs to be changed and what does not. If he suggests this then tell him that you need some time to think about it. Usually one wish to be just friends while the other expects more out of it, and at such you a state, you might want to have things clear and no confusions involved.</p>

<h1>If you are ever tempted to drink, take a friend along.</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104510/8a288564-8afa-11e6-9ee7-b4d811ee0964.gif">
Drinking while you are alone and sad after a break up is very common.Although some find it a convenient way to deal with such traumatic situations, it is not really a solution to it. If you are tempted to go for a drink, take a trusted friend along who would make sure you don’t up making regrettable choices when you are drunk.</p>

<h1>Start up an intense work out regime.</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104512/8a2c681e-8afa-11e6-8e6c-81d934bc15db.gif">
You might have come across options like these which people usually choose. The point is to boost your self-confidence and keep you focus on your own well-being. Moreover, doing something such as kickboxing is a great way of getting all the inner frustration out and doing something productive.</p>

<h1>Allow yourself to cry whenever you need to.</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif">
This one can be a bit confusing but letting it all go and getting yourself out of the phase should be your motive.</p>

<p>Most importantly give time to do things that you like doing and being around people who love and care for you.
Before loving others, it is important to love ourselves, beginnings could be little difficult but once you start initiating things, you feel good about it. Remember the solution is always live up in the present than recalling the past. Your life is important.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Sweetest Ways to Tell Your Partner About Your Pregnancy]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/03/How-to-tell-him-about-your-pregnancy/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-03T13:18:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/03/How-to-tell-him-about-your-pregnancy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103253/6908ad66-8af3-11e6-91d1-6fff11b6948d.jpg" width="500" height="600">
Being in a long distance relationship it took us long time to plan a kid. Finally the good news arrived and I was pregnant by 2 month. The joy was to the cloud and back.
Even if you are sure and going to be new parents to be., here are some sweetest way to tell your partner the same, the tips are as follows:-</p>

<!--more-->


<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103252/69043c4a-8af3-11e6-9f8b-94abc6787cd6.jpg" width="500" height="600"></p>

<h1>Cupcake delight</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103265/74fef99a-8af3-11e6-920c-a7f23ce2d3b2.gif">
The customized cup cakes could do all that wonders. A romantic and surprise cup cake for soon to be daddy will be a perfect one.</p>

<h1>Sweeter box of chocolates</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103324/d22f1b0e-8af3-11e6-8cf9-af577009b9c1.gif">
They are most easy thing to bake and spelling daddy on every piece of chocolate could be an good option to break the news.</p>

<h1>Jigsaw puzzle</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103487/b9ff3702-8af4-11e6-980d-58f1642709a3.gif">
When you wish to give him that nail bitting moment and keep that fun of surprise on then jigsaw puzzle could be a perfect option for you.</p>

<h1>Coffee mug hidden message</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103527/fa6adfee-8af4-11e6-91bb-eb0400a56351.jpg">
Imagine that he has entered home after long time, in order to break the ice and start conversations coffee would be an ideal option. The best way to express your feelings is that the message in the interiors of the mug could express it better. Planning a coffee together could be the best one.</p>

<h1>Baby lottery</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103528/fa6c06b2-8af4-11e6-9acd-715e023c210e.jpg">
Times have gone where people only used scratch cards to win lottery or recharge, you can even use scratch card to announce your pregnancy.</p>

<h1>Announcing on customized t-shirt</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103530/faa56cea-8af4-11e6-9f18-f4146c0cfb84.jpg">
Hip hurray we are going to be new parents to be, trust us fun will be different when he will wear a t-shirt. You could choose from variants of colors.</p>

<h1>Baby cake pops</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103529/fa912dd4-8af4-11e6-8ec1-6d45336494be.gif">
This time is right  to express your creativity to loved ones. You could order for baby cake pops and when he arrives surprise him with that.</p>

<h1>Small cute plate on dining table</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103526/fa6a651e-8af4-11e6-983c-830bcc351508.jpg">
A little spoon, dish and bowl with handwritten message will bring that big blushing smile.</p>

<h1>Baby photos everywhere</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103528/fa6c06b2-8af4-11e6-9acd-715e023c210e.jpg">
Before he gets up from the bed, fill your bedroom with lot of photos. We are sure that cute baby photos will also melt his heart. Doing your own photoshoot with some cute dolls to surprise him will also work wonders.</p>

<h1>Take him for garden stroll</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19120993/84af3fcc-8b42-11e6-851b-63fbc6f8b7ae.jpg">
There is nothing pure like nature and revealing heart out. Breaking the news of baby may require some peaceful environment; taking him to toddlers play area will give him that different joy all together.</p>

<p>Relationship grows better with a new arrival of new kid. Motherhood is all together different joy. We insist all of you to eat right and fresh.
Enjoy the present with all good moments. We are sure that these tips will surely bring in more joy than anything else. You could go boundless with creativity even if you are planning to do DIY.
“I love you” is always worth to say for giving him that perfect good feeling.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deal It Right for Perfect Dream Date!]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/03/first-date-tips/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-03T13:16:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/03/first-date-tips</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19019990/4b9ea3b6-88b9-11e6-818a-201fac58cebd.gif">
Dating online is no more a taboo. It has become a pretty normal way of finding dating partners. Not to miss out some relationships that turned into having a bright future.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Online dating can be a very tricky business. While it can work wonders for a few, it can even become troublesome for others. Under such circumstances, one must be self-informed about everything that goes around.
Not all online experiences turn out to be good ones and thus, here are a few tips which will help you connect to a partner suitable for you and also help you avoid making silly mistakes:</p>

<h1>Select a good site.</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19020016/39b50720-88ba-11e6-8e6a-7a36570515e0.jpg">
Even before you start dreaming about your to-be date; it is necessary to give enough time to select an appropriate site for online dating. While there are sites which allow you to make choice for yourself from a number of members using the same website, there are also sites that suggest dates to you based on your compatibility.
If you wish to have the freedom of choice and are ready to go through hundreds of accounts, then the prior one is what you should be looking for.</p>

<h1>Choose someone with similar interests.</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19020012/25cb172c-88ba-11e6-8221-7356013943f9.jpg">
If you are specific about what you are looking for, for example, of a particular community or work place or a defined age group or even in terms of preferred sexuality, there exist sites which work wholly based on that particular category.
This way it will be much more sorted, easier and faster. Also while choosing a partner; people like to usual go for someone with whom they share similar interest. This helps you to start a good conversation.</p>

<h1>Not being too choosy is the key.</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19020014/31813178-88ba-11e6-8acb-5611f4cd88d4.jpg">
It is a human tendency to make a list of have’s and have not’s when you start talking to each other or meet on the first date. You might have thoughts like ‘he doesn’t dress well’ or ‘she does not have good eyes’ or ‘he does not earn enough’.
However, when you are going for online dating, it is very important to have an open mind and not to be too much judgmental about everything. Letting your inner voice stay at peace and seeing what’s kept on the plate for you is a wise choice. You might as well turn out to like the person.</p>

<h1>Be honest.</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19019984/1b259cf8-88b9-11e6-88ad-4a78b058f81a.gif">
The truth can’t be denied that it is very tempting to exaggerate or stretch things while writing your bio. Nevertheless, lying can lead to a number of disappointments in the future. It is best to stay honest since the start and have nothing to hide about.
False revealing can make you lose a potential partner. Not pretending or trying to be someone or something you are not is the best option to go for.</p>

<p>Online dating has become a fade lately because of which it has become very important to beware aboutpeople who use these sites for their selfish needs or to trick people. One ‘must’ stand by rule is to keep it low at the start. Do not give too many details.
Rest is all that your personality and charms needs to manage.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Movies Related to Womens Issues Everyone Should Watch at Least Once]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/26/top-10-movies-related-to-womens-issues-everyone-should-watch-at-least-once/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-26T12:29:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/26/top-10-movies-related-to-womens-issues-everyone-should-watch-at-least-once</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015068/5707e8d8-881a-11e6-9af6-6ca86c160dd6.jpg" width="600" height="500">
It all began with eve teasing, slowly took the form of molestation, and finally turned into brutal rape. There is no denying the fact that the issues related to women have increased to great extent now days.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Even though, there have arrived various laws and norms for the safety of females in our country but still the number of such issues has not gone down, in fact, these have increased in the past few years.
No matter, how much this menace keeps on rising, there are still such people in the society who will keep on attempting to do things that create awareness in the minds of people regarding the safety of women. One such awareness is created in the minds of public through empowering movies related to women’s issues. So, we picked some great ones and brought a list for you:</p>

<h1>Arth</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015062/5699e590-881a-11e6-953a-b870094f3719.jpg">
This movie is based on the internal struggle of two women who make a man pivot of their existence. One women rejects every male in order to lead a single and independent life and the other one ditches the man after self-introspection. At the end, women are portrayed as winners.</p>

<h1>Aastha: In the prison of spring</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015061/565c2d68-881a-11e6-9ba7-af8d36328d6f.jpg">
This movie pictured the female protagonist to another realm where a bored house wife turns into a prostitute at night and fulfills the chasm of materialistic needs of life. It was directed by Basu Bhattacharya in 1997.</p>

<h1>Lajja</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015065/56d46206-881a-11e6-9977-531ffcba500c.jpg">
Filmed in the year 2001, Lajja is another female centric movie that depicts a land where women worshipped as shakti are humiliated and killed just because they are females. Directed by Rajkumar Santoshi, it highlights societal malpractices.</p>

<h1>The Dirty Picture</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015070/57376f2c-881a-11e6-8100-a44d2e945470.jpg">
This movie characterizes Vidya as southern siren Silk Smitha, a woman who was not ashamed of her physique, instead, she flaunts it, without caring about the repressed sexuality. She shone like a star and was hailed as a female hero.</p>

<h1>Kahaani</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015148/3a1cb3dc-881c-11e6-95dd-d06eb627cbff.jpg">
Cinematographed in 2012, Kahaani shows another amazing performance by Vidya Balan. The plot of the movie showcased the inner reserves of a woman’s power. Despite of being pregnant, she goes on her mission and completes it with vigor and zeal.</p>

<h1>Jazbaa</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015063/56c29828-881a-11e6-966f-f6578f858a55.jpg">
Jazbaa is another women centric movie that stars Aishwarya Rai Bacchan, an attorney forced to defend a criminal after her daughter was kidnapped.</p>

<h1>Sarabjit</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015069/5712efbc-881a-11e6-9f4b-7ff5a440d54d.jpg">
This movie also pictures Aishwarya Rai Bacchan in the role of Dalbir Kaur who falls a prey to an abusive husband. She leaves him and starts living with her brother’s family, working as an independent woman.</p>

<h1>Neerja</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015149/3a5a415c-881c-11e6-83af-3cd9e6fc478e.jpg">
In Neerja, Sonam Kapoor played the role of the courageous flight attendant who had to lose her life in order to save the highjacked plane from terrorists.</p>

<h1>Piku</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015067/56fd8ece-881a-11e6-9695-2f7342e143b2.jpg">
Piku is a light and humorous film showing Deepika Padukone as an independent single lady who has to give up on her dreams and desires in order to take care of her old father.</p>

<h1>Pink</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015068/5707e8d8-881a-11e6-9af6-6ca86c160dd6.jpg">
It is an Indian Courtroom Drama that conveys that women should have the liberty to walk and speak freely at night.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Questions Every Guy Wants to Ask His Girl]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/25/7-questions-every-guy-wants-to-ask-his-girl/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-25T12:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/25/7-questions-every-guy-wants-to-ask-his-girl</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813009/3000fbb2-8306-11e6-873d-4fdec1d7d180.jpg" width="400" height="500">
Every guy is curious about his girl. Apart from the fact, that he loves her so much, there still some ‘questions that he certainly thinks of asking to her. Here we have a list of interrogations that a guy would like to have with his girl:</p>

<!-- more -->


<p><br/><br/><br/><br/></p>

<h1>Why do you spend so much time on makeup?</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813011/300899ee-8306-11e6-88a2-16ea09db0b3e.jpg" width="600" height="500">
Often, most of the girls are seen with little or too much makeup on. There is hardly any girl who does not likes to put on makeup in order to look good. So, this can be one of the questions that a guy would probably want to ask her girl that why does she spend so much time on doing makeup. And the answer would be because the girls like the way they look in it. Also, it is fun to wear makeup.</p>

<h1>How frequently do you talk bad about your friends?</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813008/2fee873e-8306-11e6-8ee1-2aa132311b0a.jpg">
There is a difference between gossiping about someone and talking bad about them. Gossip can be harmless but talking bad can be something serious. So, another question that a guy would like to ask his girl is that does she talk bad about her friends. To be frank, the ones whom one calls her friend, she can never talk bad about him or her.</p>

<h1>Do you watch porn? If yes, how often?</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813009/3000fbb2-8306-11e6-873d-4fdec1d7d180.jpg">
This one got to be another question that would interest a guy. He might want to ask this to her girlfriend if she also enjoys watching porn and how often does she watches them. well, the answer can be most of them don’t even like to think of doing this. This is because girls are more of mental than visual. They believe in imagination and storyline, so watching such poorly acted video might not be their thing.</p>

<h1>Why do you take so much time while taking a shower?</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813012/300bd708-8306-11e6-8ce2-593994244b55.jpg">
It is found that many girls take a lot of time in bathing. So, the guy is always inquisitive to know that what makes his girl also spend so much time in bathing.</p>

<h1>What would you say about No shave November?</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19012722/24349d3c-87db-11e6-8feb-199618ef89e7.jpg">
There is no denying the fact that girls also need to shave certain areas of their body, where it is inevitable. But like the boys it is very common that girls feel lazy about this too. So, this one would definitely make a guy pose a question on her girly.</p>

<h1>What habit/habits do you hate in your guy?</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813010/30039124-8306-11e6-8adc-0859f99f37ae.jpg">
Well, this one would be a beneficial question for every guy. If they dare to ask the bad habits in them that their girl hates and wants them to change, it would somewhere do good to them as well as their relationship, provided that the girl answers honestly.</p>

<h1>Do you like to check out other guys just for an eye candy?</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19012723/249edd32-87db-11e6-94a2-917ac0edaf9d.jpg">
Yet another question that every guy would rush on is that how often do their girlfriend checks out other guys for providing an eye candy to themselves.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do You Love Her or Just a Crush Find It Out Here]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/25/do-you-love-her-or-just-a-crush-find-it-out-here/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-25T12:29:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/25/do-you-love-her-or-just-a-crush-find-it-out-here</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813044/82b6d6a0-8307-11e6-9a62-386a7c5b5470.jpg" width="400" height="500">
Getting confused between liking someone and loving her is a very normal thing. Most of the guys take years to realize that they love a girl or it is just a cute little crush that they have on them. In fact, many a times it happens so that even after coming into a relationship, they are confused about whether they love her or they just have a crush on her. To clear this confusion a little bit, here is a small attempt that would make you realize the difference between love and crush:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Temporary feeling:</h1>

<p>Crush is temporary feeling. It is nothing but attraction. If you have a crush on a girl, you will only have such a feeling when the girl is around you. When she is not around, you would not feel anything like attraction but in case of love, you will their presence in every moment of your life.</p>

<h1>Priority</h1>

<p>When you love someone, she would be your priority and you would value her more than yourselves. Sometimes, you would even do anything or go anywhere for her, without even giving a second thought to it but in case of crush, you would not have that much of guts to do ‘anything’ for her. Somewhere, you will resist taking the risk.</p>

<h1>On your mind, all the time</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813077/6988c584-8308-11e6-9670-9cf2b13c6603.png">
You will like your life to be filled with her memories, when you love a girl. Perhaps, you would feel her right, even if she is wrong at some point. Her behavior would not change even an inch of your love for her. Also, you would remember each and every moment you spend or spent with her but in case of crush, you would only start to think of her when someone talks about her to you or she appears in front of you.</p>

<h1>Their happiness makes you happy</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813075/69758de8-8308-11e6-857b-d1ca929128da.jpg">
When you love a girl, her happiness would make you happier than yours  but if it is just a mere crush, you would feel happy for them but prioritize your happiness.</p>

<h1>Hard to forget</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813076/697b1420-8308-11e6-8abb-ad4d6b607cbb.jpg" width="500" height="600">
If you truly love her, it would be hard to forget her after she is gone. You might take her out of your life but you can never take her out of your mind as well as heart. You will feel her in everyone you come across but crush fades away with the passage of time and as the person moves away from your life.</p>

<h1>What she feels, bothers you</h1>

<p>When you are in love with a girl, you are affected by what she likes or dislikes, what are her desires, or what interests her the most. All these things would keep on rolling in your mind even if she has left you. On the contrary, when you have a crush on a girl, you would attempt to know her likes and dislikes and what other feelings she has but that would be for a short period of time. The moment you stop receiving a response since long, it would hardly bother you.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Issues Faced by Youth Today]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/24/5-issues-faced-by-youth-today/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-24T12:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/24/5-issues-faced-by-youth-today</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806702/1383d1da-8252-11e6-9496-1494d04dfaf1.jpg" width="400" height="500">
In the modern scenario, the serious issues and concerns related to kids are coming to light slowly and gradually and now that we have entered this new era, the society also has begun to recognize them. not only are they coming to the notice, but also, a need to find solution to these is arising. So, to familiarize a person with these, we are listing a few here:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Obesity</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806695/d139813a-8251-11e6-8b4c-29e68ff9c41f.jpg">
A very common thing to hear but can be a serious concern, if we ponder upon deeply. The kids belonging to today’s generation are gaining weight and getting fatter and fatter day by day and mind it- there is a difference between chubby and obese. It can be said that it is an aftermath of social media and that the modern gadgets have made humans a slave to technology. Kids spend hours and hours sitting in front of television or a computer instead of indulging themselves in outdoor activities. As a result, they are gaining more of weight. The quote- ‘All work no play, makes Jack a dull boy’ fits perfectly to them. Ultimately, this leads to acute disorders like depression, lowered self-esteemed, self-confidence going null, and so on. Also, other maladies like fluctuations in blood pressure and diabetes are two of the consequences.</p>

<h1>Unemployment</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806697/0152688c-8252-11e6-9621-eb42310db0aa.jpg">
It is a well-known fact that a developing country faces too much of employment problem. The present youth is capable enough and also possesses the right qualification but there is a lack of employment opportunities in the country. This renders them jobless, doing nothing, which then leads to catastrophic results like suicide or taking some other dangerous step.</p>

<h1>Relationships</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806702/1383d1da-8252-11e6-9496-1494d04dfaf1.jpg">
One of the major issues faced by 90 percent of youngsters today is failure in love relationships. As per Maslow’s Need Hierarchy Theory, love or belongingness is one of our needs that holds priority in life. But, looking at today’s youth, it seems like there whole world revolves around the person they fall in love with. If they find themselves stuck in a relationship where there is lack of love or respect or due to any other reason, it fails; they end up harming themselves or taking a disastrous action.</p>

<h1>Poverty</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806710/501cb7c4-8252-11e6-8abd-5351e2df9d17.jpg">
Poverty can be considered yet another element that profoundly effects the youth as well as their psychology today. The division of families based on income creates disparity among people and the kids have to live in poverty. Just because their parents cannot earn sufficient amount of money, the little ones are also deprived of government assistance. As a result their childhood goes dingy and their future bleak.</p>

<h1>Alcohol/Drug addiction</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806701/1381cb88-8252-11e6-9bc3-5ea2f381af58.gif">
Drugs and alcohol are being consumed like candies and beverages in today’s world and the most addicted ones to these are the youngsters of today. Not only boys, but also young girls can be found with a cigarette or a packet of cocaine in their hands. In addition, the modern trends like hookah parlors and going out for clubbing are kindling the fire.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Shop From Streets]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/19/why-shop-from-streets/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-19T22:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/19/why-shop-from-streets</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641943/62d0d65a-7ebc-11e6-8e60-9e56dd3ac1bd.jpg" width="450" height="600" title="Bargaining" >
With advent of many e-commerce sites and recent emergence of mall culture in india, here are top 7 reasons why street shopping is still a hit.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641945/62e48c2c-7ebc-11e6-9beb-387444617a2c.jpg"></p>

<h2>1. Bargaining is fun - every girl&rsquo;s right</h2>

<p>A bargain is something you don&rsquo;t need at a price you can&rsquo;t resist. - Franklin Jones
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641944/62d14356-7ebc-11e6-83a4-141257d22e5e.jpg"></p>

<h2>2. Street food - The only thing I like better than talking about food is eating : John Walters</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641950/636edf3a-7ebc-11e6-8d15-9086fe5841ab.jpg">
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641949/636b5928-7ebc-11e6-89bf-28aa02e085db.jpg"></p>

<h2>3. No need of cards -&ldquo;Na credit card bada na debit, sabse bada rupaiya!!&rdquo;</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641946/6320e73a-7ebc-11e6-9928-56e494cabd75.jpg">
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641948/6340981e-7ebc-11e6-8a68-fdc9d2aa4502.jpg"></p>

<h2>4. Worth every penny - value for money</h2>

<p>It is not the money that matters, it&rsquo;s how you use it that determines its true value.
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641956/63f894c8-7ebc-11e6-97f9-a8671888260f.jpg">
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641957/6403da04-7ebc-11e6-82d1-8b5ab7a252bb.jpg"></p>

<h2>5. Verify your goods - goods are tangible</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641960/6489419e-7ebc-11e6-8879-fc1586f2d9a7.jpg">
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641962/64aeb42e-7ebc-11e6-99b1-2ffcedeeedad.jpg">
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641963/64c10cb4-7ebc-11e6-9f42-6c8746127e7b.jpg">
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641959/642e4b04-7ebc-11e6-80ff-8ab40b5ecc3a.jpg"></p>

<h2>6. No hidden costs - no shipping, packages, delievery charges</h2>

<p>The price you see is the price you pay !!
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641954/63e39e92-7ebc-11e6-999b-7502c54105cc.jpg">
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641955/63f61284-7ebc-11e6-9f8d-4205a1779b11.jpg"></p>

<h2>7. Friendly staff - To help you choose</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18641952/63b8b1be-7ebc-11e6-90a6-4fbbb7c9a7a7.jpg"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Take Care of Your Skin Before Wedding]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/15/how-to-take-care-of-your-skin-before-wedding/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-15T12:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/15/how-to-take-care-of-your-skin-before-wedding</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18655783/4fb1ccf8-7f09-11e6-9548-e2f3978fe741.jpg" width="400" height="500">
When everything on your big day is so perfect and flawless, how can your skin stay far behind? When it comes make your skin ready for your special day, it must not be taken for granted but yes, do not take too much of stress as it can lead to unwanted and catastrophic results for your skin. To help you with this further, here we have some tips as to how you can get that perfect and radiant skin for your wedding:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Say no to new skin products</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18655781/4f711c3a-7f09-11e6-8ecb-9365c470bb8e.JPG">
Do not even think of trying any new products at least up to three weeks before your wedding and these products include skin care, make-up, hair care, and yes, even washing powder. In case an kind of skin reaction takes place, it can take a long time to calm down, which, I think none of the girls can afford before her wedding day.</p>

<h1>Do not leave it like a last minute decision</h1>

<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18655782/4fb17a82-7f09-11e6-9c13-3a666297811e.jpg">
The earlier you figure out the skin issues and decide to start working on them, the better would it be for you. In addition, using the products that exfoliate your skin would be a great help in getting rid of the dead skin cells. When the dead cells are removed, your skin would look fresh and the color complexion of your skin would be enhanced manifolds. Also, do not forget to use a good SPF to avoid damaged skin due to exposure to sun.</p>

<h1>Green tea, your best friend</h1>

<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18655783/4fb1ccf8-7f09-11e6-9548-e2f3978fe741.jpg">
Green tea has as many benefits as you want to count. It has always been beneficial to drink green tea. Not only can this help with weight loss but also its anti-oxidant properties help reduce acne and brighten the skin.</p>

<h1>Drink plenty of water</h1>

<p>Water is undoubtedly a wonder liquid. The more water intake you do, the more benefits you are going to get. It is believed that drinking more and more water brings glow on your face. Medically, acne and pimple are caused as a result of stomach disorders, so, drinking more of water, help heal stomach problems and consequently give a bright and beautiful skin. Water also pinkens your lips.</p>

<h1>Eat lot of fruits</h1>

<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18655784/5009e23a-7f09-11e6-8a88-09891b2e754d.jpg">
The essential nutrients in fruits like papaya, cucumber, tomato are said to bring a kind of flamboyant glow to your skin. So, as and when your big day is near, start feeding yourself with a whole meal of fruits and let your skin have the complete food. Also, it helps your body gain vital minerals as well as vitamins that would keep you happy and energetic throughout the month.</p>

<p>So girls, not to worry! We have got a solution to all your wedding related issues. Just keep following the aforesaid steps with dedication and this would definitely pave way for a clear and glowing skin that would make your better half a complete fan of yours. Stay happy, stay petty, coz happy girls are the prettiest!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Honeymoon Dresses to Wow Him]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/15/5-honeymoon-dresses-to-wow-him/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-15T12:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/15/5-honeymoon-dresses-to-wow-him</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550457/95725a82-7b71-11e6-9e6b-2924f7b15b7e.jpg" width="400" height="500">
After the wedding ceremonies are done, the newly wedded couple is all ready to get set and go for their honeymoon. You want everything to be the best, be it the honeymoon destination, the venue where you’ll b staying, the places that you are going to visit, the activities you are going to do, the places you are going to eat or shop. Everything is planned in advance and you just can’t wait to do it all. Your excitement level is simply unstoppable!</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Honeymoon! The dreamy phase of every girl’s life, where everything seems to be perfect and the way it had to be. So, you are in your dreamy phase and can’t keep your hands off each other. You just can’t wait to reach your honeymoon spot, but before you set out for it, do not forget to do your homework. Yes, we are talking about a few pretty and hot outfits that would simply make him go nuts over your beauty! Also, a dress chosen wisely can make it an amazing as well as a never forgetting honeymoon for you. Here are a few suggestions as to what dresses can you take along on your honeymoon and have those picture perfect memories:</p>

<h1>Evening dress</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550455/9558ed54-7b71-11e6-83a2-fb4d7c6986ed.jpg" width="600" height="700">
Nothing can make you look classier than an elegant yet sexy evening dress. They say red is the color of love so why not put on a red evening dress and have a candle light dinner beneath a sky lit with stars. Pair it with pencil heels and a beige or gold clutch and slay him!</p>

<h1>Floral tunic</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550456/956e0658-7b71-11e6-8438-a619ff6f4cc4.jpg" width="600" height="700">
A tiny tunic makes every girl look pretty and hot at the same time. So, wearing a cute floral dress while going out for shopping would not let him take his eyes off you. Putting on a light and natural makeup would add to the glow on your face and give you that perfect look that would make him love you more and more.</p>

<h1>Boho piece</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550453/951f542c-7b71-11e6-9634-8e3c1f603e84.jpg">
A boho one piece is all you need to have that attractive look for your honeymoon. Moreover, it would make your better half go completely crazy after you.</p>

<h1>Hot pants</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550454/954add72-7b71-11e6-95c6-97a8c9d5d202.jpg" width="600" height="700">
Hot pants give every girl a sexy chic look. So a denim hot pant wore with a sexy top or a cool tee accompanied by a pair of shades and  wedges would get you a look that would make his eyes glued to you.</p>

<h1>Barely there</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550457/95725a82-7b71-11e6-9e6b-2924f7b15b7e.jpg">
A beaded net top or dress in nude in color will leave a little to his imagination. The beaded threadwork on the outfit would make you look sexy and he would not be able to resist you anymore and you will be all set for a hot and amazing night.</p>

<p>Hope you like our suggestions on the kind of dresses that would make your honeymoon an extra special and extra hot one! Do not forget to click amazing pictures and make a beautiful collection of your beautiful memories.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Best Indian Wedding Songs for the Grand Bridal Entry]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/11/8-best-Indian-wedding-songs-for-the-grand-bridal-entry/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-11T12:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/11/8-best-Indian-wedding-songs-for-the-grand-bridal-entry</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417590/530a3f42-7852-11e6-9294-5bc2cd9fc9f9.jpg" width="400" height="500">
Wedding! The most auspicious and important day of every girl’s life! On this so very special day, everything ought to be perfect. From a beautiful bridal dress to the perfect background song during the entry, there needs to be sublimity in everything and every girl wants that these dreams come true.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Picture yourself on your wedding day walking down the alley with your favorite people by your side. The marvelous attire and a soft romantic song being played in the background, while you move towards your prince charming. Doesn’t it seem like a fairy tale where you are the princess and the evening belongs to you! So, to help you with this fairy tale turning into reality, we have a list of songs to make your bridal entry an epic one:</p>

<h1>Raabta</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417601/8875089c-7852-11e6-9126-72595dcd31f9.jpg">
Raabta song from the movie Agent Vinod can be an excellent choice to make the bridal entry a decent yet a grand one! The lyrics of the song, “Kehte Hai Khuda Ne…” perfectly fit the moment, addressing the bride’s and bridegroom’s emotions to each other.</p>

<h1>Din Shagna Da</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417608/ab9a5494-7852-11e6-86e9-a37cd6077c95.jpg">
I think Din Shagna Da is played at almost every Indian wedding when the beautiful maiden enters. There is hardly any wedding where we won’t hear “din shagna da chadheya” playing in the background, as the bride is stepping towards her to be husband.</p>

<h1>Sajde kiye hai laakhon</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417664/e7174404-7853-11e6-85f8-5e7d181c2eb8.jpg">
From the legend Akshay Kumar’s movie Khatta Meetha, Sajde kiye hai laakhon is also an ideal and lovely song that can be played at the time of bridal entry. The song is soothing to the ears and would perfectly convey the heart-tendering feelings going on in the hearts of the bridegroom as well as the bride.</p>

<h1>Tum se hi</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417668/0d05ea80-7854-11e6-9f8f-8fb2a24d8fd0.jpg">
Another amazing song for a bride’s entry is the song “Tum se hi” from the movie Jab we met. It describes how important both of them feel about each other.</p>

<h1>Teri Ore</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417590/530a3f42-7852-11e6-9294-5bc2cd9fc9f9.jpg">
I think there cannot be a better song that would best describe the moment. As the bride moves towards her better half, the lyrics of the song match every step she takes or each moment she does, while moving forward.</p>

<h1>O Re piya</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18617466/3d618402-7ded-11e6-94e6-4fc865e880cc.jpg">
The song “o re piya” sung by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan is good enough to grab people’s attention as and when you enter the venue on your big day.</p>

<h1>Kabira Encore</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417691/a6a4f28a-7854-11e6-9b88-444fff453698.jpg">
Kabira encore version is another wonderful song that can be played well when the bride enters the wedding hall. It makes the atmosphere so senti-menti that the people around start shedding tears looking at the bride.</p>

<h1>Latika’s theme song</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18617465/3d123bfe-7ded-11e6-9119-a3d8d6c156ce.jpg">
Sung by A.R. Rehman, from the movie Slum Dog Millionaire, this theme song is just a feeling that would definitely bring goose bumps on the skin of the listeners. The more you listen to this, the more you will feel it and love it.</p>

<p>So girls , on your big day, don’t let the DJs ruin your eye-catching entry by playing some cheap beats. Choose your own jingle for your special day!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Ways to Re-use Your Bridal Lehenga]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/05/7-ways-to-re-use-your-bridal-lehenga/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-05T21:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/05/7-ways-to-re-use-your-bridal-lehenga</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250508/6ecce898-73a1-11e6-918f-451afab578b6.jpg" width="400" height="500">
When it comes to choosing the Bridal Lehenga, we just never mind the thousands of rupees as well as the long hours spent in finalizing the same. We take extra initiative to customize it according to our preference and make it more attractive in every way possible. But what happens of that precious piece of clothing, the bridal lehenga , after the wedding. Well if I am not wrong, then half of my readers will raise their hand if I say its wrapped up in a malmal ka kapda safely in the wardrobe. Well here are some great ideas to re use your bridal lehenga in a classy fashion again and again.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Lessen the volume and Cut it along.</h1>

<p>Though it may sound very harsh and painful but one can surely lessen down the motifs and heavy embellishments by simply cutting it off and toning it down in its look. With the extra kalis removed which was forcefully inserted at that time or event with the net out it will look more subtle and wearable.
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250132/b938d0c4-739f-11e6-8ae8-f779a4d6da8a.jpg"></p>

<h1>Switch the style to Anarkali</h1>

<p>With the help of a good tailor, its quite easy to transform your wedding attire to an embellished anarkali which looks less bridal in comparison to a bridal lehenga. The skirt and the blouse can be stitched together with a waist belt or the same can be stitched with a separate simpler blouse to get the desired effect.
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250242/46f88c24-73a0-11e6-878e-0abb97a8dcf3.jpg"></p>

<h1>Long Kurtis with Lehengas</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250412/d8b718b0-73a0-11e6-847d-7d36d95ba8ab.jpg" width="500" height="600">
This is one of the most preferred styles that have hit the fashion world with a bang. And it is also a great way to reuse the bridal lehenga with a toned kurti and set the look. Even jackets with thin borders are also a good option to try along.</p>

<h1>Combining the bridal set with other attires</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250339/aaba739e-73a0-11e6-8b2f-a31b13861729.jpg">
Usually the bridal lehenga teamed up with designer blouses and embellished dupatta forms the bridal set and altogether they provide the bridal feel. So the best way is to team the lehenga with a toned top, wear the blouse with a plain skirt and use the dupatta with a neutral shaded salwar kameez.</p>

<h1>Color Blocks</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250285/73bdf9e2-73a0-11e6-8379-7be272a1b291.jpg">
It is not always necessary to team up bridal lehenga with same colored blouses. Color blocking is quite in the fashion so if the idea is to attend some wedding function then pair up the embellished lehenga with a no work blouse of different color and just set the elegant look for the occasion.</p>

<h1>Drape it as a saree</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250339/aaba739e-73a0-11e6-8b2f-a31b13861729.jpg">
There are many cases when the lehenga sets have a long flowing dupatta with loads of zari work on it. The best way to tone the dress down and still keep the charm is to drape the dupatta as a saree pallu and use a toned down blouse to maintain the classy look</p>

<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250508/6ecce898-73a1-11e6-918f-451afab578b6.jpg"></p>

<h1>Use as it is</h1>

<p>We all love our lehengas and honestly there are many who just don’t want to alter it. For them the best way to use it is by wearing it just as it is but with a simpler accessories, toned make up, and by letting the hair fall casually.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Destinations for Your Last Single Girls Trip]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/05/10-destinations-for-your-last-single-girls-trip/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-05T19:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/05/10-destinations-for-your-last-single-girls-trip</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239264/c88e218e-7361-11e6-8e2b-a9ef93478244.jpg" width="500" height="600">
Ever been on an ‘only girls’ trip? If you haven’t done it or thought about it yet then go girl, do it now! Yes, here we are referring to an all-girls trip before you step in to your married life. When it comes to your last ‘single girls’ trip, it has to be something unique and epic! Here are 10 destinations for you that would let you have the time of your life.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Udaipur</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18238964/74dbdab0-735f-11e6-9a66-a01849176716.jpg">
Do forts, lakes and palaces are something that interests you? If so, here is the perfect destination for you and your girlies and that’s none other than Udaipur. This place is situated to the south of Rajasthan and coming here would make you feel as if you are here to take pleasure of the rich and cultural heritage of your motherland.</p>

<h1>Amboli</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239048/325a3c6c-7360-11e6-99a8-785bb37b40dc.jpg">
If you are a nature lover, you are definitely going to get mesmerized with the eye-catching beauty of Amboli, a beautiful hill station in South Maharashtra. The panoramic view of Amboli Falls and Shirgaonkar Point will make you fall in love with this place. Added to the fun, spicy Malvani food would provide you the remaining satisfaction.</p>

<h1>Rishikesh</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239104/8969b64a-7360-11e6-8184-1917d5516b77.jpg">
Bring out the adrenaline junkie in you and be as adventurous as you can! Plan a road trip to Rishikesh and attend the Ganga aarti, taking place at Triven Ghat. Going Rishikesh and not doing river rafting would be regretful. Splash through the white waters of the place and give yourself a wave of thrilling fun. The treehouse café Little Buddha near Laxman Jhula is also worth a visit.</p>

<h1>Ladakh</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239194/2ad549f4-7361-11e6-8b14-d927e16ca65d.jpg">
Snow lovers would simply not resist going to Ladhakh. It is usually found that girls love snow all around, crystal clear lakes, all of it presenting nature at its best.</p>

<h1>Alleppey</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18655871/fb0ccb5c-7f09-11e6-95fa-2a3c51160a42.jpg">
Taking your best friends along and staying in a boathouse would be so much fun! The backwaters of Alleppey would let you have this fun with all the best girls of your life. Also, don’t forget to pay a visit to the Alleppey Beach.</p>

<h1>Nainital</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239229/7ce9e6be-7361-11e6-81de-534f8447f499.jpg">
Well, being a mini hill station of Uttarakhand, Nainital is not at all a bad option an all girls trip. The alluring Naini Lake and the mountains make this place a big hit among the travelers. The Kumaoni cuisine can also be tasted at its best when you visit this place.</p>

<h1>Ziro Valley, Arunachal Pradesh</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239113/968b815a-7360-11e6-8642-90103c7637f2.jpg">
Ziro Valley is counted amongst the most ‘worth watching’ places of Arunachal Pradesh. The Apatani Tribe and their rich and prosperous heritage can be a great source of knowledge about this place.</p>

<h1>Shimla</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239186/14a91f34-7361-11e6-93a3-f43aa76755a9.JPG">
For the ladies, here is the safest hill station Shimla and along with its breathtaking beauty, don’t miss out the Toy Train.</p>

<h1>Varanasi</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239104/8969b64a-7360-11e6-8184-1917d5516b77.jpg">
This divine city would arise the goddess in you and the morning boat ride is one of a kind.</p>

<h1>Sikkim</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239198/33fdf26a-7361-11e6-90df-fc8c286f3ab1.jpg">
The gorgeous valleys and the sky touching mountains accompanied by hot water springs are best of the combo that can be found in Sikkim, presenting the wow factor of north eastern India.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Do if You’re on Your Period on Your Wedding Day?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/03/period-on-your-wedding-day/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-03T19:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/03/period-on-your-wedding-day</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18057833/388b1bfa-6e2f-11e6-909b-e36c5d673d28.jpg" width="500" height="600">
Wedding Day is the most special day of every girl’s life. So, the special day of your life is about to arrive. Everything is planned, the perfect dress, the most romantic venue of the city, honeymoon destination, and what not? But oops! What’s happening? You suddenly realize your chums are here and you definitely did not invite them to your wedding. Well, the best way to avoid such a situation is to try and fit it into your marriage plans much before the time. If you happen to experience your period on wedding day, a few things can be done to avoid any kind of mishaps.
The first thing to be done is stay calm and composed. Keep a smile pasted to your face and enjoy the day. Here are some tips for you in case you happen to experience period on the most auspicious day of your life:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Rush to the doctor</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18058016/14777b54-6e30-11e6-872f-34f4ccc3da38.jpg" width="600" height="500">
In any case of uneasiness or a disease, all of us look for the doctor. Similarly, if you have these uninvited guests suddenly interrupting the special occasion of your life, doctor’s clinic is not far away! Start taking the pills two weeks before your period is due, it may delay your next period for your day. This might not be a foolproof solution though, but help’s for sure.</p>

<h1>Use a menstrual cup</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18058048/3c0b9786-6e30-11e6-96d6-e95ba80dca33.jpg">
They really do help: The menstrual cups can prove to be great help for the ‘aunt flo’ blunder that just took place. These cups can easily be inserted into the vagina and help cover the opening to the cervix. Tampons can also be used as a backup, otherwise pads are always your best friend during your menstrual cycle. These help prevent leakage. If you want to keep things tidy on your wedding night, the cup can also be inserted prior to sex.</p>

<h1>Make love on your wedding night anyways</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18057878/6d0618ee-6e2f-11e6-960c-e9cdb6fae890.jpg">
Due to extra sensitivity as well as lubrication, some women enjoy being intimate during their menstrual flow whereas, on the other hand, some find it more painful. Well, the whole thing entirely depends upon you and your better half. If your partner is ok with it, just go ahead and have an intercourse. Just make sure to take tiny precautions in order to avoid untidiness, like bring a towel along so that you can place it down to protect the bed.</p>

<p>In short, any of the brides can experience this mishap on the very special day of her life, but not to worry girls! There is always a solution to everything. Just don’t panic too much! Keep calm and tranquil, it’s your day girl! Enjoy it to the fullest and don’t forget to wear a smile all day long. This smile will add on to your glow on the wedding day. Discuss this with your friends and know each other’s experience in case such a thing ever happened to anyone of you.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Momos Point in Delhi]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/03/best-momos-point-in-delhi/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-03T19:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/03/best-momos-point-in-delhi</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17994563/5944851c-6b77-11e6-9c2c-0f5d9d67d482.jpg" width="500" height="600">
Who doesn’t love momos? I think there is hardly any food lover who could say a no to momos. Delhi is a city that offers a wide range of delicious and irresistible momos. While one wonders where to eat best vegetarian momos or best non-vegetarian momos or best fried momos or best tandoori or wheat momos in Delhi, one ought to try following places and give their taste buds a wave of happiness and satisfaction, making it crave for more. Moreover, you will find plenty of street momos in the city of Delhi, a few being:</p>

<!-- more -->


<p><br/>
<br/></p>

<h1>Dilli Haat</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17994566/594f2710-6b77-11e6-9a0f-4bcb608ed319.jpg">
Dilli Haat can be said to be heaven for the momos lovers. Ranging from vegetarian momos in paneer to non-vegetarian momos in pork, there is something for everyone. The Sikkim and Nagaland stall is the best place where you can grab tastiest ever street momos.
Momo’s Point, Kamla Nagar
Momo’s Point in Kamla Nagar serves usual momos with a great taste. In addition to these, they also have Masala Momos, with a desi, spicy touch.</p>

<h1>Brown Sugar, M Block Market,Greater Kailash</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17994563/5944851c-6b77-11e6-9c2c-0f5d9d67d482.jpg">
Located in the M block market of Greater Kailash, New Delhi, Brown Sugar serves some of the taste bud tingling momos of the city. The momos are popular by the name of wheat steamos and are served in different vegetarian as well as non-vegetarian varieties like Chicken, Mushroom, Spinach, and Paneer. Chicken Momos of this little café are a must try.</p>

<h1>Crazy Bruno, Anand Lok Market</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17994564/59461274-6b77-11e6-8f56-90e622620313.jpg">
When it comes to best momos of the city, how can one not remember the one and only name Crazy Bruno. Placed in Anand Lok Market, opposite Gargi College, this place serves a complete assortment of momos you just can’t deny. From Afghani Momos to Makhni Gravy Momos, Tandoori Momos, Malai Momos, Spicy Cheese Momos, and Crispy Chilly Momos, you may fall short of time but you can definitely not fall short of the different kinds of momos platted at this place.</p>

<h1>Dolma Aunty Momos, Lajpat Nagar</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17994568/597910b6-6b77-11e6-963e-4b93d5c1bfd8.jpg">
Dolma Aunty Momos of Central Market, Lajpat Nagar has been selling momos since last 20 years. Aunty’s chicken and paneer momos served with spicy chutney would invoke the foodie in you.</p>

<h1>Chalte Firte, Near DU</h1>

<p><img class="ceneter" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17994565/5946cfac-6b77-11e6-959e-f73fe58ecbb9.jpg">
Situated in Kamala Nagar, covering the vicinity of Delhi University, Chalte Firte serves items like Steamed Butter Masala Momos, Afghani Momos, and Fried Gravy Momos. Being another best momos point of the city, this place does a justice to the delicate dumplings called momos.</p>

<h1>Hawkers, Vasant Kunj</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17994569/597c5302-6b77-11e6-9640-922904481c16.jpg">
‘Hawkers’ is yet another classic food joint in Vasant Kunj area of New Delhi where you can find the most amazingly tasty fried moms. Only a glimpse would water your mouth.</p>

<h1>Tee Dee</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17994570/5984a124-6b77-11e6-8395-0167dfea82ee.jpg">
Perhaps, the best place for momos in Majnu Ka Tilla is Tee Dee, as you will find varieties like soupy momos in vegetarian, steamed, fried in Chicken and beef variants.</p>

<h1>Noodle Bowl, Dwarka</h1>

<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17994561/593cfc7a-6b77-11e6-9037-f117fe5a94be.jpg" width="300" height="400">
Noodle Bowl is your place if you are looking for juiciest pork momos in Dwarka. High on flavor, they offer quantities that are generous enough to satisfy your stomach. Also, they offer a home a delivery.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Just Educators but Role Models: Make Them Feel Special This Teachers Day!]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/03/teachers-day/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-03T13:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/03/teachers-day</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/18225112/167eff1c-7209-11e6-99cf-c6beb0d2bec8.jpg" width="500" height="600">
During our school days we had so many friends that we had to cut short the names of who to call on our birthdays and family
functions but when we grow up, after college and come into the corporate world, people get busy in their respective lives.
There are just a few friends left who remain close to our heart but our educators, our teachers are the ones who have thousands of people who remember them for ages.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/18225115/16879b40-7209-11e6-85f4-38703cabe40d.jpg" title="" >
Teachers moud us into respectable human beings and give us such life lessons that help us in our lives.
Isn’t it our moral duty to remember our teachers on their special day and make them feel special?
Teachers are the inspirational figures who give us the courage to constantly keep moving.
However, take out time from your corporate lives and make them feel special this teacher’s day.</p>

<h1>Token of appreciation</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/18225113/1680c78e-7209-11e6-8655-86c4fd6adbad.jpg">
Teachers deserve appreciation as they remember thousands of names, they know what we are best at and our weakness as well.
Take out time and order a gift of gratitude for them like a basket full of their favorite things (if at all, you remember what they like), you can also draw and make a special card for them or a scrapbook (if you have images with your teacher).
This gesture of appreciation will make the teachers feel it down their spine and will be a wonderful sign of gratification.</p>

<h1>Think creatively</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/18225111/15fff71c-7209-11e6-844a-887ddeb977b8.gif">
This is the era where people are not able to spare time for their families, they are so busy and engrossed in the daily chores that maintaining relations becomes a complicated task.
You don’t have to go out of the way but you can simply make your teachers feel special by making a creative picture and sending it on their Facebook with a heartwarming wish or a heartfelt message for them, make it certain that your teachers acknowledge the message and wishes.</p>

<h1>Celebrate together</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/18225119/364b684e-7209-11e6-9d82-5aa61b44ad9c.jpg">
Teachers are more than just our mentors, they are our role models. And if we can surprise them by going out of the way to meet them, nothing like it. Celebrate their special day and make them feel that they are important for you.
These are small-small things that make a huge difference.</p>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/18225114/1682527a-7209-11e6-9fe5-d168a5769271.jpg">
We might consider these things as trivial but for our teachers, it makes a huge difference for them when their pass-out students remember them and make them feel on the seventh heaven. This is just an act of reverence to make them feel wanted and upright. If you think about the school and college days; don’t you remember how your teachers molded into what you are today?
How they took pains to help you in growing up? On this teacher’s day, make them feel special and watch a beam appear across their faces.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cheap & Best Hangout Points for College Students]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/26/cheap-and-best-hangout-points-for-college-students/"/>
    <updated>2016-08-26T19:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/26/cheap-and-best-hangout-points-for-college-students</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17888542/0f3eca66-6949-11e6-8f18-06eaa8d79017.jpg" width="500" height="600">
Every college group has its own hangout point, which is special to them. In every college memory, each rind of gossip takes place in food joint or a café. While we converse about any big or small topic, the snacks and fast food are present as our companion. Their pep is not less than the college where the students study. To continue their vivacity, here we bring to you some of the cheapest and the best hangout points for college students in Delhi.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Rico’s</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17888539/0d9e1770-6949-11e6-97b2-0863ca823b02.jpg">
Great food accompanied with super fast service and what not? Perky interiors, amazing aura further add to the charisma of the place. Although the café is little expensive than other cafés, but the delicious food served here does full justice to whatever amount one spends here. The must try of this place is chicken stroganoff and the black forest waffle, which you could definitely not resist.</p>

<h1>Keventer’s</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17888714/e15930ae-6949-11e6-8dc5-314e44f37b70.jpg">
Well, milk shakes are our all time comrades. To cheer up your mood nothing can be better than a chilled glass of milk shake topped with your favorite ice cream. Keventer’s situated in Connaught Place is the favorite milk shake hub of the college students. Even though the infrastructure of this place is not too well organized but it still stands strong and serves the best in all the aspects.</p>

<h1>Amar Colony Market</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17888792/434abe2c-694a-11e6-998a-8e4bd76987b5.jpg">
Known for its aunty ke fries and Lebanese shawarma, amar colony market offers such scrumptious and pocket-friendly food items that you just can’t move away without trying at least one dish. This place offers a variety of eatables having something for anyone and everyone.</p>

<h1>Crazy Bruno</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17888814/5cf108f4-694a-11e6-8612-cf5506b2636e.jpg">
The momos lovers just can’t afford to miss this eatery located in Anand Lok Market, opposite Gargi college. They serve different varieties of momos including Malai Momos, Afghani Momos, Crispy Chilly Momos, Makhni Gravy Momos, Tandoori Momos, and not to miss Spicy Cheese Momos. Other than a complete assortment of momos, the menu also includes sandwiches, noodles, authentic Muglai food, as well as salads.</p>

<h1>QD’s</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17888826/77b48cba-694a-11e6-82ab-ddca9634cce2.jpg">
Perhaps the first place in Delhi to have given momos a tandoori flavor and twist, QD’s serves lip smacking chicken as well as vegetarian momos. One can relish their delicious taste at its outlets in North Campus and Satyaniketan.</p>

<h1>Dilli Haat</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17888873/c1dca106-694a-11e6-98c3-cedb8cf92f7f.jpg">
A place that offers unique flavors of India, Dilli Haat has various food stalls offering delicacies to taste. At the same time, you can shop exciting things from different state stalls. Being one of the most lively places of Delhi, this place is the center to many events and performances that can be a good past time.</p>

<h1>India Gate</h1>

<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17888984/7c4a4926-694b-11e6-9e4e-9d2e627eba83.jpg" width="500" height="200">
While talking of the hangout destinations in Delhi, how can anyone forget about the famous India Gate. The alluring atmosphere and strolling the art galleries and museums around feels amazing. The place offers an amazing fusion of patriotic and romantic feelings. The cheap street food around is worth giving a try. All in all, this place deserves a hangout while in Delhi.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best & Budget-free Pubs and Night-out Restaurants in Delhi]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/26/best-and-budget-free-pubs-and-night-out-restaurants-near-north-campus-and-south-campus/"/>
    <updated>2016-08-26T19:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/26/best-and-budget-free-pubs-and-night-out-restaurants-near-north-campus-and-south-campus</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18011846/78bc2424-6bd4-11e6-81ce-d64c0a77f0b9.jpg" width="500" height="600">
Going out for night outs and partying is such a cool thing to do in the coolest city of Delhi. This is the reason why most of the youngsters love coming to this city for their higher education. Yet another thing that just can’t be ignored is the very little money in the pocket during the college time. At one point, you might feel as if you are in complete recession. But not to worry! For the collegians, there are many cool places where boozing and partying can totally be pocket friendly. Here is a list of some of the best as well as the budget free pubs and night out restaurants near North Campus and South Campus in Delhi.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>My Bar Lounge and Restaurant</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18011845/78b5bf08-6bd4-11e6-80f5-0fe5203a15fb.jpg">
Located in Connaught Place, My Bar is filled with so many college students that it can be called as their second home. The reason why this place never falls short of customers is the fact that it is actually reasonable and the collegians can easily have the best time boozing here by spending little amount of money.</p>

<h1>Sam’s Café</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18012087/94c1b444-6bd5-11e6-9cd4-414c3314b07e.jpg">
This place sits in the main bazaar of Paharganj and probably the best place to chill and relax. Accompanied by voyagers as well as foreign nationals, this is a cool place, where after having your drinks and stuff, you can go up to the rooftop and relish the alluring view of Daryaganj.</p>

<h1>Pocket Bar</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18012167/f4ff609a-6bd5-11e6-8118-93d176b92422.jpg" width="700" height="450">
A part of the Vasant Square Mall, Vasant Kunj, Pocket Bar sounds so much like friendly to your pocket. The dark red hue of the place gives it a classy retro look, the ones that could be seen in old movies. This place offers ‘happy hours’ that go up to 12 hours. This happy hour can fetch you amazing deals on your drinks and snacks, letting you have the time of your life.</p>

<h1>Big Banana</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18011847/78bdb532-6bd4-11e6-9fc8-627d35685f45.jpg">
The moment we think of night clubs in Delhi, how can Saket not click our minds? Big Banana is an amazing place if you want to visit a lounge that has a spacious bar and is tranquil, at the same time.</p>

<h1>Skooter</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18012877/0595c2b6-6bd9-11e6-858e-0044cb6d871b.jpg">
A nightclub inside Hotel Samrat, New Delhi, this place is popular for Delhi’s premiere crowd. Themed with black and pink décor, Skooter has two floors. The ground floor is for normal entry whereas the first floor is meant for VIPs.</p>

<h1>Garage Inc.</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18012752/7bdd7a0a-6bd8-11e6-97b1-629fd25a5c42.jpg" width="700" height="450">
A budget-philic, all day breakfast menu that is 24x7 ‘happy hours’ can be found nowhere but in Hauz Khas Village. Smoking and chilling at the Garage Inc. can be less costly as compared to other pubs in Hauz Khas Village. The indoor, outdoor, as well as the balcony seats promise to provide you amazing boozing experience.</p>

<h1>Urban Hub</h1>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18012471/38bf9e84-6bd7-11e6-9925-ae5dc3e4e0aa.jpg" width="700" height="450">
Trending in North Campus, Urban Hub is filled with college students. It is a fancy place that offers drinks and snacks at affordable rates. They provide flavored hookah as well.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ragged Jeans Trend to Follow, This Fall!]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/19/the-ragged-jeans-trend-to-follow-this-fall/"/>
    <updated>2016-08-19T09:45:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/19/the-ragged-jeans-trend-to-follow-this-fall</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798197/d92b4bb6-65ec-11e6-9268-e8c738640615.jpg" width="500" height="400" title="High neck blouse" >
Distressed denim has never truly left style and tore pants are the simplest approach to accomplish the look. Infusing a component of road wear edge into your easygoing day wear has never been simpler. The tore jean is likely more flexible than you might suspect.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Tore pants are a definitive gesture to summer and with first look at hotter climate to come, now is the ideal time to consider redesigning your closet. Whether you decide on the inconspicuous choice of essentially distressing your denim or totally drench yourself in the pattern and tear and torque your pants into something taking after bothered shorts, it is a promise that can make the tore jean work for you.</p>

<ol>
<li><p>All alone, tore pants and a straightforward sweater are super easygoing. Be that as it may, include a statement neckband and heels. You will hence have a marvelous outfit.
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798198/d92fe8d8-65ec-11e6-87f3-a01d7455a81c.jpg"></p></li>
<li><p>Front-tuck an old-fashioned shirt into thin pulverized pants and put on booties – moment chic outfit.</p></li>
<li><p>You can simply keep things super easygoing with a cardigan, and tennis shoes. The way to make this look less bumpy is to wear perfectly sized pants and include some charming frill.
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798199/d934f788-65ec-11e6-80c9-4c48a3e771fd.jpg"></p></li>
<li><p>Wear high-waist torn denim with a sparkly crop top for some genuine marvelousness.</p></li>
<li><p>In hotter climate, include level shoes and a flowy kimono top for the easygoing look.</p></li>
<li><p>Include glitz top and beautiful heels for a basic watch that still emerges and makes you the center of attraction.
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798201/d93d81dc-65ec-11e6-8b81-e21668c88b4a.jpg"></p></li>
<li><p>Pair your torn pants with oxford shoes for an adorable outfit.</p></li>
<li><p>Tuck in front, a designed sweater into your torn denim and include heels for the ideal spring outfit.
<img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798200/d936d454-65ec-11e6-99c9-193ec6f9a221.jpg"></p></li>
<li><p>Some way or another, you must learn to style those much loved shoes, tore pants, and a sweatshirt to look ludicrously cool.</p></li>
</ol>


<p>In the event that you were still in any uncertainty regarding how flexible the tore pants drift truly is, look to any semblance of these road style trends and styling options. They demonstrate to us that ripped pants are easy to pull off and work with a scope of styles. Whether you&rsquo;re deciding on a keen look and dress your tore pants up with a jacket, dress down for a more easygoing look with a plain bit of knitwear. You can also tear your pants directly down into shorts for an even comfortable and a never ending trendy style, the conceivable outcomes are inestimable.</p>

<p>In this manner, on that note, in case you&rsquo;re in any uncertainty that the tore jean is a short lived pattern, you&rsquo;d not be right. Distressed denim has been around for some time and it&rsquo;s not going anyplace in a rush. It&rsquo;s a look that&rsquo;ll take you through each season from spring into summer and once more into winter. Prepare your tweezers and have scrounged in your tool kit for some great quality sandpaper. Torn pants are enormous for Spring/Summer and on the off chance that you don&rsquo;t take after this recommendation, then let it  be an all alone head.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Denim Brigade that You Cannot Miss, This Fall!]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/19/denim-brigade-that-you-cannot-miss-this-fall/"/>
    <updated>2016-08-19T09:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/08/19/denim-brigade-that-you-cannot-miss-this-fall</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798143/745a2a54-65ec-11e6-90c2-0acac849f0e1.jpg" width="500" height="400" title="High neck blouse" >
Denim is a kind of cotton material known for its utilization in pants and other garments. It utilizes a solid twill weave with a trademark corner to corner ribbing. Initially utilized for laborers' garments, denim is presently pervasive and has even entered the universe of high form. About everybody has no less than one article of clothing made of this fabric in the storage room nowadays.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Style today is deficient without denim. Denim comes in all structures, looks and washes to coordinate with each dress. It is hard to trust that the same denim was initially utilized in dress for the jeans and overalls worn by mineworkers on the west coast (US).</p>

<h2>1.  Dry Denim</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798142/744c4498-65ec-11e6-92c4-ee368d33df10.jpg">
Dry or crude denim, rather than washed denim, is a denim fabric that is not washed in the wake of being colored amid its creation. Most denim is washed subsequent to being made into a piece of attire. It is done so keeping in mind the end goal to make it milder and to wipe out any shrinkage which could bring about a thing to not fit after the proprietor washes it. Notwithstanding being washed, non-dry denim is some of the time falsely distressed to accomplish a well-used in look.</p>

<h2>2.  Selvage Denim</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798143/745a2a54-65ec-11e6-90c2-0acac849f0e1.jpg">
Selvage denim is a sort of denim which frames a spotless normal edge that does not unwind. It is ordinarily introduced in the unwashed or crude state. Normally, the selvage edges will be situated along the out crease of the jeans, making it unmistakable when sleeves are worn. Despite the fact that selvage denim is not totally synonymous with unwashed denim, the nearness of selvage commonly suggests that the denim utilized is of a higher quality.</p>

<h2>3.  Stretch Denim</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798146/7460792c-65ec-11e6-879d-08611058cb2f.jpg">
It is more often around 98% cotton and 2% Spandex for a touch of that easy-going stretch that we as a whole love. This mix gives you awesome simplicity and in the meantime some backing for those inconvenient spots you aren&rsquo;t so partial to like around the hips or thighs. Stretch denim pants are one of the quickest developing sections of the ladies' business sector for pants makers.</p>

<h2>4.  Poly Denim</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798145/746041f0-65ec-11e6-9136-e3a3d652c623.jpg">
These mixes engage the individuals who like the look of denim yet favor polyester mixes that wash and dry rapidly and are lighter in weight and somewhat dressier. These for the most part speak to a somewhat more established business sector, but on the other hand are discovering support as pant suits when the look is intended to be dressy yet easygoing.</p>

<h2>5.  Ramie Cotton Denim</h2>

<p><img class="center" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17798144/745e09c6-65ec-11e6-8d06-cb290d9bf091.jpg">
Ramie cotton denims are found in an assortment of mixes, with a wide value fluctuation. Ramie is a plant fiber more often than not included in light of the fact that it decreases wrinkling and adds a smooth radiance to the fabric. It isn&rsquo;t as solid as cotton and this is the main reason that it must be mixed with this more grounded material so as to stand up as a denim material.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
