<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[JunkJam | Fashion! LifeStyle! Market! Travel!]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2018-09-16T14:03:27+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Places to Have Tandoori Chai in Delhi]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/16/the-best-places-to-have-tandoori-chai-in-delhi/"/>
    <updated>2018-09-16T13:59:17+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/16/the-best-places-to-have-tandoori-chai-in-delhi</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594461-abaa8400-b9b8-11e8-8868-56f57f37c6cd.jpg" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594461-abaa8400-b9b8-11e8-8868-56f57f37c6cd.jpg" width="400" height="500" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594461-abaa8400-b9b8-11e8-8868-56f57f37c6cd.jpg"></noscript>
In the event that you haven&rsquo;t heard about Tandoori Chai, you are most probably living under a rock! This searing hot tea has been breaking the internet ever since it came into existence.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>What is tandoori chai?</h2>

<p>What else do you need when you can have a sizzling cup of tandoori chai for breakfast? Probably some parantha or bun maska to go along with it. There are a few tandoori chai joint in Delhi and their tandoori flavored Chai is to die for.</p>

<h2>How Is It Prepared?</h2>

<p>There’s a one of a kind procedure in making the tea with the assistance of a tandoor. The clay pots are put in a pre-heated tandoor.  Once it is nearly cooked, this tea is filled into very hot kulhads or clay pots to complete the process of cooking, making the kulhad give the chai a smoky flavor. After that this hot tandori chai is served to the customers in clean kulhads.</p>

<h3>Alpha&rsquo;s tandoori chai</h3>

<h4>Address:</h4>

<p>Shop no. 6, Commercial complex, near Batra cinema, Mukherjee Nagar, New Delhi</p>

<p>Have you heard a lot about tandoori chai on social media and finally want to have some hot tandoor tea? Then you must visit Alpha&rsquo;s tandoori chai. The price is affordable and they serve tea in kulhad. Start your morning with a tasty tea.</p>

<h3>Mucchad Di Chai</h3>

<h4>Address:</h4>

<p>H.No. 128 Saidullajaib, Saiyad Ul Ajaib Village, Sainik Farm, New Delhi</p>

<p>This hidden gem in Saket is just about 5 minutes walk from Saket metro station and close to garden of five senses. They serve amazing tandoori chai with sandwiches and parathas at an extremely affordable price. This small sweet outlet is the best place for hanging out with your buddies. Certainly one of the must-visit places for tea lovers.</p>

<h3>Tandoori Chai</h3>

<h4>Address:</h4>

<p>Gali no 43 madarse wali gali near jafrabad metro station, Jafrabad, Delhi</p>

<p>This little shop situated in the madarse wali gali serves amazing kulhads of tandoori chai that you will love. This place is just perfect for all the chai lovers. So, if you are one of them, you must make a trip to this amazing place.</p>

<h3>Mister Chai</h3>

<h4>Address:</h4>

<p>19 Ashoka Road, Connaught Place, Shangri-La&rsquo;s - Eros Hotel, New Delhi</p>

<p>Situated in the heart of Shangri-La&rsquo;s - Eros Hotel, Mister Chai offers amazing tandoori chai in a lavish setting. It has the components of an Indian tea shop presented in a modern feel. Serving awesome tandoori chai at a reasonable value, Mister Chai is the perfect place for hangouts with your family and friends. The details of the interior offer the perfect vibe for visitors to unwind and enjoy the treats on offer. Mr. Chai serves 24x7. So, the next time you are in the mood for some tandoori chai, you know where to go.</p>

<p>These are some of the best places in Delhi to have tandoori chai. Start your mornings with a perfect combination of parantha, sandwich, cookies, or bun maska and tandoori chai at these places in Delhi.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 on Budget International Holiday Destinations for 2018]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/16/10-on-budget-international-holiday-destinations-for-2018/"/>
    <updated>2018-09-16T13:52:17+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/16/10-on-budget-international-holiday-destinations-for-2018</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594404-c29ca680-b9b7-11e8-9d6f-cc025e41b2ce.jpg" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594404-c29ca680-b9b7-11e8-9d6f-cc025e41b2ce.jpg" width="400" height="500" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594404-c29ca680-b9b7-11e8-9d6f-cc025e41b2ce.jpg"></noscript>
There are numerous great spots to visit all around the globe, ranging from the beaches to the old and captivating destinations. For those searching for incredible 2018 budget holiday destinations, there is plenty to choose from. Here are some of the most affordable destinations to visit this year:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>1.  Thailand</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594407-c3cdd380-b9b7-11e8-9586-8bbde49f1d8e.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594407-c3cdd380-b9b7-11e8-9586-8bbde49f1d8e.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594407-c3cdd380-b9b7-11e8-9586-8bbde49f1d8e.jpg"></noscript>
Some want the calmness in the midst of tropical beaches and jungles, while others look for the zeal of large, bustling cities. However, there are numerous people who wish to visit a place that offers a tad bit of everything on their vacation and to do everything on a budget. Thailand is a perfect budget travel destination, regardless of what kind of holiday you&rsquo;re after.</p>

<h4>2.  Nepal</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594403-c2041000-b9b7-11e8-8e13-bcf530d80988.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594403-c2041000-b9b7-11e8-8e13-bcf530d80988.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594403-c2041000-b9b7-11e8-8e13-bcf530d80988.jpg"></noscript>
Situated in the midst of the gripping Himalayas, Nepal is a beautiful nation of rivers and snow peaks, yaks and yetis, and monasteries. Nepal offers the quiet and peaceful environment for any individual who needs to take a break from the hustle and bustle of the city life.</p>

<h4>3.  Vietnam</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594408-c4666a00-b9b7-11e8-810b-3919660c38b2.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594408-c4666a00-b9b7-11e8-810b-3919660c38b2.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594408-c4666a00-b9b7-11e8-810b-3919660c38b2.jpg"></noscript>
Vietnam, a nation with plenty of natural magnificence, rich history, and extraordinary heritage is absolutely heaven. The must visit place for explorers all around the globe, this is a standout amongst the most affordable tourist destinations.</p>

<h4>4.  Bhutan</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594400-c03a4c80-b9b7-11e8-8a1d-868a397cfbcc.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594400-c03a4c80-b9b7-11e8-8a1d-868a397cfbcc.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594400-c03a4c80-b9b7-11e8-8a1d-868a397cfbcc.jpg"></noscript>
The Happiest Country on the planet, Bhutan is the best place to be for some peace, quietness. Known for its natural beauty and the immense scope of unexplored landscapes, Indians can even visit this country without a passport!</p>

<h4>5.  Sri Lanka</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594406-c3353d00-b9b7-11e8-9c87-306839745d9a.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594406-c3353d00-b9b7-11e8-9c87-306839745d9a.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594406-c3353d00-b9b7-11e8-9c87-306839745d9a.jpg"></noscript>
One of our neighboring nations, it offers an extensive variety of budget-friendly choices for everyone. Known for the stunning shorelines, utterly lip-smacking food, and the Ramayana connection – this nation has something to offer for everyone.</p>

<h4>6.  Laos</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594401-c0d2e300-b9b7-11e8-86bf-b5f8592b0073.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594401-c0d2e300-b9b7-11e8-86bf-b5f8592b0073.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594401-c0d2e300-b9b7-11e8-86bf-b5f8592b0073.jpg"></noscript>
This Southeast Asian nation known for its Buddhist monasteries, mountainous terrain, and the wonderful French architecture can be your next travel destination.</p>

<h4>7.  Singapore</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594405-c29ca680-b9b7-11e8-8f61-633954c63450.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594405-c29ca680-b9b7-11e8-8f61-633954c63450.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594405-c29ca680-b9b7-11e8-8f61-633954c63450.jpg"></noscript>
Gone are the days when Singapore was just a mere stopover – it is currently a go-to destination for everybody who is on a budget. It is such a diverse country, to the point that you can go here and enjoy regardless of whether you have a tight budget.</p>

<h4>8.  Malaysia</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594402-c16b7980-b9b7-11e8-82b0-1a0df43f330a.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594402-c16b7980-b9b7-11e8-82b0-1a0df43f330a.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594402-c16b7980-b9b7-11e8-82b0-1a0df43f330a.jpg"></noscript>
A standout amongst the most admired tourist destinations for Indians particularly for its affordable options, Malaysia has a lot to offer. From flawless beaches to the wonderful cities – you are never going to get bored here.</p>

<h4>9.  Indonesia</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594399-c03a4c80-b9b7-11e8-8e2f-d3ba47c4bf43.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594399-c03a4c80-b9b7-11e8-8e2f-d3ba47c4bf43.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594399-c03a4c80-b9b7-11e8-8e2f-d3ba47c4bf43.jpg"></noscript>
One of the biggest archipelago countries on the planet, Indonesia is the must-visit destination for Indians as it is one of the least expensive nations to visit from India.</p>

<h4>10. Seychelles</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594404-c29ca680-b9b7-11e8-9d6f-cc025e41b2ce.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594404-c29ca680-b9b7-11e8-9d6f-cc025e41b2ce.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594404-c29ca680-b9b7-11e8-9d6f-cc025e41b2ce.jpg"></noscript>
Seychelles is an archipelago of 115 islands in the Indian Ocean, off East Africa. Highly praised for the delightful shorelines, natural beauty, and coral reef, it is a must-visit for any individual who wishes to visit the least expensive countries.</p>

<p>These are only ten of the best and most affordable places to visit this year. There is something in each corner of the globe to you fulfill your fancy and furthermore be an extremely affordable trip as well.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Must Watch Indian Web Series if You Are a Travel Lover]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/16/7-must-watch-indian-web-series-if-you-are-a-travel-lover/"/>
    <updated>2018-09-16T13:46:48+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/16/7-must-watch-indian-web-series-if-you-are-a-travel-lover</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594353-ea3f3f00-b9b6-11e8-8c79-36840db5c255.jpg" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594353-ea3f3f00-b9b6-11e8-8c79-36840db5c255.jpg" width="400" height="500" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594353-ea3f3f00-b9b6-11e8-8c79-36840db5c255.jpg"></noscript>
Can&rsquo;t swing a major get-away this year? Grounded travelers have an assortment of phenomenal travel-related series to choose from, because of some essential films. Have you ever watched a film that truly moved you, as in got you down to book tickets to the fascinating destination? Here is a couple of Indian web series on Travel that is really popular.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h3>Tripling</h3>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594355-ead7d580-b9b6-11e8-8fe3-e9e1fea64c45.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594355-ead7d580-b9b6-11e8-8fe3-e9e1fea64c45.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594355-ead7d580-b9b6-11e8-8fe3-e9e1fea64c45.jpg"></noscript>
This story is about three siblings, who go on a trip of a lifetime! They set out on a road trip and bond over in the course of their adventure and have the time of their lives. Trust me, you won&rsquo;t have the desire to stop until you complete the whole season.</p>

<h3>Way Back Home</h3>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594357-ec090280-b9b6-11e8-959d-5f4c46b6e459.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594357-ec090280-b9b6-11e8-959d-5f4c46b6e459.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594357-ec090280-b9b6-11e8-959d-5f4c46b6e459.jpg"></noscript>
Traveler Rohan Thakur explores the most stunning spots in Himachal Pradesh in this a delightful first-of-its-kind sound/visual Himalayan travelogue. Rohan has featured some of the best hidden gems of the Himalaya that people generally miss out on. This is a must-watch this series and you will thank us!</p>

<h3>Away from Home</h3>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594351-e90e1200-b9b6-11e8-86c6-323905a10a63.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594351-e90e1200-b9b6-11e8-86c6-323905a10a63.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594351-e90e1200-b9b6-11e8-86c6-323905a10a63.jpg"></noscript>
This series contains eight episodes and will give you a great idea about the life in the Andaman and Nicobar Islands. The series has the potential to motivate you so much that you may end up packing your bags and setting out to this beautiful beach destination.</p>

<h3>Under The Rupee</h3>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594356-eb706c00-b9b6-11e8-87f1-1d6d09c5f72d.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594356-eb706c00-b9b6-11e8-87f1-1d6d09c5f72d.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594356-eb706c00-b9b6-11e8-87f1-1d6d09c5f72d.jpg"></noscript>
Under the Rupee will smash all the clichés, which make people believe that making a trip to Europe requires a lot of money. This series also stars Rohan Thakur and you&rsquo;ll see Thakur finding the ancient yet astounding parts of Europe. You will learn how to spend smartly without wasting a huge amount of money while setting out to any European destination. A must-watch series without a doubt!</p>

<h3>The Trip</h3>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594354-ead7d580-b9b6-11e8-86c2-2de76e1a6fdc.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594354-ead7d580-b9b6-11e8-86c2-2de76e1a6fdc.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594354-ead7d580-b9b6-11e8-86c2-2de76e1a6fdc.jpg"></noscript>
Featuring diva Lisa Haydon and comedian Mallika Dua alongside two other ladies, this web series is an all-girls trip from India to Thailand. It&rsquo;s a refreshing series that attempts to show the best of Thailand. You truly need to watch it!</p>

<h3>GottadoIndia</h3>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594352-e9a6a880-b9b6-11e8-8faf-e2fcb90d70ad.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594352-e9a6a880-b9b6-11e8-8faf-e2fcb90d70ad.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594352-e9a6a880-b9b6-11e8-8faf-e2fcb90d70ad.jpg"></noscript>
GottadoIndia is a youtube channel by Scherezade Shroff, who explores the delightful spots in India. She captures her journey and food excursions for you to enjoy back at home. This dynamic youtuber will surely influence you to get up from your couch and fulfill your bucket list!</p>

<h3>Mumbiker Nikhil</h3>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594353-ea3f3f00-b9b6-11e8-8c79-36840db5c255.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594353-ea3f3f00-b9b6-11e8-8c79-36840db5c255.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594353-ea3f3f00-b9b6-11e8-8c79-36840db5c255.jpg"></noscript>
Travel buffs out there will love this one! This isn&rsquo;t a series but instead a YouTube channel by a biker and one of the Indian Vloggers Nikhil, who goes to a different destination on his treasured bike.</p>

<p>A lot of us watch many travel series just to realize that we do this unintentionally because we are enthusiastically in love with travel experiences.</p>

<p>When you watch a series, you are driven into embarking to some unknown place looking for experience and thrills. You can enjoy a series by sitting back and watching it with a companion or alone. Sip a glass of beverage, get a bowl of popcorn and be transported to a refreshing new world for a couple of hours!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethnic Fashion Trends for Navratri and Where to Shop Them]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/16/ethnic-fashion-trends-for-navratri-and-where-to-shop-them/"/>
    <updated>2018-09-16T13:38:06+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/16/ethnic-fashion-trends-for-navratri-and-where-to-shop-them</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594290-e3fc9300-b9b5-11e8-9251-1c6747e7d9d2.JPG" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594290-e3fc9300-b9b5-11e8-9251-1c6747e7d9d2.JPG" width="400" height="500" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594290-e3fc9300-b9b5-11e8-9251-1c6747e7d9d2.JPG"></noscript>
Among all the various celebrations that exist everywhere throughout the nation, Navratri far surpasses the rest as far as sheer spectacle and speculate. The 9-day celebration is one of the greatest in the nation alongside Dussera and Diwali. On the event of Navratri, a considerable measure of you will want to dress your best, have a good time and participating in all the different dances that occur, for example, the garba and dandiya. However, for those of you who have no clue how to dress up during Navratri, you need to keep reading thoroughly below, where we&rsquo;ve compiled the best Ethnic Fashion Trends for Navratri and also given you tips on the best way to look your finest in every department of your Navratri style.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>1.  Long kurtas with palazzo suits for Navratri</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594289-e3fc9300-b9b5-11e8-92f7-2a34b8a0afe3.JPG" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594289-e3fc9300-b9b5-11e8-92f7-2a34b8a0afe3.JPG" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594289-e3fc9300-b9b5-11e8-92f7-2a34b8a0afe3.JPG"></noscript>
Even though traditional outfits are usually favored for Navratri, you can simply try something new and go the in a trendy way by matching voguish outfits that go well together. One such mix that truly functions admirably is the pairing of long kurtas with palazzo suits which will truly enable you in breaking out each one of those elegant dance moves you have in store for the dance floor. Since Navratri is a sensory overload of colors, a interesting method to spice things up is to pick colorful dupattas.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594288-e363fc80-b9b5-11e8-955b-d0cfe3b8e9bc.JPG" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594288-e363fc80-b9b5-11e8-955b-d0cfe3b8e9bc.JPG" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594288-e363fc80-b9b5-11e8-955b-d0cfe3b8e9bc.JPG"></noscript></p>

<h4>2.  Anarkalis for Navratri</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594285-e232cf80-b9b5-11e8-8100-b544f8bbd8ae.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594285-e232cf80-b9b5-11e8-8100-b544f8bbd8ae.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594285-e232cf80-b9b5-11e8-8100-b544f8bbd8ae.jpg"></noscript>
There are no two different opinions about Anarkalis being truly excellent. The silhouette and styling of this ethnic outfit are very complementing for most body types and renders a fantastic and magnificent appeal. Despite the fact that it&rsquo;s basically traditional in style, Anarkali Suits still keep on being amazing in current times. That is primarily one of the principle reasons why Anarkali Suits are most favored for special and traditional occasions, for example, Navratri celebrations.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594284-e232cf80-b9b5-11e8-9dc1-ff18582d593c.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594284-e232cf80-b9b5-11e8-9dc1-ff18582d593c.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594284-e232cf80-b9b5-11e8-9dc1-ff18582d593c.jpg"></noscript></p>

<h4>3.  Festive Lehenga Choli</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594287-e2cb6600-b9b5-11e8-81a0-456a60119452.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594287-e2cb6600-b9b5-11e8-81a0-456a60119452.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594287-e2cb6600-b9b5-11e8-81a0-456a60119452.jpg"></noscript>
Navratri is one such Indian celebration where individuals incline toward a traditional Indian outfit. Navratri is synonymous with Lehenga Choli, the reason being it is celebrated largely in Gujarat and Rajasthan where Lehenga Cholis are mostly worn by the ladies. Today, there&rsquo;s a plenty of Lehenga Choli Designs available in the market to suit your taste.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594286-e2cb6600-b9b5-11e8-9476-9c5538364354.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594286-e2cb6600-b9b5-11e8-9476-9c5538364354.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594286-e2cb6600-b9b5-11e8-9476-9c5538364354.jpg"></noscript></p>

<h4>4.  Silk Sarees for Navratri</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594291-e4952980-b9b5-11e8-8436-0ce0313b3240.JPG" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594291-e4952980-b9b5-11e8-8436-0ce0313b3240.JPG" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594291-e4952980-b9b5-11e8-8436-0ce0313b3240.JPG"></noscript>
Amid celebrations like Navratri, individuals favor only ethnic traditional Indian outfits. Silk Sarees, maybe, best speak to ethnic Indian Fashion. In this manner, Silk Sarees with their unmatched brilliance are a perfect Indian outfit for Navratri. India has an extensive assortment of Silk Sarees to offer, for example, Kanjeevaram Silk Sarees, Mysore Silk saree, Benarasi Silk Zareez, Poochampalli Silk Sareez, Sambalpuri Silk Zarees, and so forth.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594290-e3fc9300-b9b5-11e8-9251-1c6747e7d9d2.JPG" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594290-e3fc9300-b9b5-11e8-9251-1c6747e7d9d2.JPG" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594290-e3fc9300-b9b5-11e8-9251-1c6747e7d9d2.JPG"></noscript></p>

<p>Buying wonderful Navratri Fashion Online</p>

<p>In the event that you have decided to purchase Navratri outfits, then the best game-plan for you would be to online shop from a reputed online ethnic fashion site which is notable for having the best collection of Navratri dresses online that incorporate an assortment of Indian ethnic styles, all available at amazingly reasonable costs with huge rebates, deals and offers as well.</p>

<h4>Best Websites to Shop Navratri Outfits Online</h4>

<ul>
<li>Jabong.com</li>
<li>Ajio.com</li>
<li>Myntra.com</li>
<li>Craftsvilla.com</li>
<li>Lifestylestores.com</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beautiful Rangoli Designs for Diwali]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/16/beautiful-rangoli-designs-for-diwali/"/>
    <updated>2018-09-16T13:28:10+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/16/beautiful-rangoli-designs-for-diwali</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594220-9d5a6900-b9b4-11e8-90af-a2fc345d338c.jpg" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594220-9d5a6900-b9b4-11e8-90af-a2fc345d338c.jpg" width="400" height="500" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594220-9d5a6900-b9b4-11e8-90af-a2fc345d338c.jpg"></noscript>
One of the most popular folk art, practiced in majority of Indian households, Rangoli is a celebration with colours. Almost every part of India, includes the practice of rangoli in their celebration of prominent festivals, round the year. But it is in Diwali, where the art gets a maximum exposure since it is almost a ritual to decorate the house with Rangoli in this festival.  People try to fetch unique yet new rangoli designs to decorate their rooms and gateways and make the festival more colourful.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Rangoli Designs for Diwali</h2>

<p>Diwali is a festival of Goddess Laxmi, who embodies prosperity and wealth and that is why every decoration, including beautiful rangoli designs manifest on use of bright colours, portrayal of diyas, swastika, lotus and swirling patterns that highlight the festive sense and the spirit of the occasion.</p>

<p>Spreading all these emotions this form of art is attractive but not always easy to execute. Specially the complex and integral rangoli designs often need expertise to implement. That is why here are some trendy and easy motifs that are simple to do yet beautiful to look.</p>

<h3>Mehndi Designs for Karva Chauth</h3>

<h4>Carpet style rangoli design for Diwali:</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594217-9c293c00-b9b4-11e8-9aca-548086c2d167.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594217-9c293c00-b9b4-11e8-9aca-548086c2d167.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594217-9c293c00-b9b4-11e8-9aca-548086c2d167.jpg"></noscript>
When it comes to designing in the hallway or in a larger area the best option is the carpet style Rangoli. With specific lined borders the designing can be done with fewer curvatures and more of line patterns. Use of multi colours makes it look bright and vibrant.</p>

<h4>Semi Circular Shaped Rangoli design for Diwali:</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594219-9d5a6900-b9b4-11e8-94dc-bdbaa294b587.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594219-9d5a6900-b9b4-11e8-94dc-bdbaa294b587.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594219-9d5a6900-b9b4-11e8-94dc-bdbaa294b587.jpg"></noscript>
Best placed in the entrance of the house, this kind of Rangoli designs are popular for its ease of design. Highlighted with bright colours and simple shapes, the design gets more beautiful with diyas placed around.</p>

<h4>Round shaped easy rangoli design for Diwali:</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594218-9cc1d280-b9b4-11e8-843e-ee2a41c34176.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594218-9cc1d280-b9b4-11e8-843e-ee2a41c34176.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594218-9cc1d280-b9b4-11e8-843e-ee2a41c34176.jpg"></noscript>
Traditional round shape and use of colourful florals designs with white highlighters can create quite a sophisticated look in rangoli designs. The round shaped designs are popular for ages and have successfully kept their charm till today. Decorating the centre of the puja room or the gateway with these designs can be an excellent idea.</p>

<h3>Easy Rangoli Designs for Diwali</h3>

<h4>Bangle shaped easy Rangoli design for Diwali:</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594216-9c293c00-b9b4-11e8-81de-a7de2be3a4e5.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594216-9c293c00-b9b4-11e8-81de-a7de2be3a4e5.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594216-9c293c00-b9b4-11e8-81de-a7de2be3a4e5.jpg"></noscript>
Forming a design with bangle shapes are easy and quite attractive too. The complexity of the designs is minimal thus refraining from the risk of being messy this is an excellent style for the beginners. Use of ear buds, combs and even flowers are also popular ways of filling the designs and creating a elaborate form.</p>

<h4>Swastika Rangoli:</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594220-9d5a6900-b9b4-11e8-90af-a2fc345d338c.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594220-9d5a6900-b9b4-11e8-90af-a2fc345d338c.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594220-9d5a6900-b9b4-11e8-90af-a2fc345d338c.jpg"></noscript>
Being an auspicious sign, Swastika designs are often used in Rangoli and in the most creative ways possible. Being an easy shape it can be easily drawn and designed in definite patterns or even in the midst of elaborate designs as a highlighter.</p>

<p>Designing a Rangoli is nothing but expressing the free spirit of mind and the celebration mood of the occasion. Since there is no fixed rule so creativity can take its toll and speak out the best way it can.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the Maldives Good for a Honeymoon?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/16/is-the-maldives-good-for-a-honeymoon/"/>
    <updated>2018-09-16T13:19:50+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/16/is-the-maldives-good-for-a-honeymoon</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594110-bfeb8280-b9b2-11e8-9a0e-2004acfbe7d3.jpg" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594110-bfeb8280-b9b2-11e8-9a0e-2004acfbe7d3.jpg" width="400" height="500" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594110-bfeb8280-b9b2-11e8-9a0e-2004acfbe7d3.jpg"></noscript>
Are you longing for a tropical honeymoon? Then, the Maldives is a great place to unwind and appreciate nature’s beauty. These islands are particularly incredible for individuals who wish to unwind on white sandy shorelines and not be barraged by crowds. Here are 6 extraordinary reasons to pick the Maldives as your honeymoon destination:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>1. The incredible Weather Year-Round</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594114-c24ddc80-b9b2-11e8-8f5f-8a2f1e3c7c34.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594114-c24ddc80-b9b2-11e8-8f5f-8a2f1e3c7c34.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594114-c24ddc80-b9b2-11e8-8f5f-8a2f1e3c7c34.jpg"></noscript>
In the event that your wedding isn&rsquo;t occurring during the summer months, you might be stressed over finding a place to go for a honeymoon where the weather conditions are good. The weather in the Maldives is just incredible regardless of the season you visit. Just make sure you pack a lot of sunscreens and you will be able to enjoy the sunshine every day.</p>

<h4>2. Seclusion</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594113-c1b54600-b9b2-11e8-97be-67fee0add05c.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594113-c1b54600-b9b2-11e8-97be-67fee0add05c.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594113-c1b54600-b9b2-11e8-97be-67fee0add05c.jpg"></noscript>
The Maldives is largely water, with over 1000 little islands. Most islands are uninhabited, and those with people just contain a couple of resorts on the whole island. This implies that there won’t be too many people. Some of the islands just have a couple of villas, which means that the whole island will probably have less than ten couples on it at one time. It&rsquo;s considerably more enjoyable to appreciate the shoreline when there are fewer people.</p>

<h4>3. Diving and Snorkeling</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594111-c0841900-b9b2-11e8-840b-02e4f2f49712.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594111-c0841900-b9b2-11e8-840b-02e4f2f49712.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594111-c0841900-b9b2-11e8-840b-02e4f2f49712.jpg"></noscript>
The Indian Ocean is a deep blue heaven that is home to a large group of plants and creatures. This makes it a phenomenal place for diving. The coral reefs are truly wonderful and you can explore those along with caves, caverns, and wrecks that are packed with marine creatures. A lot of people love the diving spots in the Maldives. Many resorts give complimentary boat rides to the patrons. Make sure to carry a camera that is waterproof to capture the unbelievable sights underwater.</p>

<h4>4. The Food</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594112-c11caf80-b9b2-11e8-8443-eb57c3b00e6d.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594112-c11caf80-b9b2-11e8-8443-eb57c3b00e6d.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594112-c11caf80-b9b2-11e8-8443-eb57c3b00e6d.jpg"></noscript>
You will get world-class cuisine at almost every restaurant in the Maldives. The traditional cuisine is a blend of Indian and Sri Lankan food but with a twist. Kulhi Boakibaa is an extraordinary dish; it is a cake made of tuna and coconut that is somewhat spicy and utterly fulfilling. Gourmet buffets are also available at the restaurants. Some of the resorts also have about 6 restaurants to select from. They also bar that offer exotic drinks.</p>

<h4>5. They are gradually disappearing</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594115-c2e67300-b9b2-11e8-8228-2500275892a5.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594115-c2e67300-b9b2-11e8-8228-2500275892a5.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594115-c2e67300-b9b2-11e8-8228-2500275892a5.jpg"></noscript>
Maldives has the lowest height on the planet. This means that these stunning islands won&rsquo;t be around until the end of time. As the ocean levels rise, the islands will probably get submerged. Try not to miss the beauty and isolation of this brilliant honeymoon destination.</p>

<h4>6. Best Resorts With Numerous Options</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594110-bfeb8280-b9b2-11e8-9a0e-2004acfbe7d3.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594110-bfeb8280-b9b2-11e8-9a0e-2004acfbe7d3.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45594110-bfeb8280-b9b2-11e8-9a0e-2004acfbe7d3.jpg"></noscript>
Maldives offers various hotel options for visitors. Honeymooners are ensured to have a lavish stay including all-water accommodation, best spas, access to lagoons, luxurious swimming pools, stunning corals, preserved marine life, underwater eateries and a lot more.</p>

<p>Regardless of whether you&rsquo;re searching for a place to unwind on the shoreline with a drink, or a place to go swimming without the big crowd, Maldives is certainly the ideal honeymoon spot!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Easy Yoga Asanas for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/08/7-easy-yoga-asanas-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2018-09-08T02:50:32+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/08/7-easy-yoga-asanas-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45244027-ab085280-b313-11e8-951e-943d499295d4.jpg" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45244027-ab085280-b313-11e8-951e-943d499295d4.jpg" width="400" height="500" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45244027-ab085280-b313-11e8-951e-943d499295d4.jpg"></noscript>
These days, yoga appears to be the most prominent type of weight reduction exercise, since individuals say that it is simple to practice and that there is no fuss in doing yoga. Yoga asanas for weight reduction are turning into the most loved subject among yoga experts and it will just be a matter of time before yoga for weight reduction is practiced everywhere throughout the nation!</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Below are 7 easy yoga asanas for weight loss</p>

<h4>1.  Plank</h4>

<p>Holding a plank might be amazing compared to other approaches to strengthen your core. It is easy to do but the results of plank would show in your abs really quickly. Draw the top of your head and your heels in opposite directions and move your chest forward between your arms.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45243491-b35f8e00-b311-11e8-8f63-7b9ca5818013.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45243491-b35f8e00-b311-11e8-8f63-7b9ca5818013.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45243491-b35f8e00-b311-11e8-8f63-7b9ca5818013.jpg"></noscript></p>

<h4>2.  Bow Pose</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45243487-b22e6100-b311-11e8-95d5-a15cd8e1ae76.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45243487-b22e6100-b311-11e8-95d5-a15cd8e1ae76.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45243487-b22e6100-b311-11e8-95d5-a15cd8e1ae76.jpg"></noscript>
It efficiently burns fat while toning your stomach region and additionally your arms and legs. Begin by lying down on your stomach. Gradually bend your knees and go back to hold your feet. Raise your abdominal area whilst extending your feet upward. Keep your shoulder blades relaxed.</p>

<h4>3.  Cobra Pose</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45243488-b2c6f780-b311-11e8-8bd9-589b8dad5ad2.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45243488-b2c6f780-b311-11e8-8bd9-589b8dad5ad2.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45243488-b2c6f780-b311-11e8-8bd9-589b8dad5ad2.jpg"></noscript>
This posture is one of the easiest yoga poses for weight reduction. Begin by lying face down with the highest points of your feet flat on the floor. Place your hands under your shoulders while squeezing your hips and legs down. Gradually lift your abdominal area and head far from the yoga mat. Hold your shoulders back and look upwards.</p>

<h4>4.  Warrior I Pose</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45243493-b35f8e00-b311-11e8-84c0-c41dfe5d0002.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45243493-b35f8e00-b311-11e8-84c0-c41dfe5d0002.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45243493-b35f8e00-b311-11e8-84c0-c41dfe5d0002.jpg"></noscript>
The Warrior I is a very important posture when you&rsquo;re doing yoga for weight reduction. It helps tone down the arm, stomach, and thigh muscles. Begin by standing straight with your feet around 4-5 steps apart. Gradually turn both your feet and chest towards the left. Keeping your right leg straight, gradually bend your left knee over your toes. At that point raise your arms over your head in prayer position before raising your head to look at your hands.</p>

<h4>5.  Wind-Releasing Pose</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45244215-7779f800-b314-11e8-8f90-30dc9c9af025.png" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45244215-7779f800-b314-11e8-8f90-30dc9c9af025.png" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45244215-7779f800-b314-11e8-8f90-30dc9c9af025.png"></noscript>
This simple yoga for weight reduction tones and strengthens your stomach region. Resting on the floor, gradually bring your knees to your chest while keeping your ankles together. Raise your head far from the yoga mat while clutching your arms over your knees.</p>

<h4>6.  Side Stretch Pose</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45243492-b35f8e00-b311-11e8-87b8-86b7c8bb1b45.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45243492-b35f8e00-b311-11e8-87b8-86b7c8bb1b45.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45243492-b35f8e00-b311-11e8-87b8-86b7c8bb1b45.jpg"></noscript>
Again one of the simplest yoga postures for weight reduction, the Side Stretch is efficient in burning calories and increasing your heartbeat. Begin by positioning your feet wide apart. Turn both your chest and feet to one side. Turn your abdominal area over your right leg until its parallel to the floor. Next, touch your hands to the ground.</p>

<h4>7.  Downward Dog</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45243490-b2c6f780-b311-11e8-9072-4d82e24e1449.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45243490-b2c6f780-b311-11e8-9072-4d82e24e1449.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45243490-b2c6f780-b311-11e8-9072-4d82e24e1449.jpg"></noscript>
Searching for a method to tone your full body? Then Downward Dog is your thing. To achieve the most muscle-toning benefits, turn your thigh muscles inward, and do the same with your upper arms.</p>

<p>Turning to yoga for weight reduction won&rsquo;t just enable you to get thin, however, will also enhance your balance and flexibility in the long term.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Easy Treks in India for a Beginner]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/22/7-easy-treks-in-india-for-a-beginner/"/>
    <updated>2018-08-22T20:26:42+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/22/7-easy-treks-in-india-for-a-beginner</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471354-572a1800-a649-11e8-9050-dd3d472aea8f.jpg" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471354-572a1800-a649-11e8-9050-dd3d472aea8f.jpg" width="400" height="500" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471354-572a1800-a649-11e8-9050-dd3d472aea8f.jpg"></noscript>
With the charisma of the grand Himalayas, trekking there is an experience for a lifetime. This is due to the fact that besides enjoying the scenic beauty of the Himalayas, you also experience a blend of joy, adventure, and self-realization. If you don’t indulge in adventure sports regularly, yet want to go on a trek, try one of these below-mentioned easy treks in India:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>1.  Sham Valley Trek</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471359-58f3db80-a649-11e8-83f0-6910201332ac.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471359-58f3db80-a649-11e8-83f0-6910201332ac.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471359-58f3db80-a649-11e8-83f0-6910201332ac.jpg"></noscript>
Sham Valley Trek is also called &ldquo;Baby Trek&rdquo; because of lower altitude. You can visit the Indus Valley, the ancient kingdom of Sham and Likir monastery. This trek is fairly easy since the highest elevation that one has to trek is 4500 meters. The best time for this trek is from June to October.</p>

<h4>2.  Chopta Chandrashila Trek</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471355-57c2ae80-a649-11e8-96df-6381893c8549.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471355-57c2ae80-a649-11e8-96df-6381893c8549.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471355-57c2ae80-a649-11e8-96df-6381893c8549.jpg"></noscript>
Chopta Chandrashila Trek a standout amongst the most astonishing treks of the Garhwal Himalayas. The best part is that you can go there any time of the year. You get the chance to see the wonderful sight of snow-capped Himalayas from the renowned Chandrashila point during this trek. The magnificent sight of the Himalayas is soothing for both the eyes and soul.</p>

<h4>3.  Dodital Trek</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471356-57c2ae80-a649-11e8-97ba-313daeb7a503.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471356-57c2ae80-a649-11e8-97ba-313daeb7a503.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471356-57c2ae80-a649-11e8-97ba-313daeb7a503.jpg"></noscript>
Dodital is a lake located at an altitude of about 10847 ft. This lake is encompassed by thick forests. The best time to go on this trek is between mid-March and October since this is the time when verdant green meadows of the area are at its bloom because of the retreating monsoons.</p>

<h4>4.  Dzongri Trek</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471357-585b4500-a649-11e8-8b26-2efa4ae1afbc.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471357-585b4500-a649-11e8-8b26-2efa4ae1afbc.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471357-585b4500-a649-11e8-8b26-2efa4ae1afbc.jpg"></noscript>
Situated at an elevation of 4020 meters, Dzongri is another trek that you can easily take. The Dzongri track goes through moss-laden woods of birch, oak, rhododendron, maple, and bamboo. You can go on this trek from March to early June and September to mid of November.</p>

<h4>5.  Valley of flowers Trek</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471360-58f3db80-a649-11e8-8b50-d30f7f38556c.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471360-58f3db80-a649-11e8-8b50-d30f7f38556c.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471360-58f3db80-a649-11e8-8b50-d30f7f38556c.jpg"></noscript>
Valley of flowers resembles a fairytale land filled with stunning, vivacious and bright colored flowers. It is prominent because of its biggest collection of wild flora species. Go for this trek just for the gorgeous view that it offers. Best time to go on this trek from July to mid-September.</p>

<h4>6.  Nag Tibba Trek</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471358-585b4500-a649-11e8-87aa-0062762369d9.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471358-585b4500-a649-11e8-87aa-0062762369d9.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471358-585b4500-a649-11e8-87aa-0062762369d9.jpg"></noscript>
Nag Tibba trek is an extremely brilliant hilly expedition, particularly if you go there during the winters. In winters, the surrounding mountains are snow-capped and the road too is covered with the thin layer of snow. If you are fortunate, you might even experience the snow, which will be all the more stunning.</p>

<h4>7.  Brahmatal Trek</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471354-572a1800-a649-11e8-9050-dd3d472aea8f.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471354-572a1800-a649-11e8-9050-dd3d472aea8f.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44471354-572a1800-a649-11e8-9050-dd3d472aea8f.jpg"></noscript>
Brahmatal peak opens all through the winter, even in January when the season is at its peak; and not many trails permit such leverage in the region. The trek is wonderful and simple, with moderate elevation that can be reached without much training and guidance.</p>

<p>These simple treks in India assure you an absolute adventurous time in the Himalayan foothills. So what are you waiting for? So whenever you have a long weekend, just go for one of these easy treks in India.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Websites Giving the Best Deals on Ethnic Wear for Raksha Bandhan]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/22/5-websites-giving-the-best-deals-on-ethnic-wear-for-raksha-bandhan/"/>
    <updated>2018-08-22T20:16:18+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/22/5-websites-giving-the-best-deals-on-ethnic-wear-for-raksha-bandhan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470760-285f7200-a648-11e8-8d45-cfb969003344.jpg" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470760-285f7200-a648-11e8-8d45-cfb969003344.jpg" width="400" height="500" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470760-285f7200-a648-11e8-8d45-cfb969003344.jpg"></noscript>
Raksha Bandhan is fast approaching and it&rsquo;s the right time for us to buy ethnic wear. Festive occasions like this are special for us because apart from getting a chance to celebrate, we also get to buy and wear different kinds of stunning ethnic wear. Who doesn&rsquo;t love to pamper themselves every once in a while by dressing up in ethnic royalty?</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>More and more people are starting to use websites, mobile apps, etc. to find the best deals and not make the trip to the closest bricks-and-mortar shop. By using the right websites and resources, it can be very easy to find great deals online. Here are 5 of the best websites offering online deals this Raksha Bandhan:</p>

<h4>1.  Myntra</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470764-28f80880-a648-11e8-8009-364df6526750.JPG" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470764-28f80880-a648-11e8-8009-364df6526750.JPG" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470764-28f80880-a648-11e8-8009-364df6526750.JPG"></noscript>
Myntra is an e-retailer that is offering exclusive and mega discounts on ethnic wear this Raksha Bandhan. There are more than 1500 Indian brands and 200 brands globally and is certainly one of the topmost style destinations for all ethnic fashion enthusiasts. Must check out their lucrative offers and buy something for yourself and your sibling.</p>

<h4>2.  Amazon</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470760-285f7200-a648-11e8-8d45-cfb969003344.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470760-285f7200-a648-11e8-8d45-cfb969003344.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470760-285f7200-a648-11e8-8d45-cfb969003344.jpg"></noscript>
Based in the United States and one of the largest online retailers in the world, Amazon offers an amazing ethnic wear collection. Outfits within this category have been categorized according to genders, such as women&rsquo;s and men&rsquo;s clothing; according to brands, such as Manyavar, Biba, etc. or also according to stores, such as of that belonging to a specific designer, and so on. The site offers a 30-day return on its all its products with &lsquo;no questions asked&rsquo;. So, you must check out their amazing offers today.</p>

<h4>3.  Jabong</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470761-285f7200-a648-11e8-9ef8-1f9a19455bed.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470761-285f7200-a648-11e8-9ef8-1f9a19455bed.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470761-285f7200-a648-11e8-9ef8-1f9a19455bed.jpg"></noscript>
Since essentially Jabong is a fashion portal, it offers a great variety of options for women, men, kids, in ethnic wear. It offers its customers with options that range from local brands and even designers like Rohit Bal to Rohit Gandhi-Rahul Khanna, etc. If you are someone who loves ethnic fashion, their ethnic wear is something you must check out. You Raksha Bandhan outfit worries will be sorted.</p>

<h4>4.  Lifestyle India</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470762-28f80880-a648-11e8-845a-8b96d905016d.JPG" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470762-28f80880-a648-11e8-845a-8b96d905016d.JPG" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470762-28f80880-a648-11e8-845a-8b96d905016d.JPG"></noscript>
Lifestyle India is a fashion retailer that offers menswear, women&rsquo;s wear, jewelry, cosmetics, and so on. They also have brick and mortar stores across India. It provides its customers with exclusive deals with new discounts on ethnic wear and also offers affordable fashion.</p>

<h4>5.  Ajio</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470759-27c6db80-a648-11e8-960e-1dd5f28d9798.JPG" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470759-27c6db80-a648-11e8-960e-1dd5f28d9798.JPG" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44470759-27c6db80-a648-11e8-960e-1dd5f28d9798.JPG"></noscript>
Within the fashion category, their products are categorized into men&rsquo;s, women&rsquo;s, and kid&rsquo;s fashion, which are further categorized according to the type of fashion product and type of clothing. Ajio offers an assortment of options within each fashion section for both women and men, such as Ethnic wear, which consists of sarees, anarkalis, palazzos, dress material, semi stitched and stitched kurtas, salwars and churidars, and so on.</p>

<p>All you need to do is find something that you love and then compare the offers you are getting, which are offered at these amazing websites and then buy the one that meets your budget along with your requirements.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Things to Do in Andaman Nicobar Islands]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/15/10-things-to-do-in-andaman-nicobar-islands/"/>
    <updated>2018-08-15T12:20:53+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/15/10-things-to-do-in-andaman-nicobar-islands</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134850-27c361f4-a084-11e8-94a0-ecf714c7527c.jpg" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134850-27c361f4-a084-11e8-94a0-ecf714c7527c.jpg" width="400" height="500" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134850-27c361f4-a084-11e8-94a0-ecf714c7527c.jpg"></noscript>
Andaman and Nicobar Islands is a ceaselessly stunning, serene and enthralling cluster of islands - almost a paradise. Due to its flora fauna, Andaman &amp; Nicobar is surrounded by turquoise color water. Adventure voyages, crystal clear waters, amazing view and the most amazing sea food delicacies- these are just few amongst the countless amazing things that you can do at Andaman &amp; Nicobar Islands. Below are some of them:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>1.  Snorkeling</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134848-277ec576-a084-11e8-8b1e-67e5ca869c86.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134848-277ec576-a084-11e8-8b1e-67e5ca869c86.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134848-277ec576-a084-11e8-8b1e-67e5ca869c86.jpg"></noscript>
Snorkeling will certainly bind you to this place eternally, for the indescribable and hidden sea life seen through this activity is something you will always remember.</p>

<h4>2.  Scuba Diving</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134844-268ec3dc-a084-11e8-8924-8883d84cc72b.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134844-268ec3dc-a084-11e8-8924-8883d84cc72b.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134844-268ec3dc-a084-11e8-8924-8883d84cc72b.jpg"></noscript>
Fishes, Coral Reefs, Sea Anemones, Sea Cucumbers, Clams –the list is never-ending and colors are something that you just can&rsquo;t visualize. Scuba diving into the colorful life of sea makes for a lifetime experience - how frequently do we dive into their world after all?</p>

<h4>3.  Parasailing</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134843-264bb006-a084-11e8-9c9d-63d14c24f463.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134843-264bb006-a084-11e8-9c9d-63d14c24f463.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134843-264bb006-a084-11e8-9c9d-63d14c24f463.jpg"></noscript>
Parasailing is another thrilling adventure activity in the Andaman &amp; Nicobar Islands. Beautiful clouds, sea, and waves here will make it a memorable one.</p>

<h4>4.  Traveling in a Sea Plane</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134846-26f76144-a084-11e8-914b-96df20f48f09.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134846-26f76144-a084-11e8-914b-96df20f48f09.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134846-26f76144-a084-11e8-914b-96df20f48f09.jpg"></noscript>
Traveling in a seaplane is one of the most special things you can do in the Andaman &amp; Nicobar Islands. You can go for this exceptional ride while going to Havelock from Port Blair or while returning.</p>

<h4>5.  Bird watching</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134840-25c4a098-a084-11e8-96e2-720e3b6db1ea.jpeg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134840-25c4a098-a084-11e8-96e2-720e3b6db1ea.jpeg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134840-25c4a098-a084-11e8-96e2-720e3b6db1ea.jpeg"></noscript>
Bird watching is a very pleasurable past time - one that is loved by people all around the world. Most bird watching enthusiasts will love Andaman &amp; Nicobar Islands and get to track down diverse species of birds for the utter enjoyment of it.</p>

<h4>6.  Swimming</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134852-280764f8-a084-11e8-801d-2398450606b8.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134852-280764f8-a084-11e8-801d-2398450606b8.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134852-280764f8-a084-11e8-801d-2398450606b8.jpg"></noscript>
Swimming in the open water in Andaman &amp; Nicobar Islands will be a unique experience for you. The sea conditions, the weather will make for a great experience.</p>

<h4>7.  Sightseeing</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134847-273b7b4a-a084-11e8-95df-7645fd32afe4.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134847-273b7b4a-a084-11e8-95df-7645fd32afe4.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134847-273b7b4a-a084-11e8-95df-7645fd32afe4.jpg"></noscript>
Once you see this place you will definitely get enthralled by its scenic attractions and outstanding topography. Dense forests, pristine beaches, and lush green vegetation make Andaman &amp; Nicobar Islands nothing less than heaven.</p>

<h4>8.  Attending the Light &amp; Sound Show at Cellular Jail</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134839-2581d34e-a084-11e8-81bb-33d37661619f.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134839-2581d34e-a084-11e8-81bb-33d37661619f.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134839-2581d34e-a084-11e8-81bb-33d37661619f.jpg"></noscript>
Going to the Cellular Jail in Port Blair is among the best things to do in Andaman &amp; Nicobar Islands. The jail, previously Kaala Paani Jail, was used as a prison by the British. Its Light &amp; Sound Show is the highlight.</p>

<h4>9.  Island Hopping</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134841-260a34a0-a084-11e8-9974-b7e52285ba3e.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134841-260a34a0-a084-11e8-9974-b7e52285ba3e.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134841-260a34a0-a084-11e8-9974-b7e52285ba3e.jpg"></noscript>
If you are fascinated by nature, then it would be the best place for you. Visiting and exploring this island is equal to finding the heaven on earth. The beauty of this island is beyond the words and illustrations.</p>

<h4>10. Catch exquisite sunrises and sunsets</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134850-27c361f4-a084-11e8-94a0-ecf714c7527c.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134850-27c361f4-a084-11e8-94a0-ecf714c7527c.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44134850-27c361f4-a084-11e8-94a0-ecf714c7527c.jpg"></noscript>
One of the best things you can enjoy at sea is being able to see beautiful sunrises and sunsets. If you love seeing sunrises and sunsets then this will certainly be something you can enjoy tour here. Be sure you carry your camera to capture those precious memories.</p>

<p>Apart from its attractions and activities, Andaman &amp; Nicobar Islands is equally famous for its exotic seafood, warm hospitality and outstanding hotels and resorts.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Internet Going Gaga Over Kiki Challenge?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/12/why-is-internet-going-gaga-over-kiki-challenge/"/>
    <updated>2018-08-12T17:11:55+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/12/why-is-internet-going-gaga-over-kiki-challenge</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001679-ec635038-9e53-11e8-8d13-6cb2d822fed2.jpg" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001679-ec635038-9e53-11e8-8d13-6cb2d822fed2.jpg" width="400" height="500" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001679-ec635038-9e53-11e8-8d13-6cb2d822fed2.jpg"></noscript>
A new challenge has surfaced in the realm of online video challenge. Besides, at this point, you must already know that it&rsquo;s the Kiki Challenge!</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Dancing alongside a moving auto or car may sound strange, however, that is the thing that a huge number of social media users around the world are doing to participate in this viral Kiki Challenge or In My Feelings Challenge - inspired by Canadian rapper Drake&rsquo;s most recent song. This song’s lyrics go like, &lsquo;Kiki do you love me&rsquo; and it has made police around the world to issue alerts against this unsafe challenge.</p>

<p>So, what is basically the KiKi challenge? This demands the challenge participant to move alongside a moving vehicle and afterward hop once more into the car. The car moves slowly with the individual hopping out of it and dancing to Drake&rsquo;s latest track, &lsquo;In My Feelings&rsquo;, on street– for the most part, in the middle of ongoing traffic.</p>

<h3>How did this all start?</h3>

<div class="videoWrapper">
<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/FRtDn_4f_wI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div>


<p>In spite of the fact that the &ldquo;Kiki, do you love me?&rdquo; is made by Canadian rapper Drake, yet the KiKi challenge turned into a web sensation on June 30 when comic Shiggy posted an Instagram video wherein he was dancing to this Drake song on a street. Later American footballer Odell Beckham Jr likewise recorded himself dancing to this song. Even superstars like Will Smith have participated in the Kiki challenge and he’s seen dancing on top of a bridge in Budapest.</p>

<p>In case, you are active on social media, you must&rsquo;ve watched them all dancing to this most recent hit number of Canadian rapper Drake. Your social media feed must be filled with people participating in this bizarre challenge and the number of people attempting it is increasing every second. And not only stars, common people are going gaga over this newly surfaced Kiki challenge. Social media enthusiasts seem to take that challenge very seriously.</p>

<p>The current trend has additionally led the Indian celebs too participate in the Kiki challenge. Actors like Nia Sharma and Adah Sharma have shared their recordings on Instagram. Comedy pioneers like AIB have posted some interesting recordings of the Kiki challenge. They have included the older recordings of Anushka Sharma and Sachin Tendulkar conversing with the common people on the road.
If you are a shoe lover and always have an urge to buy a pair of shoes, then you probably can’t have enough pairs to satiate your love for shoes. While you might not have all the shoes you would like to have, here are the essential 7 pairs that every girl should have in their collection:</p>

<p>The impact of this Kiki challenge is so massive that police departments around the globe needed to issue warnings after seeing the recordings online where people have fallen out of the car even before they began doing the dance. To think about it, the challenge is not only bizarre but also very risky. Not only could it be risky for the participant but also for the people moving on the streets.
The US, Spain and the UAE Police departments cautioned individuals that the Kiki challenge is hazardous and individuals attempting it may face criminal accusations due to the massive risks involved.</p>

<p>Essentially, Mumbai police too warned individuals to &ldquo;desist from public nuisance or face the music!&rdquo;</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Shoes Every Girl Must Own]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/12/7-shoes-every-girl-must-own/"/>
    <updated>2018-08-12T16:28:12+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/12/7-shoes-every-girl-must-own</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001289-9f8b3b7e-9e4c-11e8-8c47-4330971ed49c.jpg" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001289-9f8b3b7e-9e4c-11e8-8c47-4330971ed49c.jpg" width="400" height="500" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001289-9f8b3b7e-9e4c-11e8-8c47-4330971ed49c.jpg"></noscript>
If you are a shoe lover and always have an urge to buy a pair of shoes, then you probably can’t have enough pairs to satiate your love for shoes. While you might not have all the shoes you would like to have, here are the essential 7 pairs that every girl should have in their collection:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>1.  Pumps</h4>

<p>When it comes to style, pumps never go out of style. These shoes are good for all ages and are very versatile when it comes to mixing and matching your overall outfit. Pumps are becoming more abundant on the shoe racks at the stores and they are commonly seen as fashionable for everyday wear.  You can get them in just about any color and they match up effortlessly with anything from a skirt and top to a pair of jeans. Its strength lies in its ease of use and its versatility.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001286-9dce9b32-9e4c-11e8-8837-cccd4a47ade5.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001286-9dce9b32-9e4c-11e8-8837-cccd4a47ade5.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001286-9dce9b32-9e4c-11e8-8837-cccd4a47ade5.jpg"></noscript></p>

<h4>2.  Sneakers</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001289-9f8b3b7e-9e4c-11e8-8c47-4330971ed49c.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001289-9f8b3b7e-9e4c-11e8-8c47-4330971ed49c.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001289-9f8b3b7e-9e4c-11e8-8c47-4330971ed49c.jpg"></noscript>
We wear shoes almost every day of our lives. That means that we want supportive, comfy shoes for all the different areas of our daily lives. Sneakers are one of the few shoes that you can pick that fit into almost every part of your daily life. Whether you want to go for a walk, play a game, go out dancing or even to work you can certainly find a pair of sneakers that will fit right in. Sneakers are well-known for their comfort and their relaxed style.</p>

<h4>3.  Ankle boots</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001276-99042e8c-9e4c-11e8-928c-23c870e7c398.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001276-99042e8c-9e4c-11e8-928c-23c870e7c398.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001276-99042e8c-9e4c-11e8-928c-23c870e7c398.jpg"></noscript>
Ankle boots are a wonderful fashion accessory, whether you choose high-heeled, tasseled, fur-lined or flat, a good quality pair of ankle boots can set you apart in the fashion game. One of the trendiest items of footwear available, ankle boots can make an array of style statements.</p>

<h4>4.  Flat Sandals</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001278-9a6da4ce-9e4c-11e8-9600-9fde9c61ee09.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001278-9a6da4ce-9e4c-11e8-9600-9fde9c61ee09.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001278-9a6da4ce-9e4c-11e8-9600-9fde9c61ee09.jpg"></noscript>
Flat sandals are one of the staple accessories of summer and spring fashion. They are comfortable and suitable footwear for a plethora of events from a beach party or an evening outing.</p>

<h4>5.  Knee High Boots</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001282-9c8cd716-9e4c-11e8-9388-a3720bd3dbf7.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001282-9c8cd716-9e4c-11e8-9388-a3720bd3dbf7.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001282-9c8cd716-9e4c-11e8-9388-a3720bd3dbf7.jpg"></noscript>
Knee high boots come in a huge number of designs and colors so you are certain to find at least one pair that you love. Knee high boots can be worn with almost anything in your wardrobe so you can go formal to casual to sensual with these boots in a jiffy.</p>

<h4>6.  Heels</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001279-9b38bf7e-9e4c-11e8-8163-ed2696abc38e.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001279-9b38bf7e-9e4c-11e8-8163-ed2696abc38e.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001279-9b38bf7e-9e4c-11e8-8163-ed2696abc38e.jpg"></noscript>
Women love to complete their look with heels. Heels are a trendy accessory in their closet and they have been highly popular among girls for a long time. These are the most classic type of shoes that women love to wear to accentuate their look.</p>

<h4>7.  Wedge Sandals</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001290-a7337daa-9e4c-11e8-8923-6496e9dbd43c.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001290-a7337daa-9e4c-11e8-8923-6496e9dbd43c.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/44001290-a7337daa-9e4c-11e8-8923-6496e9dbd43c.jpg"></noscript>
If you are looking for something comfy and easy to walk in, step into wedge sandals. Wedges are such a versatile shoe that they can be paired with virtually any outfit, from formal to informal.</p>

<p>These are the top 7 types of must-have shoes in a typical women&rsquo;s closet. With all the fresh style coming out every season, you will certainly find that perfect pair for you.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delhi NCR Restaurants That Provide the Best Dinner Buffet]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/11/delhi-ncr-restaurants-that-provide-the-best-dinner-buffet/"/>
    <updated>2018-08-11T21:21:46+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/11/delhi-ncr-restaurants-that-provide-the-best-dinner-buffet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993615-dd1881da-9dad-11e8-964b-ef5c32a5c50e.jpg" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993615-dd1881da-9dad-11e8-964b-ef5c32a5c50e.jpg" width="400" height="500" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993615-dd1881da-9dad-11e8-964b-ef5c32a5c50e.jpg"></noscript>
Delhi is a city that is known for amazing food, especially when it comes to buffets. There are a number of restaurants who offer great value for money all the time. Here are some of the best Delhi-NCR restaurants that provide the best dinner buffet:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>1. Barbeque Nation</h4>

<p>With one of the most elegant dining space, Barbeque Nation buffet, with Veg dinner buffet costing INR 950+tax and non-veg dinner buffet costing INR 1047+tax, is worth every penny. Dinner buffet is from 6:30PM to 10:30. Some of the amazing dishes include their delectable veg and non-veg starters, Butter Chicken, Cocktails, Biriyani, Malai Kulfi, and Salads. Their lavish dinner buffet is the best way to spend your evening. Additionally, their staff is warm and courteous.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993518-65ea1836-9dac-11e8-99b5-e552c18282ea.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993518-65ea1836-9dac-11e8-99b5-e552c18282ea.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993518-65ea1836-9dac-11e8-99b5-e552c18282ea.jpg"></noscript></p>

<h4>2. The Buffeteria</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993519-66209cb2-9dac-11e8-9389-c762944ec433.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993519-66209cb2-9dac-11e8-9389-c762944ec433.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993519-66209cb2-9dac-11e8-9389-c762944ec433.jpg"></noscript>
The Buffeteria gives a charming feel. Indian cuisine is prepared perfectly throughout the buffet. And Butter Chicken, Malai Chaap, Palak Patta Chaat, Rasmalai, Gulab Jamun, Rasgulla, Kheer are some of the popular dishes there. Dinner buffet runs from 7 PM to 11 PM. Expect to pay ₹750 to ₹890 for dinner, but it is well worth it. This place is ideal for when you wish to have some top-quality food with your friends and family and unwind in a calm ambiance.</p>

<h4>3. Band Baaja Baaraat</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993517-65aedfb4-9dac-11e8-9ad3-474e498fe130.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993517-65aedfb4-9dac-11e8-9ad3-474e498fe130.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993517-65aedfb4-9dac-11e8-9ad3-474e498fe130.jpg"></noscript>
Serving the dinner buffets, ranging from ₹700 to ₹950, this Band Baaja Baaraat buffet at the Rio gives you a selection of many creatures of the sea, with stations themed after countries throughout the world. It is a tremendous value for money, as you can choose from the range of Veg Starter, Dal Makhani, Honey Chilli Potatoes, Gol Gappe, Gulab Jamun, Momos, and many other varieties of perfectly-cooked food.</p>

<h4>4. Pirates Of Grill</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993520-66573f9c-9dac-11e8-8878-6d76105ed9db.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993520-66573f9c-9dac-11e8-8878-6d76105ed9db.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993520-66573f9c-9dac-11e8-8878-6d76105ed9db.jpg"></noscript>
Pirates Of Grill is a restaurant cum bar with a beautiful decor that you will love spending time at with your friends and family. They prepare many kinds of dishes, from Panner Tikka, Honey Chilli Potatoes, Salsa Potato, Chicken Biriyani, Mocktails, and more. And the desserts are so good you love them. At between ₹700 to ₹950 for dinner, it is an excellent buffet deal. Their buffet is quite a good bargain featuring succulent barbecue starters and an array of Brazilian grilled snacks.</p>

<h4>5. Themis Barbecue House</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993606-a63f32e4-9dad-11e8-8d0e-48252ccaa2a7.png" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993606-a63f32e4-9dad-11e8-8d0e-48252ccaa2a7.png" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993606-a63f32e4-9dad-11e8-8d0e-48252ccaa2a7.png"></noscript>
Themis Barbecue House offers an elaborate dinner buffet. These are all fantastic values, with massive selections of delectable foods, and of course, cocktails and drinks. All are offered at affordable dinner buffet rates. The service, the quality and the presentation – everything is on point. Their buffet is very good, especially for the price featuring Prawn, Mushroom Tikka, Beetroot Halwa, Dahi Kebab, Chicken Pizza, etc. They offer a plethora of options for you to choose from and is perfect for the food lovers.</p>

<p>If you are looking for the best buffets in Delhi, these 5 options are sure to leave you full and content. While these buffets are some of the best that you can find, there are tons of other options in Delhi for dinner buffets.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Must Have Bottom Wears for Every Fashionista]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/11/8-must-have-bottom-wears-for-every-fashionista/"/>
    <updated>2018-08-11T21:05:44+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/11/8-must-have-bottom-wears-for-every-fashionista</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993469-a5502dcc-9dab-11e8-972b-e0f36a656bf6.jpg" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993469-a5502dcc-9dab-11e8-972b-e0f36a656bf6.jpg" width="400" height="500" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993469-a5502dcc-9dab-11e8-972b-e0f36a656bf6.jpg"></noscript>
A couple of years ago, there weren&rsquo;t a whole lot of choices available for bottom wears. But as fashion got trendier, the world has become your oyster! Palazzos, cigarette pants, dhoti pants, culottes - the silhouettes are endless! So, whatever your shape and preference, here are 8 must-have bottom-wears for you.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>1.  Palazzos</h4>

<p>The key to looking stylish in palazzos is to feel comfy wearing them, which is exactly what palazzos are all about - comfortable and fashionable. Palazzos are stylish and cool summer-wear and give women a much-needed break from the dull blue jeans, dresses, normal work pants and salwar kameez. Palazzos have become a rage in India; it is the most loved Indo-western trend adopted from the flared silhouettes of the 60s and 70s.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993400-4abde742-9daa-11e8-9b08-98d23f2143d7.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993400-4abde742-9daa-11e8-9b08-98d23f2143d7.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993400-4abde742-9daa-11e8-9b08-98d23f2143d7.jpg"></noscript></p>

<h4>2.  Culottes</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993397-4a1a79e0-9daa-11e8-8fc2-7da07cd78de1.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993397-4a1a79e0-9daa-11e8-8fc2-7da07cd78de1.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993397-4a1a79e0-9daa-11e8-8fc2-7da07cd78de1.jpg"></noscript>
Culottes were unquestionably one of the most sought-after fashions of the 60s and 70s. Not only could you go to an exercise class in them but also run errands, without having to change your clothes. Now culottes can be one of the most versatile clothing items in your closet. Simply pair culottes with a t-shirt for casual gatherings or wear a dressier top and shoes for special occasions. You certainly need to give the culottes a chance this season.</p>

<h4>3.  Ethnic skirts</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993399-4a8847c2-9daa-11e8-96d1-11f5bc0e69bf.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993399-4a8847c2-9daa-11e8-96d1-11f5bc0e69bf.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993399-4a8847c2-9daa-11e8-96d1-11f5bc0e69bf.jpg"></noscript>
Pass up the pencil skirts this season and buy yourself a stunning long ethnic skirt. And you are sure to look like a diva! These skirts paired with crop top are the perfect party wear for women attending any small function.</p>

<h4>4.  Cigarette pants</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993396-49e5a9a4-9daa-11e8-9333-9386bcf4a461.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993396-49e5a9a4-9daa-11e8-9333-9386bcf4a461.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993396-49e5a9a4-9daa-11e8-9333-9386bcf4a461.jpg"></noscript>
No girl’s closet can ever be complete without a pair of 4.  Cigarette pants! It is one Indian outfit that can be worn to the office or even lunch dates. They are loved for their flattering fit and have the power to make you feel oh-so-chic.</p>

<h4>5.  Dhoti pants</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993398-4a52d8bc-9daa-11e8-924a-f1f0a89fe4b0.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993398-4a52d8bc-9daa-11e8-924a-f1f0a89fe4b0.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993398-4a52d8bc-9daa-11e8-924a-f1f0a89fe4b0.jpg"></noscript>
The dhoti pants are back in style, giving women some incredible designs to pick from. It&rsquo;s truly a great item for anyone looking for an appealing bottom-wear to add to their closet.</p>

<h4>6.  Ripped jeans</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993402-4af89798-9daa-11e8-8566-5c480773eef6.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993402-4af89798-9daa-11e8-8566-5c480773eef6.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993402-4af89798-9daa-11e8-8566-5c480773eef6.jpg"></noscript>
The ripped jeans are now very much in fashion. It has done well in the majority of countries and is fast catching up in other places too. Especially, teenagers are crazy about this ripped style and they sure know how to look cool without getting influenced by the latest trends.</p>

<h4>7.  Boyfriend jeans</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993395-49b117de-9daa-11e8-94d2-fea55c6c1403.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993395-49b117de-9daa-11e8-94d2-fea55c6c1403.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993395-49b117de-9daa-11e8-94d2-fea55c6c1403.jpg"></noscript>
When summer comes, can boyfriend jeans be far behind? One of the great products of the boyfriend fashion trend is the boyfriend jeans. These jeans are the latest rage amongst the comfortable fashion lovers. The best part is that you can steal it from your partner&rsquo;s closet!</p>

<h4>8.  Shorts/ hot pants</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993403-4b2fc43e-9daa-11e8-8168-4985f284b249.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993403-4b2fc43e-9daa-11e8-8168-4985f284b249.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993403-4b2fc43e-9daa-11e8-8168-4985f284b249.jpg"></noscript>
There is nothing comfier than wearing shorts or hot pants in summer day. They are not only worn during vacation but also anytime since they offer minimalism and hot look!</p>

<p>Now that you know what bottom war items to have in your closet, it&rsquo;s time to go online and start shopping for the perfect bottom wear available for girls out there.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Expect From Amazon and Flipkart Freedom Sale This Time]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/10/what-to-expect-from-amazon-and-flipkart-freedom-sale-this-time/"/>
    <updated>2018-08-10T08:59:45+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/10/what-to-expect-from-amazon-and-flipkart-freedom-sale-this-time</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43937675-b05c11d4-9c7c-11e8-820c-554194d0850e.jpg" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43937675-b05c11d4-9c7c-11e8-820c-554194d0850e.jpg" width="400" height="500" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43937675-b05c11d4-9c7c-11e8-820c-554194d0850e.jpg"></noscript>
We all love sales. Don’t we? This Independence Day, both the leading e-commerce companies –Flipkart and Amazon are offering choicest offers and discounts on a multitude of items. Amazon&rsquo;s Freedom Sale will go on for 4 days, whereas Flipkart&rsquo;s The Big Freedom Sale will be on for 3 days.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>Flipkart&rsquo;s The Big Freedom Sale</h4>

<p>Flipkart&rsquo;s The Big Freedom Sale has been declared. The e-commerce retailer has disclosed that its next massive sale, on the occasion India&rsquo;s 72nd Independence Day, will be held from August 10, 2018, to August 12, 2018. While offers haven&rsquo;t been disclosed yet, Flipkart has declared that it will hold blockbuster deals, rush hour deals, The Freedom Hour and hourly deals during the 3 days sale period. The Flipkart deal will have deals on Electronics, Fashion, Beauty, Daily essentials, and other categories.
Apart from offers, Flipkart is additionally offering new deals at regular intervals, change of costs every 8 hours, and &ldquo;revolutionary&rdquo; offers at 12 am till 2 am. Flipkart has collaborated with Citi Bank to offer even more rewarding offers.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43937592-45bffcf0-9c7c-11e8-9a9f-9ddb3c13792f.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43937592-45bffcf0-9c7c-11e8-9a9f-9ddb3c13792f.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43937592-45bffcf0-9c7c-11e8-9a9f-9ddb3c13792f.jpg"></noscript>
From what little has been disclosed about the Flipkart deal till now, there will be offers on cell phones from brands like Xiaomi, Apple, Samsung among many others. Up to 80 percent discount is additionally expected on select items like PCs, laptops, TVs, sound equipment, and cameras from makers, for example, Apple, Dell, Google, etc. And that&rsquo;s only the tip of the iceberg.</p>

<h4>Amazon&rsquo;s Freedom Sale</h4>

<p>Like every year, Amazon India is also hosting its Freedom Sale that commences one day prior to Flipkart’s, on August 9. However, the sale will run until August 12. The sneak peak of the sale that is as of now running on Amazon website says that it will have more than 20,000 deals across 2,500 prominent brands and about 200 categories.
You can expect great bargains on cell phones, for example, OnePlus 6, Moto G6, and many others. The organization has additionally joined hands together up with SBI for more lucrative offers. There will be 10 percent of cashback on buys utilizing SBI credit cards and debit cards.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43937593-4605ab88-9c7c-11e8-990c-94636b588c27.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43937593-4605ab88-9c7c-11e8-990c-94636b588c27.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43937593-4605ab88-9c7c-11e8-990c-94636b588c27.jpg"></noscript>
One can get upto 40% discount on appliances and TVs. Moreover, one can get upto INR 22,000 by exchanging select products. They additionally have amazing benefits like no-cost EMI and 48-hour installation. One can avail these offers on brands, for example, LG, Samsung, Sony, Voltas, Whirlpool, BPL, and Sanyo.
Amazon Prime customers will be eligible for special offers and deals too. They are additionally rolling out the Amazon App Jackpot with prizes upto INR 4 Lacs.</p>

<h4>Conclusion</h4>

<p>Whether you are looking forward to buying some home appliance or you are looking for the perfect gift for someone special in your life, you should take the maximum advantage of these sales. Be it Flipkart or Amazon, you can get a wide collection of items at competitive rates.
To stay geared up for the Freedom sale, we recommend that you add your favorite products to your wishlist, update your delivery address and save debit/ credit card details to your account in advance.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friendship Day Quick Gift Ideas]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/05/friendship-day-quick-gift-ideas/"/>
    <updated>2018-08-05T14:03:08+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/05/friendship-day-quick-gift-ideas</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684163-cdc2f016-98b8-11e8-834c-01a85ad8b278.png" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684163-cdc2f016-98b8-11e8-834c-01a85ad8b278.png" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684163-cdc2f016-98b8-11e8-834c-01a85ad8b278.png"></noscript>
Did you just remember that it is first Sunday of August and it is supposed to be friendship day? Ooh Shit! Me too. Remember the promises that you made while coming out of school or College or leaving your city, to stay in touch and share every small details and big events of the life. Well..time kaha hai?</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>So, this friendship day celebrate all kind of long distance and short distance friendship and surprise your friends with these amazing gifs and let them know they still hold important position in your heart as well as life.</p>

<h4>1. Cake:</h4>

<p>AAh..who doesn’t love cake?! This one is for foodie friend of yours with whom you have shared uncountable number of fights on the last loaf. Let them get nostalgic with the memories and come back to you. And friendship is nothing less than a CELEBRATION!!
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684169-cf15e2e8-98b8-11e8-95b2-332e9edaed23.png" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684169-cf15e2e8-98b8-11e8-95b2-332e9edaed23.png" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684169-cf15e2e8-98b8-11e8-95b2-332e9edaed23.png"></noscript></p>

<h4>2. Friendship Trophy:</h4>

<p>You were not so good or not so bad that you are now, before you met your friend. So this is for that friend of yours who brought you out of break up trauma, spoiled you and stood against odd to stand with you.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684168-cedf97f6-98b8-11e8-8189-dbaff649c68a.png" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684168-cedf97f6-98b8-11e8-8189-dbaff649c68a.png" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684168-cedf97f6-98b8-11e8-8189-dbaff649c68a.png"></noscript></p>

<h4>3. Printed Cushion:</h4>

<p>This one is for the sloth bear of your group with whom you hold numerous memories of house parties and philosophical nights. This is the best way to tell them thanks for loving you when you could not love yourself.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684167-cea74b12-98b8-11e8-9581-06222abdda50.png" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684167-cea74b12-98b8-11e8-9581-06222abdda50.png" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684167-cea74b12-98b8-11e8-9581-06222abdda50.png"></noscript></p>

<h4>4. A jar of memories:</h4>

<p>This one is for old school friend of your who loves to preserve things. Let your friend know that you too have preserved your share of memories with him/ her too.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684166-ce70cf10-98b8-11e8-8d64-102007bf15ed.png" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684166-ce70cf10-98b8-11e8-8d64-102007bf15ed.png" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684166-ce70cf10-98b8-11e8-8d64-102007bf15ed.png"></noscript></p>

<h4>5. Plant:</h4>

<p>This one is for the category of the friend who does not love much of flowers or avoid being cheesy. You could simply symbolise your friendship with the growing plant and say how much you have bloomed as a person in their friendship.
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684165-ce378f66-98b8-11e8-9284-66cd6a1195f0.png" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684165-ce378f66-98b8-11e8-9284-66cd6a1195f0.png" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684165-ce378f66-98b8-11e8-9284-66cd6a1195f0.png"></noscript></p>

<h4>6. A phone call:</h4>

<p>Well there is no problem that cannot be solved by talking, words have always created wonders. This friendship day, call your friends who you do not talk to anymore but miss them. May be they would be too waiting for your phone call!!
<img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684164-cdfd21dc-98b8-11e8-9d83-e7606cad4786.png" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684164-cdfd21dc-98b8-11e8-9d83-e7606cad4786.png" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43684164-cdfd21dc-98b8-11e8-9d83-e7606cad4786.png"></noscript></p>

<p>Don’t miss a chance to say your friends “Tera Yaar hoon mai” because “Har ek dost zaroori hota hai”</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Netflix: Go Solo With Hotstar]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/04/no-netflix-go-solo-with-hotstar/"/>
    <updated>2018-08-04T14:52:26+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/04/no-netflix-go-solo-with-hotstar</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674741-dbc4ea20-97f5-11e8-9a6f-828725b48ca0.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674741-dbc4ea20-97f5-11e8-9a6f-828725b48ca0.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674741-dbc4ea20-97f5-11e8-9a6f-828725b48ca0.jpg"></noscript>
When the world around is bragging about Netflix and its series, not having Netflix subscription should not feel like the end of the world. Here is list of things that you could watch on Hotstar without burning any hole in the pocket and can have fun, laughter riots and sense of nostalgia with a visit of serials that you used to watch in Childhood.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Here is a package of serials that can keep you engaged and entertained this weekend:</p>

<h4>1.  AIB (All India Bakchod):</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674742-dc18f67e-97f5-11e8-9cd2-536a8d83ac1b.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674742-dc18f67e-97f5-11e8-9cd2-536a8d83ac1b.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674742-dc18f67e-97f5-11e8-9cd2-536a8d83ac1b.jpg"></noscript>
YES! That group of boys, who roasted Arjun Kapoor and Ranveer Singh along with the whole bollywood troop, is available on Hotstar. This is a Hotstar Originals where they have used all the ongoing social and political issues in a humorous way.</p>

<p><em>Warning:</em> Use earplugs, these boys have rich vocabulary when it comes to slang and they don’t leave a single chance to show off it!!</p>

<h4>2.  Sarabhai Vs Sarabhai:</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674743-dc5bd0fc-97f5-11e8-8d4b-3a339b250d1c.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674743-dc5bd0fc-97f5-11e8-8d4b-3a339b250d1c.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674743-dc5bd0fc-97f5-11e8-8d4b-3a339b250d1c.jpg"></noscript>
That conflict of middle-class Monisha and the nok jhok among Sarabhais is quite a thing to re-visit. This entire series takes you down to the memory lane when you could sit and laugh without fearing of any scene of obscenity.
Only Hotstar has got the new season along with the retro one, so do not miss out!</p>

<h4>3.  Khichdi:</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674744-dcba5c3a-97f5-11e8-8c15-77798ca250dd.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674744-dcba5c3a-97f5-11e8-8c15-77798ca250dd.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674744-dcba5c3a-97f5-11e8-8c15-77798ca250dd.jpg"></noscript>
Ok! So we are the millennial who grew up with this much of awesomeness and Khichdi just added some more bright colors to it. The couple of doubtful Hansa and Genius Praful and the whole Gujrati family welcome you in their world of illogical yet entertaining conversation. The dialogues is going to linger in your mind for a while, right now in my mind is Praful&hellip;Tu to gadha hai!!
Again, Hotstar has got the latest and the oldest one.</p>

<h4>4.  Dill Mill Gayye:</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674745-dd19d714-97f5-11e8-9c90-c863b298aa64.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674745-dd19d714-97f5-11e8-9c90-c863b298aa64.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674745-dd19d714-97f5-11e8-9c90-c863b298aa64.jpg"></noscript>
Well.. talk of the town and a trend setter of its time. The romantic drama weaved around a hospital tale with set of hot actors and their sizzling chemistry. It deserves a walk. May be, you can get some romance inspo or best pick up lines.</p>

<h4>5.  Pyar ki ye ek kahani:</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674746-dd69d0b6-97f5-11e8-8a6a-464ac93b01ef.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674746-dd69d0b6-97f5-11e8-8a6a-464ac93b01ef.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674746-dd69d0b6-97f5-11e8-8a6a-464ac93b01ef.jpg"></noscript>
The saga of love among human,vampire and wolf or say Indian version of Vampire Diaries. The serial that took us to the fantasy world and made us google if vampires really exist! Another excuse to watch this serial is the chemistry of Piashree and Vivian Dsena, and simultaneous love triangle of college students.</p>

<p>Go on a solo rewind mode with Hotstar this weekend when the crowd around is doing Netflix and chill!!</p>

<p>Download the app from the <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=in.startv.hotstar&hl=en_IN" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">PlayStore</a> and just start.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Bags Every Girl Must Own]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/04/7-bags-every-girl-must-own/"/>
    <updated>2018-08-04T14:30:42+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/04/7-bags-every-girl-must-own</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674620-ae309c68-97f4-11e8-8be5-2aeaeaaa74a8.jpg" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674620-ae309c68-97f4-11e8-8be5-2aeaeaaa74a8.jpg" width="400" height="500" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674620-ae309c68-97f4-11e8-8be5-2aeaeaaa74a8.jpg"></noscript>
Bags are an essential part of a lady’s life. A lady needs to ensure she has the best and right bags to suit every single outfit in her closet. Luckily, it’s less demanding than it sounds. Here is a list of the must-have bags for all kinds of ladies.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674534-166f4164-97f3-11e8-8ce2-d614651fd8f6.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674534-166f4164-97f3-11e8-8ce2-d614651fd8f6.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674534-166f4164-97f3-11e8-8ce2-d614651fd8f6.jpg"></noscript></p>

<h4>1.  Satchel:</h4>

<p>There&rsquo;s one fundamental rule with regards to picking bags, and that is to buy them in neutral hues so that they will work everywhere - from the workplace to parties. Black, brown, grey, navy and camel are the best hues that will match well with every outfit. Pick a satchel for active lifestyles and for desk jobs and the like. Structured styles are more sophisticated and professional.</p>

<h4>2.  Backpack:</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674530-15a001b0-97f3-11e8-9432-bd5e5cfb5e86.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674530-15a001b0-97f3-11e8-9432-bd5e5cfb5e86.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674530-15a001b0-97f3-11e8-9432-bd5e5cfb5e86.jpg"></noscript>
It&rsquo;s an ideal opportunity to rediscover this school-time favorite, as there are many &ldquo;grown-up&rdquo; backpacks that are smart and practical even for a working professional. Purchase a stylish backpack; it&rsquo;s astonishing how these bags have transformed in the course the last couple of years. They look fashionable and are sufficiently big to hold a lot of stuff. Just get yourself one!</p>

<h4>3.  Tote Bag:</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674535-16a373d0-97f3-11e8-9aa5-12de63ec3446.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674535-16a373d0-97f3-11e8-9aa5-12de63ec3446.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674535-16a373d0-97f3-11e8-9aa5-12de63ec3446.jpg"></noscript>
The tote is everyone’s favorite. Every woman needs a tote bag in her closet. A sophisticated tote is ideal for a road trip or in the event that one has a couple of additional things more than usual. They add to the overall look and are also very stylish and trendy.  Made in quality leather they will never go out of style.</p>

<h4>4.  Classy Clutch:</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674531-15d368ca-97f3-11e8-8a85-f21bdda2a207.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674531-15d368ca-97f3-11e8-8a85-f21bdda2a207.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674531-15d368ca-97f3-11e8-8a85-f21bdda2a207.jpg"></noscript>
Ladies can show off their elegant style when they decide to add a statement clutch to their collection of bags. These look perfect with just a casual jeans and t-shirt day or for a night out on the town. Blow people&rsquo;s minds with this new favorite that can be grabbed to go along with pretty much anything when you just cannot decide what bag to carry.</p>

<h4>5.  Cross Body:</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674532-160552ea-97f3-11e8-9a77-be2d6a458053.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674532-160552ea-97f3-11e8-9a77-be2d6a458053.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674532-160552ea-97f3-11e8-9a77-be2d6a458053.jpg"></noscript>
Whatever the event, each lady ought to have a cross-body in her bags collection. They function admirably for a date or a night out with friends. They are just the correct size to carry just what one needs to touch up or get into the clubs. Utilize the strap to make it super easy to move around and pick something that is fun with little stylish details that turn heads.</p>

<h4>6.  Evening Bag:</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674533-163bd0b8-97f3-11e8-868d-37bf1afe50ff.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674533-163bd0b8-97f3-11e8-868d-37bf1afe50ff.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674533-163bd0b8-97f3-11e8-868d-37bf1afe50ff.jpg"></noscript>
Regardless of whether a mini strap bag or clutch, each young lady ought to have a beautiful evening bag that will be ideal for the most upscale of gatherings. While black is reliably the best choice, the most imperative thought is to discover a style that has subtle appeal, similar to a quilted style or satin finish bag.</p>

<h4>7.  The Bucket Bag:</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674588-0a0a610a-97f4-11e8-98cd-717a62e2bb77.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674588-0a0a610a-97f4-11e8-98cd-717a62e2bb77.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674588-0a0a610a-97f4-11e8-98cd-717a62e2bb77.jpg"></noscript>
These bags are exquisite and modern in one solid color and without a lot of detail. Ideal for working ladies who need big bags to carry lots of stuff and who have to attend corporate parties all the time.</p>

<p>Each of the above-mentioned bags is exclusive in their own way and is a must-have for the closet of a fashionable woman.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Best Weekend Trips You Can Explore From Delhi]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/04/5-best-weekend-trips-you-can-explore-from-delhi/"/>
    <updated>2018-08-04T14:24:51+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/04/5-best-weekend-trips-you-can-explore-from-delhi</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674470-066fd5f4-97f2-11e8-81c7-87990c913a62.jpg" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674470-066fd5f4-97f2-11e8-81c7-87990c913a62.jpg" width="400" height="500" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674470-066fd5f4-97f2-11e8-81c7-87990c913a62.jpg"></noscript>
Are you exhausted with everyday life in Delhi and need to go somewhere nearby, in the upcoming weekend?
Going on weekend getaways is a growing trend in urban cities. These short weekend trips are the ideal way to explore destinations in and around your city and come back rejuvenated. Luckily Delhi, the capital city of India has many beautiful destinations nearby. Plan a weekend trip to the below-mentioned places and enjoy getaways near Delhi to energize yourself.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>1.  Agra</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674466-f94692aa-97f1-11e8-812b-11765c81cbb9.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674466-f94692aa-97f1-11e8-812b-11765c81cbb9.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674466-f94692aa-97f1-11e8-812b-11765c81cbb9.jpg"></noscript>
The wonder Taj Mahal is situated here and its close proximity to Delhi (distance 200 km) makes it a preferable weekend destination for Delhiites. Agra Fort, the fort made of red stone on the bank of the Yamuna is another amazing spot. Other touristic spots include Jama Masjid, Samadhi Swamiji Maharaj Bagh, Mehtab Bagh, Chini-Ka-Rauza, Itimad-Ud-Daulah, Taj Nature Park, and the Museum. Famous spots to shop in Agra are - Khadi Gramodyog and Subhash emporium. Agra has numerous eating spots to tempt your taste buds and there are various stay choices accessible to suit any budget.</p>

<h4>2.  Jaipur</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674469-063cc542-97f2-11e8-9a40-e89c7426ed8a.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674469-063cc542-97f2-11e8-9a40-e89c7426ed8a.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674469-063cc542-97f2-11e8-9a40-e89c7426ed8a.jpg"></noscript>
Jaipur is one of the best tourist destinations for sightseeing, shopping and relishing Rajasthani food and culture. The renowned touring places in Jaipur are mostly its huge forts - Jaigarh, Nahargarh and Amber. Other tourist spots to see are the Jantar Mantar Observatory, Hawa Mahal, City Palace and Galta Monkey Temple. One must also enjoy shopping and food here. If your budget permits, do stay in one of the heritage hotels, it will make your trip way more unforgettable.</p>

<h4>3.  Rishikesh</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674471-06b2fb7c-97f2-11e8-8b27-0ba91359a4c5.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674471-06b2fb7c-97f2-11e8-8b27-0ba91359a4c5.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674471-06b2fb7c-97f2-11e8-8b27-0ba91359a4c5.jpg"></noscript>
An adventure hub not very far from Delhi, Rishikesh is famous for its camping and water rafting activities. It is a most loved place for adventure lovers. This culturally rich place is additionally incredible for trekking. Rishikesh is just perfect to drench yourself in yoga and spirituality with various yoga centers offering short and long-term courses. Other touristic spots in Rishikesh are Neelkantha Mahadev Temple, Swarg Ashram, Neer Garh Waterfall and Maharishi Mahesh Yogi Ashram.</p>

<h4>4.  Corbett National Park</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674468-060707b8-97f2-11e8-895d-fcc3541867e5.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674468-060707b8-97f2-11e8-895d-fcc3541867e5.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674468-060707b8-97f2-11e8-895d-fcc3541867e5.jpg"></noscript>
The celebrated reserve is an incredible destination to immerse yourself in nature through forest safaris and in case you&rsquo;re fortunate you may see a tiger as well! The park has observation towers overlooking water holes which you can climb to watch the wildlife unobtrusively. You can take a safari in a gypsy or even go for an elephant safari.</p>

<h4>5.  Mussoorie</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674470-066fd5f4-97f2-11e8-81c7-87990c913a62.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674470-066fd5f4-97f2-11e8-81c7-87990c913a62.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674470-066fd5f4-97f2-11e8-81c7-87990c913a62.jpg"></noscript>
The most ideal way to beat the sweltering Delhi heat is to run to the hills for the weekend and Mussoorie is the best weekend escape. Delhi people mostly go to Mussoorie during April to June to beat the heat and during Dec to Jan enjoy snowfall. Mussoorie is situated at a height of 2000 meters above ocean level. This quaint place allows you to rejuvenate yourself in the lap of natural beauty.</p>

<p>Explore these destinations close to Delhi during the short span of a weekend and experience a world of charm and natural beauty.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Junk Food Addas in Delhi]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/04/best-junk-food-addas-in-delhi/"/>
    <updated>2018-08-04T14:05:17+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/04/best-junk-food-addas-in-delhi</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674370-b06bc862-97f0-11e8-94a6-75987ee8d361.png" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674370-b06bc862-97f0-11e8-94a6-75987ee8d361.png" width="400" height="500" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674370-b06bc862-97f0-11e8-94a6-75987ee8d361.png"></noscript>
Delhi offers all the magnificent opportunities for you to relish the many delicious nuances of junk food. There is always good food in Delhi. People of Delhi love to eat, filling up their appetites with the best tasting and affordable food to satisfy their junk food craving. In a city like Delhi, there are sure to be different &ldquo;favorites.&rdquo; So here are some the best junk food addas that you can check out.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>1.  Kent’s, Defence Colony Market</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674329-de711358-97ef-11e8-827d-9e13008ffce5.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674329-de711358-97ef-11e8-827d-9e13008ffce5.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674329-de711358-97ef-11e8-827d-9e13008ffce5.jpg"></noscript>
There is no other place which makes chicken and mutton burgers like Kent’s. Located in the Defence Colony Market, this place deserves a visit if you are nearby. Smell the tempting aroma and eat their delicious food to satisfy your hunger. You are guaranteed to be served with freshly prepared food. If you are in the mood to have fast food, this is the place you must visit.</p>

<h4>2.  Indian Coffee House, Connaught Place</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674326-ddff4a2a-97ef-11e8-9a68-e8bd00d0f012.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674326-ddff4a2a-97ef-11e8-9a68-e8bd00d0f012.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674326-ddff4a2a-97ef-11e8-9a68-e8bd00d0f012.jpg"></noscript>
There are nearly 400 Indian Coffee House across India. This place is one the favorite quaint place that Delhiites loves to visit. Serving a variety of cuisines and fast food, it would take a lifetime to taste them all! Whatever cuisines you may like from that, you can get them prepared for you. Everything is cooked to perfection with the perfect taste to it.</p>

<h4>3.  Bille Di Hatti, Kamla Nagar</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674325-ddb55140-97ef-11e8-9066-e8fe5f1a8bd2.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674325-ddb55140-97ef-11e8-9066-e8fe5f1a8bd2.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674325-ddb55140-97ef-11e8-9066-e8fe5f1a8bd2.jpg"></noscript>
Bille Di Hatti is a fast food joint in the North Campus and it is popular among students for its lip-smacking food. Highly sought out dishes include chole bhature and lassis. For its taste that you may expect in fancy food places, this place is very affordable.</p>

<h4>4.  The Rolling Joint, Connaught Place</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674331-dee6783c-97ef-11e8-9219-b55c2fb0f108.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674331-dee6783c-97ef-11e8-9219-b55c2fb0f108.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674331-dee6783c-97ef-11e8-9219-b55c2fb0f108.jpg"></noscript>
This easily becomes a hangout for office workers in Connaught Place who are craving junk food during lunchtime. If you want to experience rolls like you have never before, this is the place to go to.</p>

<h4>5.  Laxman Fast Food, Qutub Institutional Area</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674330-deab2930-97ef-11e8-90da-4541ec49544e.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674330-deab2930-97ef-11e8-90da-4541ec49544e.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674330-deab2930-97ef-11e8-90da-4541ec49544e.jpg"></noscript>
Youngsters love this fast food place, situated at Qutub Institutional Area. The greater part of Laxman Dhaba&rsquo;s customers are students who love this place for its affordable yet tasty delicacies and also its lush green surroundings. This place serves an exciting variety of paranthas. Now, you have a new place to go to for your parantha cravings.</p>

<h4>6.  Kennedy’s, West Patel Nagar</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674328-de37d958-97ef-11e8-8585-6addaeff45a2.jpg" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674328-de37d958-97ef-11e8-8585-6addaeff45a2.jpg" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674328-de37d958-97ef-11e8-8585-6addaeff45a2.jpg"></noscript>
Located in West Patel Nagar, this is the place to be if you want to relish Chilly Chicken Burger, Hakka Noodles, and Butter Chicken Pasta. This is a place where you may want to bring the rest of your family and friends, and enjoy the experience.</p>

<h4>7.  Big Yellow Door (BYD), Satya Niketan Market</h4>

<p><img class="center lazy" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674370-b06bc862-97f0-11e8-94a6-75987ee8d361.png" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center" data-original="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674370-b06bc862-97f0-11e8-94a6-75987ee8d361.png" width="500" height="600" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43674370-b06bc862-97f0-11e8-94a6-75987ee8d361.png"></noscript>
It has to be included here. Located in Satya Niketan Market, it is a fast food place that offers delicious meals. This place mainly offers cheese fries, salads, chicken pizza and a variety of milkshakes. You will savor the most flavorful fast food here.</p>

<p>These are just some places that you can visit; there are so many other places to go. This is just enough to hopefully whet your appetite.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
