<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Latest Posts Onplaces | JunkJam | Fashion! LifeStyle! Market! Travel!]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/categories/places/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2020-05-30T00:18:40+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reasons-Why Delhi Is Best City in India??]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/02/20/reasons-why-Delhi-is-Best-Place-to-live/"/>
    <updated>2016-02-20T13:18:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/02/20/reasons-why-Delhi-is-Best-Place-to-live</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Delhi or Dilli, also famous as &lsquo;Dilwalo ki Dilli&rsquo; is the capital city of India and is usually known for its rich cultural heritage and lifestyle.</p>

<!-- more -->


<ol>
<li><p>A City Foodies will always Adore:</p>

<p>From Rabri Faludas at Giani to Dossa-Sambhar to Dhokala, Bada Paw, Paw-Bhaji, from Nehari, Biryanis, Nalla to tandoori chicken, butter chicken, biryani, sheek and shami kababs, from chhole bhature, chaat, aloo tikki, papri,
bhel-puri, gol-gappe to rosgullas,Delhi has all to delight the foodies.
Foods of Delhi cannot be complete without the mention of paranthasof Paranthewali Gali and the Chaat Corner in the Chandni Chowk.
Other than these Delhi has many restaurants that serve authentic Thai, Lebanese, Chinese, Israeli, Italian, Indonesian, Spanish, Mexican, French, Moroccan and Swiss cuisine.</p>

<p>Delhi is a paradise for food lovers. It preserves age-old eateries to glitzy restaurants offering Indian and International Cuisines to suit varied budgets.</p></li>
<li><p>Shopping Hub Of India:</p>

<p>From the Top Knotch Brand to Best price Branded stuffs at Streets;Shopping in Delhi is always happening.Be it, Indian crafts at Delhi government’s emporiums, or brand new malls, markets are flooded with goods.
Bargaining at Janpath or Sarojni Nagar, for college goers to exclusive designer stores at Khan Market, this is one good reason to settle in the city.
From Your Wedding shopping at Chandni Chowk, trendy and fashionable stuffs at Greater kailash and branded Surplus at Sarojini Nagar Market you will get every stuffs here..:)</p></li>
<li><p>Delhi Metro- Heart Line Of Delhi:</p>

<p>Cheap, comfortable, clean, fast mode of transport. This is Delhi’s lifeline. It has become the safest mode of traveling for women unlike the world upstairs.
More than 15 lakh passengers travel from delhi metro everyday.</p></li>
<li><p>Education Hub of India:</p>

<p>Delhi University, IIT, AIIMS, Jamia Millia Islamia, Delhi Technological University, GGSIPU and all other premier institutions are in Delhi.
Over 20,000  Coachings Classes for IAS,IES,Law,Engineering,Medical aspirant is running in Delhi&amp; every Year lakhs of Aspirant get their goal
With almost 6000 schools in the city, it makes the best place to live in for good education.</p></li>
<li><p>No one can stay Jobless here:</p>

<p>NCR (National capital region)  which includes Baghpat, Gurgaon, Sonepat, Faridabad, Ghaziabad, Noida, Greater Noida are the urbanized and modern settlements. Noida is a major hub for multinational firms outsourcing IT services.</p>

<p>Today, Gurgaon is home to about 250 Fortune 500 companies.</p></li>
</ol>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
