<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Latest Posts on Lifestyle | JunkJam Blog - Street Market! Fashion! LifeStyle!]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/categories/lifestyle/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2016-10-01T22:44:25+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Movies Related to Womens Issues Everyone Should Watch at Least Once]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/26/top-10-movies-related-to-womens-issues-everyone-should-watch-at-least-once/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-26T12:29:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/26/top-10-movies-related-to-womens-issues-everyone-should-watch-at-least-once</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015068/5707e8d8-881a-11e6-9af6-6ca86c160dd6.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015068/5707e8d8-881a-11e6-9af6-6ca86c160dd6.jpg</a>" width="600" height="500">
It all began with eve teasing, slowly took the form of molestation, and finally turned into brutal rape. There is no denying the fact that the issues related to women have increased to great extent now days. Even though, there have arrived various laws and norms for the safety of females in our country but still the number of such issues has not gone down, in fact, these have increased in the past few years.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>No matter, how much this menace keeps on rising, there are still such people in the society who will keep on attempting to do things that create awareness in the minds of people regarding the safety of women. One such awareness is created in the minds of public through empowering movies related to women’s issues. So, we picked some great ones and brought a list for you:</p>

<h1>Arth</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015062/5699e590-881a-11e6-953a-b870094f3719.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015062/5699e590-881a-11e6-953a-b870094f3719.jpg</a>">
This movie is based on the internal struggle of two women who make a man pivot of their existence. One women rejects every male in order to lead a single and independent life and the other one ditches the man after self-introspection. At the end, women are portrayed as winners.</p>

<h1>Aastha: In the prison of spring</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015061/565c2d68-881a-11e6-9ba7-af8d36328d6f.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015061/565c2d68-881a-11e6-9ba7-af8d36328d6f.jpg</a>">
This movie pictured the female protagonist to another realm where a bored house wife turns into a prostitute at night and fulfills the chasm of materialistic needs of life. It was directed by Basu Bhattacharya in 1997.</p>

<h1>Lajja</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015065/56d46206-881a-11e6-9977-531ffcba500c.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015065/56d46206-881a-11e6-9977-531ffcba500c.jpg</a>">
Filmed in the year 2001, Lajja is another female centric movie that depicts a land where women worshipped as shakti are humiliated and killed just because they are females. Directed by Rajkumar Santoshi, it highlights societal malpractices.</p>

<h1>The Dirty Picture</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015070/57376f2c-881a-11e6-8100-a44d2e945470.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015070/57376f2c-881a-11e6-8100-a44d2e945470.jpg</a>">
This movie characterizes Vidya as southern siren Silk Smitha, a woman who was not ashamed of her physique, instead, she flaunts it, without caring about the repressed sexuality. She shone like a star and was hailed as a female hero.</p>

<h1>Kahaani</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015148/3a1cb3dc-881c-11e6-95dd-d06eb627cbff.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015148/3a1cb3dc-881c-11e6-95dd-d06eb627cbff.jpg</a>">
Cinematographed in 2012, Kahaani shows another amazing performance by Vidya Balan. The plot of the movie showcased the inner reserves of a woman’s power. Despite of being pregnant, she goes on her mission and completes it with vigor and zeal.</p>

<h1>Jazbaa</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015063/56c29828-881a-11e6-966f-f6578f858a55.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015063/56c29828-881a-11e6-966f-f6578f858a55.jpg</a>">
Jazbaa is another women centric movie that stars Aishwarya Rai Bacchan, an attorney forced to defend a criminal after her daughter was kidnapped.</p>

<h1>Sarabjit</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015069/5712efbc-881a-11e6-9f4b-7ff5a440d54d.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015069/5712efbc-881a-11e6-9f4b-7ff5a440d54d.jpg</a>">
This movie also pictures Aishwarya Rai Bacchan in the role of Dalbir Kaur who falls a prey to an abusive husband. She leaves him and starts living with her brother’s family, working as an independent woman.</p>

<h1>Neerja</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015149/3a5a415c-881c-11e6-83af-3cd9e6fc478e.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015149/3a5a415c-881c-11e6-83af-3cd9e6fc478e.jpg</a>">
In Neerja, Sonam Kapoor played the role of the courageous flight attendant who had to lose her life in order to save the highjacked plane from terrorists.</p>

<h1>Piku</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015067/56fd8ece-881a-11e6-9695-2f7342e143b2.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015067/56fd8ece-881a-11e6-9695-2f7342e143b2.jpg</a>">
Piku is a light and humorous film showing Deepika Padukone as an independent single lady who has to give up on her dreams and desires in order to take care of her old father.</p>

<h1>Pink</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015068/5707e8d8-881a-11e6-9af6-6ca86c160dd6.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19015068/5707e8d8-881a-11e6-9af6-6ca86c160dd6.jpg</a>">
It is an Indian Courtroom Drama that conveys that women should have the liberty to walk and speak freely at night.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Questions Every Guy Wants to Ask His Girl]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/25/7-questions-every-guy-wants-to-ask-his-girl/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-25T12:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/25/7-questions-every-guy-wants-to-ask-his-girl</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813009/3000fbb2-8306-11e6-873d-4fdec1d7d180.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813009/3000fbb2-8306-11e6-873d-4fdec1d7d180.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500">
Every guy is curious about his girl. Apart from the fact, that he loves her so much, there still some ‘questions that he certainly thinks of asking to her. Here we have a list of interrogations that a guy would like to have with his girl:</p>

<!-- more -->


<p><br/><br/><br/><br/></p>

<h1>Why do you spend so much time on makeup?</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813011/300899ee-8306-11e6-88a2-16ea09db0b3e.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813011/300899ee-8306-11e6-88a2-16ea09db0b3e.jpg</a>" width="600" height="500">
Often, most of the girls are seen with little or too much makeup on. There is hardly any girl who does not likes to put on makeup in order to look good. So, this can be one of the questions that a guy would probably want to ask her girl that why does she spend so much time on doing makeup. And the answer would be because the girls like the way they look in it. Also, it is fun to wear makeup.</p>

<h1>How frequently do you talk bad about your friends?</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813008/2fee873e-8306-11e6-8ee1-2aa132311b0a.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813008/2fee873e-8306-11e6-8ee1-2aa132311b0a.jpg</a>">
There is a difference between gossiping about someone and talking bad about them. Gossip can be harmless but talking bad can be something serious. So, another question that a guy would like to ask his girl is that does she talk bad about her friends. To be frank, the ones whom one calls her friend, she can never talk bad about him or her.</p>

<h1>Do you watch porn? If yes, how often?</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813009/3000fbb2-8306-11e6-873d-4fdec1d7d180.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813009/3000fbb2-8306-11e6-873d-4fdec1d7d180.jpg</a>">
This one got to be another question that would interest a guy. He might want to ask this to her girlfriend if she also enjoys watching porn and how often does she watches them. well, the answer can be most of them don’t even like to think of doing this. This is because girls are more of mental than visual. They believe in imagination and storyline, so watching such poorly acted video might not be their thing.</p>

<h1>Why do you take so much time while taking a shower?</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813012/300bd708-8306-11e6-8ce2-593994244b55.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813012/300bd708-8306-11e6-8ce2-593994244b55.jpg</a>">
It is found that many girls take a lot of time in bathing. So, the guy is always inquisitive to know that what makes his girl also spend so much time in bathing.</p>

<h1>What would you say about No shave November?</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19012722/24349d3c-87db-11e6-8feb-199618ef89e7.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19012722/24349d3c-87db-11e6-8feb-199618ef89e7.jpg</a>">
There is no denying the fact that girls also need to shave certain areas of their body, where it is inevitable. But like the boys it is very common that girls feel lazy about this too. So, this one would definitely make a guy pose a question on her girly.</p>

<h1>What habit/habits do you hate in your guy?</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813010/30039124-8306-11e6-8adc-0859f99f37ae.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813010/30039124-8306-11e6-8adc-0859f99f37ae.jpg</a>">
Well, this one would be a beneficial question for every guy. If they dare to ask the bad habits in them that their girl hates and wants them to change, it would somewhere do good to them as well as their relationship, provided that the girl answers honestly.</p>

<h1>Do you like to check out other guys just for an eye candy?</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19012723/249edd32-87db-11e6-94a2-917ac0edaf9d.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19012723/249edd32-87db-11e6-94a2-917ac0edaf9d.jpg</a>">
Yet another question that every guy would rush on is that how often do their girlfriend checks out other guys for providing an eye candy to themselves.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do You Love Her or Just a Crush Find It Out Here]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/25/do-you-love-her-or-just-a-crush-find-it-out-here/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-25T12:29:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/25/do-you-love-her-or-just-a-crush-find-it-out-here</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813044/82b6d6a0-8307-11e6-9a62-386a7c5b5470.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813044/82b6d6a0-8307-11e6-9a62-386a7c5b5470.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500">
Getting confused between liking someone and loving her is a very normal thing. Most of the guys take years to realize that they love a girl or it is just a cute little crush that they have on them. In fact, many a times it happens so that even after coming into a relationship, they are confused about whether they love her or they just have a crush on her. To clear this confusion a little bit, here is a small attempt that would make you realize the difference between love and crush:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Temporary feeling:</h1>

<p>Crush is temporary feeling. It is nothing but attraction. If you have a crush on a girl, you will only have such a feeling when the girl is around you. When she is not around, you would not feel anything like attraction but in case of love, you will their presence in every moment of your life.</p>

<h1>Priority</h1>

<p>When you love someone, she would be your priority and you would value her more than yourselves. Sometimes, you would even do anything or go anywhere for her, without even giving a second thought to it but in case of crush, you would not have that much of guts to do ‘anything’ for her. Somewhere, you will resist taking the risk.</p>

<h1>On your mind, all the time</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813077/6988c584-8308-11e6-9670-9cf2b13c6603.png">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813077/6988c584-8308-11e6-9670-9cf2b13c6603.png</a>">
You will like your life to be filled with her memories, when you love a girl. Perhaps, you would feel her right, even if she is wrong at some point. Her behavior would not change even an inch of your love for her. Also, you would remember each and every moment you spend or spent with her but in case of crush, you would only start to think of her when someone talks about her to you or she appears in front of you.</p>

<h1>Their happiness makes you happy</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813075/69758de8-8308-11e6-857b-d1ca929128da.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813075/69758de8-8308-11e6-857b-d1ca929128da.jpg</a>">
When you love a girl, her happiness would make you happier than yours  but if it is just a mere crush, you would feel happy for them but prioritize your happiness.</p>

<h1>Hard to forget</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813076/697b1420-8308-11e6-8abb-ad4d6b607cbb.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18813076/697b1420-8308-11e6-8abb-ad4d6b607cbb.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600">
If you truly love her, it would be hard to forget her after she is gone. You might take her out of your life but you can never take her out of your mind as well as heart. You will feel her in everyone you come across but crush fades away with the passage of time and as the person moves away from your life.</p>

<h1>What she feels, bothers you</h1>

<p>When you are in love with a girl, you are affected by what she likes or dislikes, what are her desires, or what interests her the most. All these things would keep on rolling in your mind even if she has left you. On the contrary, when you have a crush on a girl, you would attempt to know her likes and dislikes and what other feelings she has but that would be for a short period of time. The moment you stop receiving a response since long, it would hardly bother you.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Issues Faced by Youth Today]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/24/5-issues-faced-by-youth-today/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-24T12:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/24/5-issues-faced-by-youth-today</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806702/1383d1da-8252-11e6-9496-1494d04dfaf1.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806702/1383d1da-8252-11e6-9496-1494d04dfaf1.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500">
In the modern scenario, the serious issues and concerns related to kids are coming to light slowly and gradually and now that we have entered this new era, the society also has begun to recognize them. not only are they coming to the notice, but also, a need to find solution to these is arising. So, to familiarize a person with these, we are listing a few here:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Obesity</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806695/d139813a-8251-11e6-8b4c-29e68ff9c41f.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806695/d139813a-8251-11e6-8b4c-29e68ff9c41f.jpg</a>">
A very common thing to hear but can be a serious concern, if we ponder upon deeply. The kids belonging to today’s generation are gaining weight and getting fatter and fatter day by day and mind it- there is a difference between chubby and obese. It can be said that it is an aftermath of social media and that the modern gadgets have made humans a slave to technology. Kids spend hours and hours sitting in front of television or a computer instead of indulging themselves in outdoor activities. As a result, they are gaining more of weight. The quote- ‘All work no play, makes Jack a dull boy’ fits perfectly to them. Ultimately, this leads to acute disorders like depression, lowered self-esteemed, self-confidence going null, and so on. Also, other maladies like fluctuations in blood pressure and diabetes are two of the consequences.</p>

<h1>Unemployment</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806697/0152688c-8252-11e6-9621-eb42310db0aa.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806697/0152688c-8252-11e6-9621-eb42310db0aa.jpg</a>">
It is a well-known fact that a developing country faces too much of employment problem. The present youth is capable enough and also possesses the right qualification but there is a lack of employment opportunities in the country. This renders them jobless, doing nothing, which then leads to catastrophic results like suicide or taking some other dangerous step.</p>

<h1>Relationships</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806702/1383d1da-8252-11e6-9496-1494d04dfaf1.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806702/1383d1da-8252-11e6-9496-1494d04dfaf1.jpg</a>">
One of the major issues faced by 90 percent of youngsters today is failure in love relationships. As per Maslow’s Need Hierarchy Theory, love or belongingness is one of our needs that holds priority in life. But, looking at today’s youth, it seems like there whole world revolves around the person they fall in love with. If they find themselves stuck in a relationship where there is lack of love or respect or due to any other reason, it fails; they end up harming themselves or taking a disastrous action.</p>

<h1>Poverty</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806710/501cb7c4-8252-11e6-8abd-5351e2df9d17.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806710/501cb7c4-8252-11e6-8abd-5351e2df9d17.jpg</a>">
Poverty can be considered yet another element that profoundly effects the youth as well as their psychology today. The division of families based on income creates disparity among people and the kids have to live in poverty. Just because their parents cannot earn sufficient amount of money, the little ones are also deprived of government assistance. As a result their childhood goes dingy and their future bleak.</p>

<h1>Alcohol/Drug addiction</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806701/1381cb88-8252-11e6-9bc3-5ea2f381af58.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18806701/1381cb88-8252-11e6-9bc3-5ea2f381af58.gif</a>">
Drugs and alcohol are being consumed like candies and beverages in today’s world and the most addicted ones to these are the youngsters of today. Not only boys, but also young girls can be found with a cigarette or a packet of cocaine in their hands. In addition, the modern trends like hookah parlors and going out for clubbing are kindling the fire.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Take Care of Your Skin Before Wedding]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/15/how-to-take-care-of-your-skin-before-wedding/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-15T12:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/15/how-to-take-care-of-your-skin-before-wedding</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18655783/4fb1ccf8-7f09-11e6-9548-e2f3978fe741.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18655783/4fb1ccf8-7f09-11e6-9548-e2f3978fe741.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500">
When everything on your big day is so perfect and flawless, how can your skin stay far behind? When it comes make your skin ready for your special day, it must not be taken for granted but yes, do not take too much of stress as it can lead to unwanted and catastrophic results for your skin. To help you with this further, here we have some tips as to how you can get that perfect and radiant skin for your wedding:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Say no to new skin products</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18655781/4f711c3a-7f09-11e6-8ecb-9365c470bb8e.JPG">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18655781/4f711c3a-7f09-11e6-8ecb-9365c470bb8e.JPG</a>">
Do not even think of trying any new products at least up to three weeks before your wedding and these products include skin care, make-up, hair care, and yes, even washing powder. In case an kind of skin reaction takes place, it can take a long time to calm down, which, I think none of the girls can afford before her wedding day.</p>

<h1>Do not leave it like a last minute decision</h1>

<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18655782/4fb17a82-7f09-11e6-9c13-3a666297811e.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18655782/4fb17a82-7f09-11e6-9c13-3a666297811e.jpg</a>">
The earlier you figure out the skin issues and decide to start working on them, the better would it be for you. In addition, using the products that exfoliate your skin would be a great help in getting rid of the dead skin cells. When the dead cells are removed, your skin would look fresh and the color complexion of your skin would be enhanced manifolds. Also, do not forget to use a good SPF to avoid damaged skin due to exposure to sun.</p>

<h1>Green tea, your best friend</h1>

<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18655783/4fb1ccf8-7f09-11e6-9548-e2f3978fe741.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18655783/4fb1ccf8-7f09-11e6-9548-e2f3978fe741.jpg</a>">
Green tea has as many benefits as you want to count. It has always been beneficial to drink green tea. Not only can this help with weight loss but also its anti-oxidant properties help reduce acne and brighten the skin.</p>

<h1>Drink plenty of water</h1>

<p>Water is undoubtedly a wonder liquid. The more water intake you do, the more benefits you are going to get. It is believed that drinking more and more water brings glow on your face. Medically, acne and pimple are caused as a result of stomach disorders, so, drinking more of water, help heal stomach problems and consequently give a bright and beautiful skin. Water also pinkens your lips.</p>

<h1>Eat lot of fruits</h1>

<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18655784/5009e23a-7f09-11e6-8a88-09891b2e754d.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18655784/5009e23a-7f09-11e6-8a88-09891b2e754d.jpg</a>">
The essential nutrients in fruits like papaya, cucumber, tomato are said to bring a kind of flamboyant glow to your skin. So, as and when your big day is near, start feeding yourself with a whole meal of fruits and let your skin have the complete food. Also, it helps your body gain vital minerals as well as vitamins that would keep you happy and energetic throughout the month.</p>

<p>So girls, not to worry! We have got a solution to all your wedding related issues. Just keep following the aforesaid steps with dedication and this would definitely pave way for a clear and glowing skin that would make your better half a complete fan of yours. Stay happy, stay petty, coz happy girls are the prettiest!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
