<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Latest Posts on Mumbai | JunkJam Blog - Street Market! Fashion! LifeStyle!]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/categories/mumbai/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2017-01-29T13:56:48+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2 Best Places to Go Street Shopping in Mumbai]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/19/2-best-places-to-go-street-shopping-in-mumbai/"/>
    <updated>2016-07-19T23:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/19/2-best-places-to-go-street-shopping-in-mumbai</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16958979/837dee66-4e00-11e6-970a-fda168654bf9.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16958979/837dee66-4e00-11e6-970a-fda168654bf9.jpg</a>" width="500" height="650" title="Street Market Mumbai" >
Mumbai is the City of Dreams for many and certainly a shopper’s delight. Where there are hub of designer shops ranging from Gucci, Louis Vuitton, Burberry to Versache , there are also lot of street markets in Mumbai where you can shop at the cheapest rates. These street markets are very crowded as one can find variety of items here, ranging from first copy of branded clothes, vintage items, Chinese gadgets, books and finger licking street food. Mumbai Street markets are a blessing for all the college going girls as well as the struggling actresses who don’t have much money to buy branded dresses for their photo shoots or celebrity parties. Here I am listing 2 Best Places to Go Street Shopping in Mumbai</p>

<!-- more -->


<p><img class="<a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16959160/458c7db0-4e01-11e6-88ae-27ad32a0b177.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16959160/458c7db0-4e01-11e6-88ae-27ad32a0b177.jpg</a>"></p>

<h1>Colaba Causeway</h1>

<p>Located in the area of Southern Mumbai, Colaba Causeway is one of the best street markets in Mumbai. This market is a huge one which stretches over several meters and offers all kind of items. You name the item and you can find it here in this market, from artificial jewellery, handicrafts, leather items, sunglasses, stoles and scarves, antique items, books , fashionable clothes, books, bags, bangles to juttis. If you are looking for any personalized gift for a friend then you can also find vendors who can write messages on a single rice grain and engrave it into a locket or key chain. Even if the prices seem to be very reasonable but still you can bargain to a great extent and save your valuable money. Here you will not only find the local people of Mumbai but also foreigners shopping, as this market is only a few kilometers away from Taj Hotel and other iconic landmarks like Gateway of India. If you want to watch a movie then you can also go to one of the oldest Theatre, Regal Cinema, which is located near the market.
<img class="<a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16958980/840beffe-4e00-11e6-9476-f153a98d8c1d.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16958980/840beffe-4e00-11e6-9476-f153a98d8c1d.jpg</a>">
<img class="right <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16958978/836996aa-4e00-11e6-9c7d-0592edcaa868.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16958978/836996aa-4e00-11e6-9c7d-0592edcaa868.jpg</a>"></p>

<h1>Fashion Street</h1>

<p>Another amazing shopping area in Mumbai is the famous Fashion Street, which perfectly fits its name. Here, you will find all the latest fashion clothes, accessories, cosmetics, and much more at affordable prices. These also include first copies of popular brands. Situated in South Mumbai, this street is a cluster of about 385 street side clothing shops placed on MG Road near Azad Maidan, opposite to Bombay Gymkhana. Along with being a favorite shopping street of the locals as well as the visitors, it is also a popular tourist destination located opposite to VSNL office building at MG Road. As we know, the more you bargain, the better price you fetch for particular apparel, so another advantage of shopping here is that it is well known for bargaining. Not only this, but in order to show concern for environment, in January 2011, as a part of green drive of BMC in collaboration with Fashion Street Shop Owners’ Association, the market at Fashion Street banned the use of plastic bags and polybags, and started using paper bags, made by the training workshop of the National Association of the Blind.
<img class="<a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16959165/4bab41f4-4e01-11e6-9d83-407c45e521c5.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16959165/4bab41f4-4e01-11e6-9d83-407c45e521c5.jpg</a>">
<img class="<a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16959161/47682a26-4e01-11e6-8515-23d94f37e41f.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16959161/47682a26-4e01-11e6-8515-23d94f37e41f.jpg</a>"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
