<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Latest Posts Onlajpat | JunkJam Blog - Street Market! Fashion! LifeStyle!]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/categories/lajpat/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2018-08-04T14:45:04+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lajpat Nagar Market]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/05/24/lajpat-nagar-market-new-delhi/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-24T08:00:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/05/24/lajpat-nagar-market-new-delhi</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490335/acd92a9e-2184-11e6-9545-6b028dba05ba.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490335/acd92a9e-2184-11e6-9545-6b028dba05ba.jpg</a>" width="500" height="650" title="Lajpat Nagar Market" /><noscript><img class="left <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490335/acd92a9e-2184-11e6-9545-6b028dba05ba.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490335/acd92a9e-2184-11e6-9545-6b028dba05ba.jpg</a>" width="500" height="650" title="Lajpat Nagar Market" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490335/acd92a9e-2184-11e6-9545-6b028dba05ba.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490335/acd92a9e-2184-11e6-9545-6b028dba05ba.jpg</a>"></noscript>
Among the important shopping areas of Delhi, Lajpat Nagar enjoys a prestigious position because of its locational advantage. A large number of people from all directions of Delhi City come for shopping at Lajpat Nagar, which offers good shopping opportunities and entertainment.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Lajpat Nagar is named after the freedom fighter, Lala Lajpat Rai, known as Punjab Kesari or Lion of Punjab. It is now divided into four parts. Lajpat Nagar I has car accessories and clothing stores, Lajpat Nagar II has the Central Market, local restaurants and home décor units, Lajpat Nagar III has the TDI Mall which houses the 3Cs Cineplex, and food outlets like Sagar Ratna, Chopsticks Express, McDonalds, The Street Foods of India and The Bakers Street while Lajpat Nagar IV, which houses the Amar Colony has a huge ladies.
<img class="<a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490225/ed1d5496-2183-11e6-9da2-631446d7423f.png">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490225/ed1d5496-2183-11e6-9da2-631446d7423f.png</a>" width="700" height="400"/><noscript><img class="<a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490225/ed1d5496-2183-11e6-9da2-631446d7423f.png">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490225/ed1d5496-2183-11e6-9da2-631446d7423f.png</a>" width="700" height="400" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490225/ed1d5496-2183-11e6-9da2-631446d7423f.png">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490225/ed1d5496-2183-11e6-9da2-631446d7423f.png</a>"></noscript></p>

<p>There is plenty to choose from in terms of bed linen, curtains, table cloth, bath mats, shower curtains and a number of other furnishings that bring warmth to a home. Just land up here and look around to find unique gifts for loved ones, dry fruits, tailors who will alter, stitch and dye clothes, stationery for the kids and so on. Unless there is a fixed price sign prominently displayed in the shop, you should surely bargain for better prices and deals everywhere.</p>

<p>There is a rich variety of cheaply priced curios sold on the streets as well. For instance, old and used wine and perfume bottles in the most interesting colors and shapes; ceramic pots and urns; plastic flowers and beaded curtains… it is purchase of such things in an unplanned, impulsive shopping spree that can either brighten up your day or fill your shopping bags with clutter. So be alert and use your discretion.</p>

<h1>How to Reach the Market:</h1>

<p><img class="<a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490229/f269dc30-2183-11e6-96b5-db26f2d50e5d.png">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490229/f269dc30-2183-11e6-96b5-db26f2d50e5d.png</a>" width="700" height="400"/><noscript><img class="<a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490229/f269dc30-2183-11e6-96b5-db26f2d50e5d.png">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490229/f269dc30-2183-11e6-96b5-db26f2d50e5d.png</a>" width="700" height="400" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490229/f269dc30-2183-11e6-96b5-db26f2d50e5d.png">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490229/f269dc30-2183-11e6-96b5-db26f2d50e5d.png</a>"></noscript></p>

<p>There is no problem that how to reach Lajpat Nagar their is the bus service of Delhi Transport Corporation as well as the Delhi Mass Rapid Transit System has provided very well connection to Lajpat Nagar. East Delhi Anand Vihar and Lajpat Nagar are connected by Route no. 543, Lajpat Nagar and North (Rohini) and West Delhi Punjabi Bagh is connected by Teevr Mudrika. The Delhi Metro Station named Lajpat Nagar is the elevated metro station that is on violet line of Metro that is being situated between Moolchand and Jangpura stations. This station was the first violet line station that was opened for public. So how to reach Lajpat Nagar is not a big issue now. Another famous place of south Delhi is Kalkaji that is situated near by Lajpat Nagar. The Delhi Metro is available from the Kalka Mandir metro station  for the visitors to reach Lajpat Nagar.</p>

<h1>Don’t Miss:</h1>

<p><img class="<a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490247/03efe03a-2184-11e6-9a48-00df4282116e.png">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490247/03efe03a-2184-11e6-9a48-00df4282116e.png</a>" width="700" height="400"/><noscript><img class="<a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490247/03efe03a-2184-11e6-9a48-00df4282116e.png">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490247/03efe03a-2184-11e6-9a48-00df4282116e.png</a>" width="700" height="400" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490247/03efe03a-2184-11e6-9a48-00df4282116e.png">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490247/03efe03a-2184-11e6-9a48-00df4282116e.png</a>"></noscript></p>

<h2>Jewellery Lane Street Shopping</h2>

<p>Central Market in Lajpat Nagar is a crowded market with numerous lanes, selling ready-made wear, saris, night suits, home textiles, crockery, jewellery and much more. In one of the lanes you will find costume jewellery, ranging from small earrings and jhumkas (chandelier-style danglers) to traditional wedding sets – Thses are ,ofcourse ,all replicas. The bangles are the biggest attraction here. You can get different colors and types of bangles: silver, glass, lacquer, white metal, oxidized silver and plastic. Some of them sport gold, silver, color paint and glass work in intricate patterns. You can match them with necklaces and earrings, even when they are not part of a set. The salesmen are most patient, experienced and updated on modern fashion – they even anticipate your needs. However , you have to be alert and bargain hard as well. The shopkeepers here are willing to bring down the prices substantially,so it is surely worthwhile to bargain. Choodas and kalire for the brides are also available.</p>

<p><img class="<a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490250/07d0609e-2184-11e6-8872-354473526920.png">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490250/07d0609e-2184-11e6-8872-354473526920.png</a>" width="700" height="400"/><noscript><img class="<a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490250/07d0609e-2184-11e6-8872-354473526920.png">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490250/07d0609e-2184-11e6-8872-354473526920.png</a>" width="700" height="400" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490250/07d0609e-2184-11e6-8872-354473526920.png">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490250/07d0609e-2184-11e6-8872-354473526920.png</a>"></noscript></p>

<h2>Salwar Lane Street Shopping</h2>

<p>This lane is parallel to the front row of shops that is opposite to 3Cs Cineplex. The market is perpetually busy and sells stitched and unstitched salwar suits in all kinds of fabrics. The shops stock salwar suits made of cotton, crepe, georgette and other materials. Some have embroidery or simple patterns on them. These suits are good for regular, casual wear, while some do lend themselves to party-wear as well. The patterns are always new and change rapidly. There are tailors and dye shops very close by, which makes it extremely convenient for shoppers to get white dupattas or salwars dyed to the exact shade. This is done in a couple of hours. The tailors do picoting (edging with loop stitches) on dupattas in a matter of minutes. Most salwar-kameez-dupatta sets are priced Rs. 600 plus, but if the fabric used is of superior quality and has intricate work, they can cost upwards of Rs. 1,000 per set. It is worth bargaining here especially if you are buying more than one salwar set.</p>

<p><img class="<a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490257/0e7b2154-2184-11e6-87ea-40a2f43f3c4a.png">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490257/0e7b2154-2184-11e6-87ea-40a2f43f3c4a.png</a>" width="700" height="400"/><noscript><img class="<a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490257/0e7b2154-2184-11e6-87ea-40a2f43f3c4a.png">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490257/0e7b2154-2184-11e6-87ea-40a2f43f3c4a.png</a>" width="700" height="400" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490257/0e7b2154-2184-11e6-87ea-40a2f43f3c4a.png">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/15490257/0e7b2154-2184-11e6-87ea-40a2f43f3c4a.png</a>"></noscript></p>

<h2>Jooti Stalls</h2>

<p>Since the branding was a tad questionable, we’re calling them the triad of shoe stores. Bang opposite KFC, stalls number 12, 13, and 14 are Lajpat Nagar’s hotspot for juttis, kohlapuris and other Indian inspired flats for men, women, and children. The stalls offer more or less the same in terms of design {thread work, cutout, solid colours, and embellishments}, styles, and price ranges. There does exist a certain competitive streak between the three stores, so if you’re in the mood for some theatrics, you can feign disinterest in one, to get yourself a better rate at the next one.</p>

<h1>Hunger’s Points in Lajpat Nagar Market:</h1>

<h2>Continental:</h2>

<ol>
<li>McDonalds</li>
<li>KFC</li>
<li>Comesum</li>
<li>Gourmet Gallery</li>
<li>Republic of Chicken</li>
<li>Qureshi’s Mutton Shop</li>
</ol>


<h2>Indian:</h2>

<ol>
<li>Moti Mahal Delux</li>
<li>Bengali Sweet Centre</li>
<li>KitKat Chinese</li>
<li>Wow Momos</li>
</ol>


<h2>Japanese:</h2>

<ol>
<li>Daitchi</li>
<li>Hot &amp; Sour</li>
<li>Princess Garden</li>
</ol>


<h2>Coffee Shops:</h2>

<ol>
<li>Barista</li>
<li>Chawla’s Chic-Inn</li>
<li>Nathu’s Sweets</li>
</ol>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
