<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Latest Posts Oncareer | JunkJam Blog - Street Market! Fashion! LifeStyle!]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/categories/career/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2018-08-11T21:17:31+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[ScholarsPro : Unlocking the Potential of e-Learning]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2017/12/14/scholarspro-unlocking-the-potential-of-e-learning/"/>
    <updated>2017-12-14T23:15:02+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2017/12/14/scholarspro-unlocking-the-potential-of-e-learning</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a lazy" data-original="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/34007108-a9ad0382-e126-11e7-9f09-9faf229a622f.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/34007108-a9ad0382-e126-11e7-9f09-9faf229a622f.jpg</a>" width="600" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left <a" data-original="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/34007108-a9ad0382-e126-11e7-9f09-9faf229a622f.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/34007108-a9ad0382-e126-11e7-9f09-9faf229a622f.jpg</a>" width="600" height="500" src="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/34007108-a9ad0382-e126-11e7-9f09-9faf229a622f.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/34007108-a9ad0382-e126-11e7-9f09-9faf229a622f.jpg</a>"></noscript>
There was a time when students had to attend long-hours classes to gain technical knowledge.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Carrying a pen and a notebook, and traveling to the classroom was a Necessity more than a Desire. No matter how unconformable the classroom chairs were, how bad the weather conditions were, they had to attend the classes. Missing a single class means disconnecting from the subject matter which won’t be repeating again.</p>

<p>All thanks to e-learning that redefined the way students and working professionals learn technology. There are online platforms that allow professionals to brush-up their technical as well as non-technical skills and get certified for the same. One of such online learning platforms is ScholarsPro <a href="http://www.scholarspro.com/">www.scholarspro.com</a>.</p>

<p>“Learn from the Scholars and become a Pro”– Scholarspro adheres to its tagline and assures that every student, be it a fresher or a professional, gets a most out of it. It’s an online learning platform that offers online training to more than 200 courses. With a dedicated team of Scholars, who are masters of their fields, Scholarspro offers a seamless online learning experience to its users.</p>

<h3>Why Go for Online Learning?</h3>

<p>In this fast pacing world, where technology is progressing at the speed of the light, getting up to date with latest technological trends has become a necessity. In such scenarios, online training programs as offered by Scholarspro helps job seekers learn technical skills at the comfort of home. They need not to attend any physical classes to learn such skills; rather they can learn the technical know-how of the desired course online, without wasting time on traveling.</p>

<h3>Get Skilled Get Certified</h3>

<p>Companies are looking for professionals who are skilled and certified. Gaining knowledge and validating the same on your CV are two different things. All thanks to online learning courses provided by Scholarspro that help professionals and students, validating their skills with a course certificate.</p>

<h3>Learning Solutions Offered by Scholarspro</h3>

<ul>
<li>Instructor-Led Learning</li>
<li>Self Paced Learning</li>
<li>Corporate Learning</li>
</ul>


<p>Instructor-Led Learning is a real-time training solution wherein students get to interact with the trainer live. This is direct and effective knowledge sharing solution that allows students to resolve their queries instantly. Students can connect to the instructor from anywhere because all they need is a good internet connection and a headphone.</p>

<p>Every student is different so as his learning capacity. Scholarspro knows this very well. Therefore, its next learning solution i.e. Self-paced learning solution allows students to learn at their own pace. Moreover, working professionals who always struggle with busy schedules, self-paced learning allows them schedule a class as per their choice. This is something which a physical classroom teaching methodology can never deliver.</p>

<h3>The Takeaway</h3>

<p>Learning technology is not easy, not because it’s complicated but because we don’t have enough time to keep us updated with the same. Attending physicals classes and sit for long-hours sessions is really not working in today’s life. All thanks to online learning platforms like Scholarspro, students and professionals can add more value to their CV by undergoing online training courses.</p>

<p>So what are you waiting for? Looking for a better job opportunity or want to upgrade your technical skill? Switch to <a href="http://www.scholarspro.com/">www.scholarspro.com</a>, and join an online training course NOW!!</p>

<p>Hope you liked this article. Have any query, do share with us in the comment section.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Must Haves if Applying for a Foreign College]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2017/02/07/6-must-haves-if-applying-for-a-foreign-college/"/>
    <updated>2017-02-07T19:36:03+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2017/02/07/6-must-haves-if-applying-for-a-foreign-college</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22694596/da270524-ed6d-11e6-816a-b32e9d91c746.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22694596/da270524-ed6d-11e6-816a-b32e9d91c746.jpg</a>" width="470" height="600"/><noscript><img class="left <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22694596/da270524-ed6d-11e6-816a-b32e9d91c746.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22694596/da270524-ed6d-11e6-816a-b32e9d91c746.jpg</a>" width="470" height="600" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22694596/da270524-ed6d-11e6-816a-b32e9d91c746.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22694596/da270524-ed6d-11e6-816a-b32e9d91c746.jpg</a>"></noscript>
If a study abroad programme seems appealing to you and you’ve applied or been selected and you are now super-duper excited about the abroad adventure. Well, congratulations! The next step is to prepare yourself for the trip. So make a probable questionnaire and kick start your preparation. Here we have complied 6 must have points in your to-do list while planning your trip.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Passport and Visa</h2>

<p>Without a passport, your abroad trip is impossible. If you already owned one, make sure that it’s not expired or won’t expire within 6 months of your intended return to the place you have opted for study. Also, check with other credentials related to the passport.</p>

<p>For newbies, it’s always advisable to apply for it before you plan a trip because the process may take a little time and also cuts the end-time hassle. One can also apply online, make payment and fix a schedule. It’s the easiest way to apply for a passport these days.</p>

<p>In addition to a passport, a traveller may need a visa to visit his/her dream country. Different countries have different visa requirements. In this regards, you will have to do some research and find out the required list. Or you can approach the nearest embassy as well. Like a passport, visa applications also takes several months to process so delay is non-advisable.</p>

<p>Apart from this, there are few countries, which allow the students to enter without a visa for 90 days. So, if your dream country comes under this umbrella than it’ll be an icing on the cake.</p>

<h2>Ensure You Have a Travel Insurance Plan</h2>

<p>While traveling abroad it is a must that you are covered by an accidental insurance plan.</p>

<p>What are Things that a Travel Insurance Covers?</p>

<ul>
<li>Coverage at the time of flight is delayed/cancelled</li>
<li>Lost luggage</li>
<li>Stolen personal belongings</li>
<li>Evacuation in the case of a health emergency or natural disaster</li>
</ul>


<p>Moreover, you can avail health insurance too from the Council of International Educational Exchange.</p>

<h2>Find a Plane Ticket at Cheapest Price: You’re Lucky</h2>

<p>Finding a plane ticket as per your budget and criteria is like an art of timing and luck. The fares are always unexpected and may vary depending on when you want to fly and to where you want to buy your tickets. There are various agencies though, you can compare the fares as well. Additionally, there are student travel agencies too who offer inexpensive tickets for students travelling abroad. You can approach them too.</p>

<h2>Research Your Destination</h2>

<p>Do some homework before flying to your destination. By knowing briefly about your soon-to-be home’s culture, language, history, economy, geography, you can ease your stay there.</p>

<h2>Settle with the Money</h2>

<p>Get an online account of you don’t have. It will be easier for you to use ATM/debit or credit cards to get cash in the local currency.</p>

<p>Moreover, never forget to inform your current bank that you are flying. Otherwise, you risk getting locked out of your account or they might flag it as a fraud.</p>

<p>Also, get some cash with you and don’t forget it the convert to the required currency. You can find the moneychangers at airport or metro stations.</p>

<h2>Finally Start Packing</h2>

<p>Now come to the last stage when you are done with all the documentations and financial requirements, start packing up. Kindly double check with your airlines to learn their luggage allowances to avoid fees. The less baggage you carry, the lesser are the chances of getting charged.</p>

<p>Finally, prepare yourself mentally, cross check everything that you have packed, especially the documents. Though you can never expect to be fully prepared upon arrival, we hope these tips will help you to plan your trip to your dream destination. Happy flight!!!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
