<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Latest Posts Onnew Delhi | JunkJam | Fashion! LifeStyle! Market! Travel!]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/categories/new-delhi/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2018-11-22T16:55:55+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delhi NCR Restaurants That Provide the Best Dinner Buffet]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/11/delhi-ncr-restaurants-that-provide-the-best-dinner-buffet/"/>
    <updated>2018-08-11T21:21:46+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/08/11/delhi-ncr-restaurants-that-provide-the-best-dinner-buffet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>{% img left <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993615-dd1881da-9dad-11e8-964b-ef5c32a5c50e.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993615-dd1881da-9dad-11e8-964b-ef5c32a5c50e.jpg</a> 400 500 %}
Delhi is a city that is known for amazing food, especially when it comes to buffets. There are a number of restaurants who offer great value for money all the time. Here are some of the best Delhi-NCR restaurants that provide the best dinner buffet:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>1. Barbeque Nation</h4>

<p>With one of the most elegant dining space, Barbeque Nation buffet, with Veg dinner buffet costing INR 950+tax and non-veg dinner buffet costing INR 1047+tax, is worth every penny. Dinner buffet is from 6:30PM to 10:30. Some of the amazing dishes include their delectable veg and non-veg starters, Butter Chicken, Cocktails, Biriyani, Malai Kulfi, and Salads. Their lavish dinner buffet is the best way to spend your evening. Additionally, their staff is warm and courteous.
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993518-65ea1836-9dac-11e8-99b5-e552c18282ea.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993518-65ea1836-9dac-11e8-99b5-e552c18282ea.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<h4>2. The Buffeteria</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993519-66209cb2-9dac-11e8-9389-c762944ec433.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993519-66209cb2-9dac-11e8-9389-c762944ec433.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
The Buffeteria gives a charming feel. Indian cuisine is prepared perfectly throughout the buffet. And Butter Chicken, Malai Chaap, Palak Patta Chaat, Rasmalai, Gulab Jamun, Rasgulla, Kheer are some of the popular dishes there. Dinner buffet runs from 7 PM to 11 PM. Expect to pay ₹750 to ₹890 for dinner, but it is well worth it. This place is ideal for when you wish to have some top-quality food with your friends and family and unwind in a calm ambiance.</p>

<h4>3. Band Baaja Baaraat</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993517-65aedfb4-9dac-11e8-9ad3-474e498fe130.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993517-65aedfb4-9dac-11e8-9ad3-474e498fe130.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
Serving the dinner buffets, ranging from ₹700 to ₹950, this Band Baaja Baaraat buffet at the Rio gives you a selection of many creatures of the sea, with stations themed after countries throughout the world. It is a tremendous value for money, as you can choose from the range of Veg Starter, Dal Makhani, Honey Chilli Potatoes, Gol Gappe, Gulab Jamun, Momos, and many other varieties of perfectly-cooked food.</p>

<h4>4. Pirates Of Grill</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993520-66573f9c-9dac-11e8-8878-6d76105ed9db.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993520-66573f9c-9dac-11e8-8878-6d76105ed9db.jpg</a> 500 600 %}
Pirates Of Grill is a restaurant cum bar with a beautiful decor that you will love spending time at with your friends and family. They prepare many kinds of dishes, from Panner Tikka, Honey Chilli Potatoes, Salsa Potato, Chicken Biriyani, Mocktails, and more. And the desserts are so good you love them. At between ₹700 to ₹950 for dinner, it is an excellent buffet deal. Their buffet is quite a good bargain featuring succulent barbecue starters and an array of Brazilian grilled snacks.</p>

<h4>5. Themis Barbecue House</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993606-a63f32e4-9dad-11e8-8d0e-48252ccaa2a7.png">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43993606-a63f32e4-9dad-11e8-8d0e-48252ccaa2a7.png</a> 500 600 %}
Themis Barbecue House offers an elaborate dinner buffet. These are all fantastic values, with massive selections of delectable foods, and of course, cocktails and drinks. All are offered at affordable dinner buffet rates. The service, the quality and the presentation – everything is on point. Their buffet is very good, especially for the price featuring Prawn, Mushroom Tikka, Beetroot Halwa, Dahi Kebab, Chicken Pizza, etc. They offer a plethora of options for you to choose from and is perfect for the food lovers.</p>

<p>If you are looking for the best buffets in Delhi, these 5 options are sure to leave you full and content. While these buffets are some of the best that you can find, there are tons of other options in Delhi for dinner buffets.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Everyone Is in Love With the Japanese Designer Brand MINISO]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/07/21/why-everyone-is-in-love-with-the-japanese-designer-brand-miniso/"/>
    <updated>2018-07-21T14:49:16+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/07/21/why-everyone-is-in-love-with-the-japanese-designer-brand-miniso</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>{% img left <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43034001-84c3c30e-8cf1-11e8-9e92-7c08e1f9efe3.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43034001-84c3c30e-8cf1-11e8-9e92-7c08e1f9efe3.jpg</a> 400 500 %}
The popular narrative says that the rise of the internet is killing physical retail. The existence of limitations, instead of full freedom, often stimulates creativeness better and brings better outcomes. This is apparently the case with the variety store MINISO.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>MINISO was established in the year 2013 by Japanese designer named Miyake Junya and Chinese businessmen named Ye Guofu. In only a brief span, their organization has blown up to a growing business kingdom with 1,800 stores in 40 nations, offering a varied collection of reasonable, curated merchandise, challenging the naysayers of physical retail. MINISO is a physical store business model around the truth of a world with web-based business. Through watchful thought of the buyers and interesting designs, it does what online stores can&rsquo;t: Offer a unique experience.
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43033996-828995be-8cf1-11e8-9e60-f93ea3b991a8.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43033996-828995be-8cf1-11e8-9e60-f93ea3b991a8.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<p>And they plan to build up another plan of action to break the price rise of traditional retailing and make the cost really match up the real cost of the items, and we additionally concentrate more on quality enhancement. Additionally, as a shopper myself, I profoundly understand that all shoppers want a blend of high quality and low cost, rather than low cost and low quality. Their affordable price which ranges from 150 INR to 790 INR is definitely their plus point and is attracting the customers all over the world.  Its super cute product range include items like bags, coin pouches, bottles, head bands,  phone holders, cute sippers, eyebrow razor, cotton pads, stationery items like small pocket diary etc.
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43033997-8311afd0-8cf1-11e8-9b59-04dfc3f60178.JPG">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43033997-8311afd0-8cf1-11e8-9b59-04dfc3f60178.JPG</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<p>The accomplishment of MINISO, despite the fact that very substantial, is still within our expectations since this model meets the trends of economic development and the actual requirements of shoppers. So since the establishment, it was anticipated that MINISO will go into various markets the world over and be largely renowned. Nonetheless, none could foresee that it would occur in such a brief time—1,800 stores have been opened worldwide in just three years. However, it likewise demonstrates that the present market needs more of such brands like MINISO in order to break and alter the business rules.
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43033998-83a3eb0c-8cf1-11e8-9dd7-812cc3147e4d.JPG">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43033998-83a3eb0c-8cf1-11e8-9dd7-812cc3147e4d.JPG</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<p>MINISO stocks around 4,000 items and people totally love their stuff. Their team consists of the best designers from all around the globe, however mainly from Sweden, Norway, Denmark, and Japan. Their designs create the basic, pure and unadorned characteristics of Japan and Northern Europe. This is the thing that sets up the cohesion of our item designs.
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43034000-8429879e-8cf1-11e8-8be1-665199aab90b.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43034000-8429879e-8cf1-11e8-8be1-665199aab90b.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<p>It is undoubtedly a great brand. As a creator brand of fast fashion, their items are substantial in quantity and they also refresh quickly. MINISO demands an item turnover of 21 days, with items refreshing every seven days in order to keep the feeling of curiosity for buyers and give them another surprise every time they visit the store. They also give careful consideration to the product display. They try to provide the best visual impact. The product display itself is inventive work that demands a lot of work.
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43034002-8886e1c4-8cf1-11e8-883d-5a4b46efea20.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/43034002-8886e1c4-8cf1-11e8-883d-5a4b46efea20.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<h3>MINISO Stores in Delhi NCR</h3>

<ul>
<li>DLF Mall of India, Sector-18 Noida</li>
<li>G.I.P Mall, Sector- 18 Noida</li>
<li>Logix City Center, Sector- 32 Noida</li>
<li>Ambience Mall, Vasant Kunj</li>
<li>DU Hub Kamla Nagar</li>
<li>Pacific Mall Anand Vihar Ghaziabad</li>
<li>MGF Metropolitan Mall - Gurgaon</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chor Bazaar - New Delhi]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/06/02/chor-bazaar-new-delhi/"/>
    <updated>2018-06-02T00:13:32+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/06/02/chor-bazaar-new-delhi</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>{% img left <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859704-5288f188-6600-11e8-82c5-92af712cde04.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859704-5288f188-6600-11e8-82c5-92af712cde04.jpg</a> 600 500 %}
Is it really chor bazaar? Like the stuffs here are stolen from somewhere and brought? How come stuffs are so cheap there? Must be defected! What! Are they really branded?? What all stuffs are available there?</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Yes, exactly! This is the state of mind when anyone listen the name of the chor bazaar for the first time which is followed by curiosity and laughter. Then, there is decision to give niche to all the questions. Let’s visit the place and find out!! Here is a guide to the “Must-take-tour” of the Chor Bazaar.</p>

<p>The market is set up on Sunday in between the lanes of Jama Majid and Red Fort. Both the monuments can be seen while shopping from the chor bazaar. If you are very much serious about shopping, the only rule that is followed is Early Bird catches the worm, get there early in the morning somewhere around 5:30am when then vendors are setting up the stalls. This is the time when chances of getting branded but stolen things are high. The price of clothes start at as low as 50 bucks and laptop by 5000 bucks. You can find branded winter-wear at as low as 100 bucks per piece.</p>

<h4>What all you could get?</h4>

<p>There is no particular list but most of the things you can head here for is:</p>

<ul>
<li>Cheap Gym Wear</li>
<li>Clothes - All variety</li>
<li>Perfumes
  {% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859711-5a7f114c-6600-11e8-8d22-cdd819335f8b.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859711-5a7f114c-6600-11e8-8d22-cdd819335f8b.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</li>
<li>Wallet</li>
<li>Old coins
  {% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859713-5b8ba1ae-6600-11e8-9ecc-77187ae808f2.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859713-5b8ba1ae-6600-11e8-9ecc-77187ae808f2.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</li>
<li>Gym equipments</li>
<li>Sports Material</li>
<li>Electronics including laptop
  {% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859714-5ca5b5ca-6600-11e8-9f6f-64fa1f9fca2f.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859714-5ca5b5ca-6600-11e8-9f6f-64fa1f9fca2f.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</li>
<li>Home decor</li>
<li>Crockery items
  {% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859716-5d6c4136-6600-11e8-836e-9e5fa65254d4.jpeg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859716-5d6c4136-6600-11e8-836e-9e5fa65254d4.jpeg</a> 500 600 %}</li>
<li>Stationary items</li>
<li>Hardware
  {% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859718-5e3ed4ca-6600-11e8-8560-b7a9bde29aa2.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859718-5e3ed4ca-6600-11e8-8560-b7a9bde29aa2.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</li>
<li>Music system
  {% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859724-5f5891ca-6600-11e8-9ecd-24fc18dbc5b6.jp://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859724-5f5891ca-6600-11e8-9ecd-24fc18dbc5b6.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859724-5f5891ca-6600-11e8-9ecd-24fc18dbc5b6.jp://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859724-5f5891ca-6600-11e8-9ecd-24fc18dbc5b6.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</li>
<li>Old cameras
  {% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859726-60672a18-6600-11e8-8d5b-38639ab6b996.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859726-60672a18-6600-11e8-8d5b-38639ab6b996.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</li>
<li>Wallets</li>
<li>Belts</li>
<li>Shoes
  {% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859727-618e3e2c-6600-11e8-8074-0670bf44ed26.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859727-618e3e2c-6600-11e8-8074-0670bf44ed26.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</li>
<li>Toys
  {% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859731-646e628e-6600-11e8-98e9-9b42f97f26f5.jpeg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859731-646e628e-6600-11e8-98e9-9b42f97f26f5.jpeg</a> 500 600 %}</li>
<li>Dry fruits</li>
<li>Spices
  {% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859732-655f3b6e-6600-11e8-8c37-5c504c21b93d.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40859732-655f3b6e-6600-11e8-8c37-5c504c21b93d.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</li>
<li>Variety of Bags</li>
<li>Watches
  {% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40860270-6c595db2-6602-11e8-896f-d785024aead7.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40860270-6c595db2-6602-11e8-896f-d785024aead7.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</li>
<li>Kitchen ware
  {% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40860274-6e657d7a-6602-11e8-8804-7f8003c46334.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40860274-6e657d7a-6602-11e8-8804-7f8003c46334.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</li>
</ul>


<p>If you are brand freak, you have to shuffle through all the stuffs and find out the one with the real tag. You can find plenty of second hand things, and most of them are branded and stolen.
Choose your domain, Lucky or unlucky! But you may find some of your stolen stuff ;)</p>

<h4>Keep in Mind</h4>

<ul>
<li>Make sure you wear comfortable clothes to roam around freely.</li>
<li>Polish your bargaining skills.</li>
<li>Re-check the stuffs for any kind of damage before paying.</li>
<li>If you are on shopping spree, carry a bag along.</li>
<li>Take care of your bag/wallet/purse.</li>
<li>Use Public transport for no parking hassle.</li>
</ul>


<h4>What else?</h4>

<p>The Delhi market will never disappoint you for food, head to chandhni chowk for the delicious breakfast. Start from Jalebi wala, one of the oldest shops in the loacality, and taste those finger licking Rabri-jalebi. Perfect start for Sunday! Later you could go to the Gurudwara Sis Ganj Sahib for some blessing, in case you are religious.</p>

<h4>Timing &amp; How to reach:</h4>

<p>The market starts setting up from 5:00 am in the morning and remains there by 11:00 am. Early you reach, more stuff you collect.</p>

<p>Take any metro to Jama Masjid metro station, prefer the violet line. Exit from the gate number 2  and you will find yourself surrounded by the stalls.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Champa Gali - New Delhi]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/04/11/champa-gali-new-delhi/"/>
    <updated>2018-04-11T22:23:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/04/11/champa-gali-new-delhi</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>{% img left <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38631485-81c0d584-3dd7-11e8-88dd-ef89ce2a1150.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38631485-81c0d584-3dd7-11e8-88dd-ef89ce2a1150.jpg</a> 500 450 %}
The alley, situated in Saidulajab village next to Saket in South Delhi, aborting the search of serenity in the city full of hustle bustle. The urban village transports you to lanes of France with its Parisian theme. The Champa gali houses Cafes, tea shop, Hand-crafted stores, restaurant to dine in, design studio and a room full of books which is highly recommended to people who want to spend some alone time or to discuss some innovative idea for the start-up.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>In case you are missing on excuses to visit this rustic street, here are reasons to visit this place:</p>

<h3>Pho King</h3>

<p>The restaurants come first when you enter in the Champa Gali. The flower embellished entry and full hearted smile of the staff members will tempt you to enter here, but what will keep you engaged is their Sitting arrangements and PAN ASIAN menu that has lot to offer. If you are not finding a place to take your loved one to spend some wonderful time, this is it!!</p>

<h4>Timing : 12pm to 11 pm  (Monday to Sunday)</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38631487-821e4c5a-3dd7-11e8-801a-0fb92ba4c09b.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38631487-821e4c5a-3dd7-11e8-801a-0fb92ba4c09b.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<h3>The Liberty Village</h3>

<p>The Liberty Village, lying in the corner of the champa gali, is the first of its kind of venture. The theme of the shop is flea market. They are giving away stuffs from some dream brands like LULU &amp; SKY  in throw away prices, YES..YOU HEARD IT RIGHT!! The reasons to visit the LIBERTY VILLAGE do not end here. The shop has got accessories and so customized COUPLE RINGS, quirky home decor and a restaurant inside to dine in. Themed wall to click pictures is another add on here.</p>

<p>A place to fulfil your shopping hunger. The place has different varieties of fragrance, t-shirts, eye-catching clutches and heels to offer.
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40589081-f3f0b43e-6204-11e8-8f78-f8318d349163.png">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/40589081-f3f0b43e-6204-11e8-8f78-f8318d349163.png</a> 600 700 %}</p>

<h3>Morellos</h3>

<p>This Cafe is right in front of entry and will catch your eyes with its daily offers displaying on a white board. The Goan themed cafe has varieties of shakes to offer along with some other snax. Morellos team ensures that you spend some quality time with your people without distracted by your gizmos and so it offers very interesting deal that they call as MORELLO DIGITAL DETOX i.e. get some off on your order for submitting all your gadge for an hour. Board Games is another thing to keep you busy while digital detox.</p>

<h4>Timing: 11 am to 10 pm (Monday to Sunday)</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38631489-82674e28-3dd7-11e8-811f-6653c382ed25.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38631489-82674e28-3dd7-11e8-811f-6653c382ed25.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<h3>Blue Tokai</h3>

<p>Enter in this well-lit and calm cafe, and you will be welcomed by aroma of coffee floating in the air, this place is a must visit for the coffee lovers. The uniqueness of this cafe is they provide detour in their live roasting room and show the basic blending process to the customers, on all the Tuesday, Thursday and Sunday. The cafe has quaint open air sitting arrangement in the backyard giving rural vibe.</p>

<h4>Timing: 9am to 10pm (Monday to Sunday)</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38631490-82af595c-3dd7-11e8-9149-482026b20ffd.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38631490-82af595c-3dd7-11e8-9149-482026b20ffd.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<h3>The People Tree</h3>

<p>This outlet could easily be pointed out with the marquee announcing the name out loud and what will lure you inside is, the show-pieces kept behind the glass. The studio-cum-shop has creative space showcasing unique stationary items made of natural and biodegradable materials, khadi and block printed apparels, quirky jewellery and variety of skin care products.
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38631491-82f5b6d6-3dd7-11e8-840d-5a821824351f.jpeg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38631491-82f5b6d6-3dd7-11e8-840d-5a821824351f.jpeg</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<h3>Jugmug Thela</h3>

<p>The quirky tea-stall has a khidki to place order, benches to sit outdoors and a room full of books to sit and discuss ideas in silence. The book-house hosts variety of deals like one can come with few books and grab a cup of tea and cookies, other time the book lovers could buy books on 50% of actual book price and that goes to NGO called as Karambagh.
Apart from dozen of Masala Chai flavours, Vietnamese Cold Coffee, Vinnese cream coffee, Chikoo ice cream and cookies to pair with the cuppa; the customer could take away these ingredient or order it online from their official website.</p>

<h4>Timing: 11am to 7:30pm (Monday to Sunday)</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38631492-833a0912-3dd7-11e8-8ad8-2b406353a58a.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38631492-833a0912-3dd7-11e8-8ad8-2b406353a58a.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<h3>Jugaad</h3>

<p>The stall is just adjacent to Jugmug Thela. The brand is hosted by an  NGO of Faridabad named as Karambagh. The shop offers apparels of patchwork, stationary items made of elephant dung and handmade jewelleries, bags and wallets printed from vegetable dye.</p>

<h4>Timing: 11am to 7:30 pm (Monday to Sunday)</h4>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38631493-8379d2d6-3dd7-11e8-8323-e8de38a79a55.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38631493-8379d2d6-3dd7-11e8-8323-e8de38a79a55.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<h3>Mettalurgy STUDIO</h3>

<p>This art and design innovation studio has some quirky design of home decor to offer.
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38632468-776974a8-3dda-11e8-81c0-65928766c3d4.png">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38632468-776974a8-3dda-11e8-81c0-65928766c3d4.png</a>  500 600 %}</p>

<h3>Social Events:</h3>

<p>The secret alley in the capital also hosts number of exhibitions, evening of poetry and music-jig, which is organized in the backyard of these shops. To stay updated click here: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/champagali/">https://www.facebook.com/champagali/</a></p>

<p>{% img center i<a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38631494-83c0edba-3dd7-11e8-9e28-551f965b9ae3.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38631494-83c0edba-3dd7-11e8-9e28-551f965b9ae3.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<h4>Location:</h4>

<p>Khasra 258, Lane 3, Westend Marg, Saidulajaib</p>

<p>Land Mark: Dark House</p>

<p>Nearest Metro Station: Saket, Gate No.:2</p>

<p>Start walking in direction of Five Sense Garden, auto drivers might not be able to guide .</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dilli Haat Market New Delhi]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/04/03/dilli-haat-market-new-delhi/"/>
    <updated>2018-04-03T21:35:43+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/04/03/dilli-haat-market-new-delhi</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>{% img left <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38262409-ba6e7632-378a-11e8-9b35-013540794364.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38262409-ba6e7632-378a-11e8-9b35-013540794364.jpg</a> 600 500 %}
Bored of shopping in malls and same regular branded shops which could be found in all the cities? Time to do something thoda hat ke!!</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Dilli haat gives you this pleasant opportunity of shopping under open sky in plaza that is paved with stones, flowering shrubs, eucalyptus trees, with pennants and bulbs hanging in the air.
With haat ambience, little stalls of dilli haat have lot to offer from all corners of vast &amp; varied land of India. Ranging from unique antiques for drawing room to hand-woven pashminas directly from Kashmir, handlooms, carved stones, rugs, leather items,  precious stones, jewellery, varieties of tea and spices and home decor will keep you clinged all the time . There is rotation of stalls allotted to craftsmen in each 15 days preserving and promoting the rich heritage of India and its culture.
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38262403-b95a372c-378a-11e8-89d6-f719258bf901.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38262403-b95a372c-378a-11e8-89d6-f719258bf901.jpg</a> 600 700 %}
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38262402-b9129c6e-378a-11e8-9ee7-cc93531d5158.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38262402-b9129c6e-378a-11e8-9ee7-cc93531d5158.jpg</a> 600 700 %}
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38262406-b9e6cef8-378a-11e8-9335-706fe9023a0a.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38262406-b9e6cef8-378a-11e8-9335-706fe9023a0a.jpg</a> 600 700 %}
{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38262401-b8cc4e94-378a-11e8-89c2-108c1e9741c0.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38262401-b8cc4e94-378a-11e8-89c2-108c1e9741c0.jpg</a> 600 700 %}</p>

<p>In case you are exhausted and hungry from walking stalls to stalls, there is food plaza offering multiple delightful cuisines from different regions of India to relish your taste buds in Eco friendly manner giving you feel of dhaba here and there.</p>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38262405-b99ddc20-378a-11e8-8ae5-cd8f72da7e91.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38262405-b99ddc20-378a-11e8-8ae5-cd8f72da7e91.jpg</a> %}
Dilli haat also has a few permanent stalls and an exhibition hall to display handcraft and handloom based shows, Seminars and Events. It also organizes food festivals for the guests. If lucky enough, you could find cultural activities around or craftsmen showing their skills live.</p>

<p>{% img center <a href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38262408-ba2af920-378a-11e8-82cc-7c78dd91311d.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/38262408-ba2af920-378a-11e8-82cc-7c78dd91311d.jpg</a> 500 600 %}</p>

<h2>LOCATIONS:</h2>

<p>Delhi haat, established jointly by Delhi Tourism Development Corporation (DTDC), Government of Delhi and NDMC, D.C. (Handicrafts) &amp; D.C. (handlooms), Ministry of Textiles &amp; Ministry of
Tourism, Government, is open on all 7 days of week and could be accessed in different parts of City as mentioned below:</p>

<h3>Dilli Haat, INA</h3>

<ul>
<li>Nearest Metro: INA on Yellow Line.</li>
<li>Timing:

<ul>
<li>10:30 am to 10:00 pm (16th February to 30th November)</li>
<li>11:00 am to 9:00 pm (1st December to 15th February)</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Entry Fees:

<ul>
<li>Rs. 30 (Adult)</li>
<li>Rs. 20 (Children)</li>
<li>Rs. 100 (Foreigner)</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>


<h3>Dilli Haat, Janakpuri</h3>

<ul>
<li>Nearest Metro: Tilak Nagar and Janakpuri East on Blue Line</li>
<li>Timing: 11:00 am to 10:00pm (January to December)</li>
<li>Entry Fees:

<ul>
<li>Rs. 30 (Adult)</li>
<li>Rs. 20 (Children)</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>


<h3>Dilli Haat, Pitampura</h3>

<ul>
<li>Nearest Metro: Netaji Subhash Place on Red Line</li>
<li>Timing: 10:00 am to 9:00 pm</li>
<li>Entry Fees:

<ul>
<li>Rs. 20 (Adult)</li>
<li>Rs. 10 (5 to 12 years)</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
