<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Latest Posts on Junkjam | JunkJam Blog - Street Market! Fashion! LifeStyle!]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/categories/junkjam/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2016-12-25T18:41:40+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Your Child Picking the Right Career Option?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/12/21/is-your-child-picking-the-right-career-option/"/>
    <updated>2016-12-21T07:45:27+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/12/21/is-your-child-picking-the-right-career-option</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375268/56872186-c752-11e6-8ceb-2216eee23654.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375268/56872186-c752-11e6-8ceb-2216eee23654.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500">
A simple effort of yours can make great change in terms of selecting the right career for your child!</p>

<p>Being a parent, has this question ever strike on your mind? Have you ever observed, towards what your little one is inclining more? In the daily hustle, parents often forget to notice those silly but important deeds of their child, which in a long run can be a big problem to tackle with. The skill of being a good parent Is not a rocket science. Yes, it can be obtained over the time. In today’s world, where academics, extra-curricular activities and distractions in the term of electronic gadgets, acquire children’s priority time, it is tough to communicate with them. However, a simple effort in this regard can make a great change.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>How to choose a right career is quite a common question floating in every students’ mind after completing the schooling. Since this is the peak time to find the right path and follow it enthusiastically, a student must be aware of his aptitude and preferences. One wrong decision might lead you to regret for lifetime. A well- structured career is an essential element to chase a successful life and here, parents can set the example as epitome of success, as they have already experienced the same phase.</p>

<p>In this article, we will give you an idea about how to help your child in choosing the right career path. Moreover, the DO’s and DON’T given here will help you in evaluate your parental role.</p>

<h2>Keep an Eye on these Imperatives:</h2>

<p>There are a few factors, which make the career selection process like a cakewalk. While determining a career for their children, parents should understand and ponder these factors. They include:</p>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375267/567c545e-c752-11e6-8c10-76e9c5ac7c9f.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375267/567c545e-c752-11e6-8c10-76e9c5ac7c9f.jpg</a>"></p>

<h3>Interest:</h3>

<p>Whatever you are doing, it should be of your interest. Without having an interest in a particular field, one can’t be successful in making this as his/her passion. Same goes to your child too. It is your duty as a parent to keep a frequent check of your child’s interest and choose a career accordingly.
<img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375266/567b37d6-c752-11e6-890d-bb5b43811011.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375266/567b37d6-c752-11e6-890d-bb5b43811011.jpg</a>"></p>

<h3>Ability:</h3>

<p>One’s ability determines his/her capabilities of doing something. It acts like a mirror of your child personality as well. By noting their ability of doing something, you can select a career exactly meant for your child.
<img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375265/567972e8-c752-11e6-9c3b-1d05801ffc63.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375265/567972e8-c752-11e6-9c3b-1d05801ffc63.jpg</a>"></p>

<h3>Research on the availability of course:</h3>

<p>The course related to a particular career should be available easily and it is, therefore, parents’ duty to do a thorough research on that before advising their child to opt it.
<img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375264/56789c2e-c752-11e6-9ced-32b230c57a39.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375264/56789c2e-c752-11e6-9ced-32b230c57a39.jpg</a>"></p>

<h3>Scope:</h3>

<p>Pay attention to the scope of a particular course, which tells us about what type of opportunities, will open up after doing that particular course or going for a career.
<img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375263/5675b1da-c752-11e6-83e4-cc55d58f47b7.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375263/5675b1da-c752-11e6-83e4-cc55d58f47b7.jpg</a>"></p>

<h3>Remuneration:</h3>

<p>Though, all the time it’s not necessary, but in today’s scenario, remuneration or salary plays an important role. Remuneration should meet the child’s aspirations, so that they can excel a satisfied and comfortable life ahead.</p>

<h2>Do’s and Don’t</h2>

<h3>Do&rsquo;s</h3>

<ul>
<li>Evaluate your child’s aptitude, strengths and weaknesses.</li>
<li>Help your child in discovering his/her own passion.</li>
<li>Motivate your child in pursuing his/her passion.</li>
<li>Inform your child regarding all aspects of the career.</li>
<li>Help the child understand the work life in the chosen career by associating with professionals in the field.</li>
<li>Stop your child from falling prey to peer-pressure and herd mentality.</li>
<li>Gain your child’s confidence and motivate them to discuss their queries with you.</li>
<li>Seek professional help whenever required.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Dont&rsquo;s</h3>

<ul>
<li>Do not impose your wish on them</li>
<li>Do not burden the child with unreal expectations</li>
<li>Don’t be impatient when dealing with children</li>
<li>Career scope changes with time; do not try to impose the ideas or views that existed during your days</li>
<li>Do not misguide the child into choosing a career of your choice</li>
<li>Do not be on rush to answer a child’s question without the knowledge. It’s ok to take time, research or seek professional help</li>
<li>Protect your child from being influenced by others in the career selection process</li>
</ul>


<p>This way you can be an active partner of your child while selecting a career. Identify your child’s interest, skills and value and start playing your role.</p>

<p>Happy Parenting</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Navigate the Traps of Online Dating to Save Your Relationship?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/12/20/how-to-navigate-the-traps-of-online-dating-to-save-your-relationship/"/>
    <updated>2016-12-20T00:07:32+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/12/20/how-to-navigate-the-traps-of-online-dating-to-save-your-relationship</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324391/870c3a8c-c647-11e6-9118-abe61a3cd600.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324391/870c3a8c-c647-11e6-9118-abe61a3cd600.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600"></p>

<!-- more -->


<p>This surely is a tech savvy age and the rise of smartphones are all the rage. It has transformed our society wherein online dating has been ticking all the wrong boxes.
Men who are in relationships might be loyal to their women but nowadays, with this emerging trend of various online dating sites gaining popularity; men are drifting towards infidelity. These online dating sites provide a gamut of attractive facilities to woo men along with hundreds and thousands of eye-catching women waiting to get ticked. Men look for excitement in their lives and what better way than online dating sites? While being in a relationship, there are times when men look for other prospects for simply flirting and passing their time, these online dating sites are a boon for these men to talk with women they have never met or spoken with.</p>

<h2>How to deal with it -</h2>

<p>Do not turn a blind eye to it, if you get acquainted with the fact that your man is getting indulged in online dating sites and is showing his interest in it. It can act like a dagger piercing through the heart but do not ignore.</p>

<h2>Educate yourself and research about his interest –</h2>

<p>If he sends across messages that are steamy and passion then he surely seeks or attention just like an egoistic man would want to do and if he is sending intimate and comforting messages then he is craving for affection emotionally.</p>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324389/86f13aac-c647-11e6-9d6b-94a3f9fef1a1.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324389/86f13aac-c647-11e6-9d6b-94a3f9fef1a1.jpg</a>"></p>

<p>You don’t need to feel that you are not of value for him because online dating is considered as a sign of infidelity and such men at times lack the ability of communicating their needs or it might even be the reason of his self-image. You need to reach out to him and talk it out instead of thinking about anything else.</p>

<h2>Set your limits –</h2>

<p>When you get to know that your man is cheating on you, you need to set your limits there and then. Stop acting like an emotional freak and if you are serious for him; make it certain that he needs to make a choice. Don’t feel the pain of his entertainment and cut all ties of physical intimacy till the time he doesn’t get back to his senses.</p>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324390/86fe7244-c647-11e6-989f-b3c925bc419d.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324390/86fe7244-c647-11e6-989f-b3c925bc419d.jpg</a>"></p>

<p>Don’t burst like a volcano over him and try to be calm. Because he might take offence despite being wrong at his part. Also, don’t blame or argue, put out your heart on your sleeve and refrain from having any physical contact with him. He might comprehend the blunder he has made to his relationship.</p>

<h2>Focus back on your life –</h2>

<p>Your happiness is equally important and if you cannot control his infidelity, be kind to yourself. Do not indulge in sleepless nights and swollen eyes. Pamper yourself and ignore his behavior. There are times when your self-esteem gets broken when your man does such things.</p>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324388/86e47ef2-c647-11e6-87fe-e9e744e0fe2a.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324388/86e47ef2-c647-11e6-87fe-e9e744e0fe2a.jpg</a>"></p>

<p>Bubble-up and make sure you date yourself and spend as much time with yourself that it makes you feel happy. Take your life back and maintain the respect and self-esteem in the ego, no matter what. Everything else will fall back into place and if he is meant to be, he will come back to you.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s How You Can Check Your Boyfriend’s Loyalty?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/12/19/heres-how-you-can-check-your-boyfriends-loyalty/"/>
    <updated>2016-12-19T07:50:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/12/19/heres-how-you-can-check-your-boyfriends-loyalty</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21299213/73ec5474-c5bf-11e6-8840-1807723aa1df.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21299213/73ec5474-c5bf-11e6-8840-1807723aa1df.jpg</a>"></p>

<!-- more -->


<p>It sends shivers down your spine when you acknowledge or even think about your beau cheating on you. Trust and faith are the base of any relationship. There are a few tests and ways through which you can check the loyalty of your boyfriend. There are times when you might be apprehensive of his behavior like phone number on waiting, replying late or reluctant to meet but it does not mean that he is cheating on you. Suspecting him for false reasons might be a disastrous feeling for your relationship so try to test him through the below mentioned ways.</p>

<h2>Steer clear from infidelity</h2>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21299210/73e10b6e-c5bf-11e6-8ccd-77cfac469d6a.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21299210/73e10b6e-c5bf-11e6-8ccd-77cfac469d6a.jpg</a>">
You don’t have to hire a company to do the loyalty test for you. Start small and conduct loyalty tests all by yourself. You don’t have to involve scores of people to do this for you when some simple tricks can do the work for you.</p>

<h2>The Social Media Test</h2>

<p>You need to develop a fake social media profile with a believable name along with photographs and friends so that it doesn’t look unreliable. The pictures that you post, make sure that those pictures are attractive and might woo your guy. Try to flirt and trifle with him. Try to judge his reply and check, if he is interested in that fake profile. Slowly and steadily ask for his number and check whether he reverts or not. If he is interested in that fake profile and shares the phone number then, he is certainly not trustworthy and you have proof to support the infidelity.
<img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21299209/73dd5a96-c5bf-11e6-9828-fd802570b6a0.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21299209/73dd5a96-c5bf-11e6-9828-fd802570b6a0.jpg</a>"></p>

<h2>Friends with Benefits</h2>

<p>Take help from your friends and make them meet your guy. Try to observe his behavior and attributes while he communicates with your friends. Ask one of your friend to become overfriendly and informal with your guy and check his response. You don’t have to exaggerate the situation, ask your friend to call and flirt with him. Just in case if he is positive towards the entire philandering then he is surely not loyal.
<img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21299212/73e5773a-c5bf-11e6-9723-8f05fa70c8d1.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21299212/73e5773a-c5bf-11e6-9723-8f05fa70c8d1.jpg</a>"></p>

<h2>Sudden change in attitude</h2>

<p>Try to observe his behavior, way of dressing, talking and meeting you. Is he ignoring you while giving you a reason of work overload or does he spend a lot of time surfing social media? These are some of the things which might be of concern for you. Does he not share his messages with you or he doesn’t like if you check his cell phone or Facebook account?
<img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21299211/73e1d198-c5bf-11e6-8ae4-0421f8ff1b80.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21299211/73e1d198-c5bf-11e6-8ae4-0421f8ff1b80.jpg</a>"></p>

<p>These are some of the ways through which you can confront your boyfriend and check whether he is loyal to you or not. You never know if he is a two-timing man or he has been cheating on you since a long time. You have to be frank and do not allow him to twist the things. If you are serious for him, try to confront it and work on your relationship. This would take time to heal because it can develop grudges between the two of you but time heals every wound. Give him a last chance but always remember that once bitten, twice shy; stay cautious and guarded.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Super Gorgeous Woman Fashion Trends Not to Miss in This Diwali]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/24/woman-fashion-trends-in-diwali-2016/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-24T15:18:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/24/woman-fashion-trends-in-diwali-2016</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651466/8a8718ce-9a2a-11e6-8cd7-eb9674c2f9e2.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651466/8a8718ce-9a2a-11e6-8cd7-eb9674c2f9e2.jpg</a>" width="400" height="600">
Well, it’s an open secret that all women’s are fashion savvy in some way or other. Some like to uniform themselves with the latest fashion and others trying to keep up with the trends at the festival season.
Whatever the occasion and whichever the place, fashion is always on the mind. So, as we all know the happy days of Diwali are here to come and I am going to discover some crazy fashion trends for this Diwali
– after all this is the best opportunity to show your bit-off fashion sense, if you are so inclined.</p>

<!--more-->


<h1>Go Indo-Western:</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19656458/b39238b2-9a3d-11e6-8c42-92740f186c51.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19656458/b39238b2-9a3d-11e6-8c42-92740f186c51.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500">
Whether you are collage going girl or working woman fusion dressing can give interesting twist to your Diwali fashion. You can try some hit fusions like choli with palazzo pants, traditional saree with off shoulder or sleeveless blouse.
All these apparels can be emphasized with delicate elements like zardosi work or you can try beads, stones and pearls as well.</p>

<h1>Jewelry time:</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651463/8a74cf0c-9a2a-11e6-92cc-7cc67e408913.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651463/8a74cf0c-9a2a-11e6-92cc-7cc67e408913.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600">
The most important thing which can make or break your look is jewelry. So, leave some good budget aside to invest in beautiful jewelry.
Huge ranges of exclusive jewelries are available in market to suit every budget and every taste. Furthermore, culture jewelry is in revival on the festive occasions, so this is an ideal time to add some traditional jewelry in your collection.</p>

<h1>Digital print:</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651459/89df5b16-9a2a-11e6-81ab-1e9a8519a764.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651459/89df5b16-9a2a-11e6-81ab-1e9a8519a764.jpg</a>">
Nowadays, digital prints hammered huge market and now you can find these prints for anarkali suits, kurties, party gown and in sarees also.
Floor length anarkali suit with digital print can give you contemporary look this Diwali.</p>

<h1>Go with Polka dots</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651467/8aa6cfa2-9a2a-11e6-932b-2336226e9d17.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651467/8aa6cfa2-9a2a-11e6-932b-2336226e9d17.jpg</a>">
Gone are the days when people were hesitant to try something different with their clothing especially on traditional festival like Diwali.
However, if you are bored with traditional sari or salwar kamiz then better you go with polka dot. It’s an innovative outfit that gives perfect model look.</p>

<h1>Footwear:</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651461/8a61e69e-9a2a-11e6-8285-7e0be452b3e4.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651461/8a61e69e-9a2a-11e6-8285-7e0be452b3e4.jpg</a>">
Well, your footwear is a mirror of your style sense. So, I suggest pair your outfit and jewelry with nice traditional footwear like kolhapuri chapples,
jodhpuri or mojadi. You can also go with nice pair of flipflops with designs and glittery stones.</p>

<h1>Get trendy with long skirts:</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651460/8a2c1fbe-9a2a-11e6-83dd-c79aefb93842.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651460/8a2c1fbe-9a2a-11e6-83dd-c79aefb93842.jpg</a>">
Do you have collection of ethnic tops and jackets? Then team up those with any vibrant colored long skirt. But make sure not to go with
very flowy or dramatic skirts as it can mess with diyas or rangoli.</p>

<h1>Stylish nose ring:</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651466/8a8718ce-9a2a-11e6-8cd7-eb9674c2f9e2.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651466/8a8718ce-9a2a-11e6-8cd7-eb9674c2f9e2.jpg</a>">
Though it’s very less considered armament in jewelry, Stylish nose ring can gives you elegant look for this Diwali. You can find various kinds of nose ring or studs with different material like metal,
stone, gold etc.</p>

<p>So, these are some fashion trends that can surely help you to make right choice for yourself to rock this Diwali festival. Enjoy your Diwali to the fullest!!!</p>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651462/8a6e4fe2-9a2a-11e6-9106-f7ccc795fc9d.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19651462/8a6e4fe2-9a2a-11e6-9106-f7ccc795fc9d.gif</a>">
Happy Diwali ☺</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Questions Every Girl Wants to Ask Her Guy?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/15/questions-every-girl-wants-to-ask-her-guy/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-15T13:18:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/15/questions-every-girl-wants-to-ask-her-guy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif</a>" width="500" height="600">
Well, it is not as if the number of questions we often bombard you with is a low figure. Nevertheless, we have a few more.
There are certain questions, which are not so easy to ask, or are better avoided. However, in alignment with our traits,
we cannot feel at peace unless these questions are answered.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>No matter how cool we might seem as girlfriends, we remain troubled by these questions.
Therefore, boys, if you are reading this, please do help us clear away the clouds of curiosity hovering over our heads by answering these questions!</p>

<h1>1.Do you love me? Like, you really do?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378810/4b5135d4-920c-11e6-9819-b7f47d541d5c.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378810/4b5135d4-920c-11e6-9819-b7f47d541d5c.gif</a>">
You might have been very clear about your serious intentions. Yet, we feel the need to re-confirm if the answer has changed, is still the same, or is modified.
And of course, we love listening to the way you express your love.</p>

<h1>2.How much do you love me?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378794/4b17ec2a-920c-11e6-8e48-76543db03aea.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378794/4b17ec2a-920c-11e6-8e48-76543db03aea.gif</a>">
We aren’t expecting a very clichéd answer for this one, but rather an honest answer that quantitatively describes your love for us.
Then you can probably just add on those historic lines proclaiming how you can even fetch us stars from Heaven. :P</p>

<h1>3.‘Do you ever stalk me the way I stalk you?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif</a>">
Umm, maybe not as diligently as we do, but at least partially in the same manner that we do?
That’s really something we girls would want to know. We love knowing how much a person is curious about us.</p>

<h1>4.Does your best friend really like us?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378797/4b195eca-920c-11e6-8d2a-09695430c5d2.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378797/4b195eca-920c-11e6-8d2a-09695430c5d2.gif</a>">
If this question has not yet come up, be assured that it soon will. Although your best friend might be very nice to us,
we cannot help but contemplate on the question if she genuinely likes us or is being pretentious and doing it for the sake of friendship.</p>

<h1>5.‘How serious were you in your previous relationship?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378798/4b1af94c-920c-11e6-8787-0feccfb25de8.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378798/4b1af94c-920c-11e6-8787-0feccfb25de8.gif</a>">
This kind of a question may lead to an awkward silence. It is similar to the awkwardness we face when we contemplate asking you this.
The answer would not really affect our relationship, but we are curious. We would want to be a bit more knowledgeable about this.</p>

<h1>6.‘Did you ever imagine getting married to your ex?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378796/4b18c352-920c-11e6-8118-fd9083e9c858.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378796/4b18c352-920c-11e6-8118-fd9083e9c858.gif</a>">
If it were a straight forward NO, we definitely would want to know the answer. However, if it’s a yes, then maybe we should just go to the next question.</p>

<h1>7. ‘What do your friends think about me?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378811/4b51c6b6-920c-11e6-9198-180e93ff30d0.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378811/4b51c6b6-920c-11e6-9198-180e93ff30d0.gif</a>">
Whether the answer is negative or positive, we are ready to face anything and everything.
We just want to know about the kind of conversation you have with your friends while discussing us.</p>

<h1>8.‘Do you still miss something special about your past relationship?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378799/4b1fccc4-920c-11e6-8dd9-f1519d838bbb.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378799/4b1fccc4-920c-11e6-8dd9-f1519d838bbb.gif</a>">
At some point, we do accept your past and stay cool with it. Yet, we do love keeping ourselves informed about such things.</p>

<h1>9.What if your parents do not accept me?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378814/4b52a34c-920c-11e6-88c1-1175cd81b92b.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378814/4b52a34c-920c-11e6-88c1-1175cd81b92b.gif</a>">
We reassure you that we will try our best to make them like us.
However, suppose they don’t, what do we do then? Where does our relationship go from here?</p>

<h1>10.Why me at all?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378795/4b1756b6-920c-11e6-8677-5966d4dc2bf0.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378795/4b1756b6-920c-11e6-8677-5966d4dc2bf0.gif</a>">
Now this one calls for a super romantic reply. We girls would love hearing about your feelings during the initial meeting, and what prompted you to choose us.
It might be the hundredth time but it is hard to explain how it feels to hear the answer every single time!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
