<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Latest Posts on Junkjam | JunkJam Blog]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/categories/junkjam/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2016-09-18T22:34:41+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Honeymoon Dresses to Wow Him]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/15/5-honeymoon-dresses-to-wow-him/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-15T12:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/15/5-honeymoon-dresses-to-wow-him</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550457/95725a82-7b71-11e6-9e6b-2924f7b15b7e.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550457/95725a82-7b71-11e6-9e6b-2924f7b15b7e.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500">
After the wedding ceremonies are done, the newly wedded couple is all ready to get set and go for their honeymoon. You want everything to be the best, be it the honeymoon destination, the venue where you’ll b staying, the places that you are going to visit, the activities you are going to do, the places you are going to eat or shop. Everything is planned in advance and you just can’t wait to do it all. Your excitement level is simply unstoppable!</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Honeymoon! The dreamy phase of every girl’s life, where everything seems to be perfect and the way it had to be. So, you are in your dreamy phase and can’t keep your hands off each other. You just can’t wait to reach your honeymoon spot, but before you set out for it, do not forget to do your homework. Yes, we are talking about a few pretty and hot outfits that would simply make him go nuts over your beauty! Also, a dress chosen wisely can make it an amazing as well as a never forgetting honeymoon for you. Here are a few suggestions as to what dresses can you take along on your honeymoon and have those picture perfect memories:</p>

<h1>Evening dress</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550455/9558ed54-7b71-11e6-83a2-fb4d7c6986ed.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550455/9558ed54-7b71-11e6-83a2-fb4d7c6986ed.jpg</a>" width="600" height="700">
Nothing can make you look classier than an elegant yet sexy evening dress. They say red is the color of love so why not put on a red evening dress and have a candle light dinner beneath a sky lit with stars. Pair it with pencil heels and a beige or gold clutch and slay him!</p>

<h1>Floral tunic</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550456/956e0658-7b71-11e6-8438-a619ff6f4cc4.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550456/956e0658-7b71-11e6-8438-a619ff6f4cc4.jpg</a>" width="600" height="700">
A tiny tunic makes every girl look pretty and hot at the same time. So, wearing a cute floral dress while going out for shopping would not let him take his eyes off you. Putting on a light and natural makeup would add to the glow on your face and give you that perfect look that would make him love you more and more.</p>

<h1>Boho piece</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550453/951f542c-7b71-11e6-9634-8e3c1f603e84.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550453/951f542c-7b71-11e6-9634-8e3c1f603e84.jpg</a>">
A boho one piece is all you need to have that attractive look for your honeymoon. Moreover, it would make your better half go completely crazy after you.</p>

<h1>Hot pants</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550454/954add72-7b71-11e6-95c6-97a8c9d5d202.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550454/954add72-7b71-11e6-95c6-97a8c9d5d202.jpg</a>" width="600" height="700">
Hot pants give every girl a sexy chic look. So a denim hot pant wore with a sexy top or a cool tee accompanied by a pair of shades and  wedges would get you a look that would make his eyes glued to you.</p>

<h1>Barely there</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550457/95725a82-7b71-11e6-9e6b-2924f7b15b7e.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18550457/95725a82-7b71-11e6-9e6b-2924f7b15b7e.jpg</a>">
A beaded net top or dress in nude in color will leave a little to his imagination. The beaded threadwork on the outfit would make you look sexy and he would not be able to resist you anymore and you will be all set for a hot and amazing night.</p>

<p>Hope you like our suggestions on the kind of dresses that would make your honeymoon an extra special and extra hot one! Do not forget to click amazing pictures and make a beautiful collection of your beautiful memories.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Best Indian Wedding Songs for the Grand Bridal Entry]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/11/8-best-Indian-wedding-songs-for-the-grand-bridal-entry/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-11T12:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/11/8-best-Indian-wedding-songs-for-the-grand-bridal-entry</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417590/530a3f42-7852-11e6-9294-5bc2cd9fc9f9.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417590/530a3f42-7852-11e6-9294-5bc2cd9fc9f9.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500">
Wedding! The most auspicious and important day of every girl’s life! On this so very special day, everything ought to be perfect. From a beautiful bridal dress to the perfect background song during the entry, there needs to be sublimity in everything and every girl wants that these dreams come true.
Picture yourself on your wedding day walking down the alley with your favorite people by your side. The marvelous attire and a soft romantic song being played in the background, while you move towards your prince charming. Doesn’t it seem like a fairy tale where you are the princess and the evening belongs to you! So, to help you with this fairy tale turning into reality, we have a list of songs to make your bridal entry an epic one:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Raabta</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417601/8875089c-7852-11e6-9126-72595dcd31f9.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417601/8875089c-7852-11e6-9126-72595dcd31f9.jpg</a>">
Raabta song from the movie Agent Vinod can be an excellent choice to make the bridal entry a decent yet a grand one! The lyrics of the song, “Kehte Hai Khuda Ne…” perfectly fit the moment, addressing the bride’s and bridegroom’s emotions to each other.</p>

<h1>Din Shagna Da</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417608/ab9a5494-7852-11e6-86e9-a37cd6077c95.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417608/ab9a5494-7852-11e6-86e9-a37cd6077c95.jpg</a>">
I think Din Shagna Da is played at almost every Indian wedding when the beautiful maiden enters. There is hardly any wedding where we won’t hear “din shagna da chadheya” playing in the background, as the bride is stepping towards her to be husband.</p>

<h1>Sajde kiye hai laakhon</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417664/e7174404-7853-11e6-85f8-5e7d181c2eb8.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417664/e7174404-7853-11e6-85f8-5e7d181c2eb8.jpg</a>">
From the legend Akshay Kumar’s movie Khatta Meetha, Sajde kiye hai laakhon is also an ideal and lovely song that can be played at the time of bridal entry. The song is soothing to the ears and would perfectly convey the heart-tendering feelings going on in the hearts of the bridegroom as well as the bride.</p>

<h1>Tum se hi</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417668/0d05ea80-7854-11e6-9f8f-8fb2a24d8fd0.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417668/0d05ea80-7854-11e6-9f8f-8fb2a24d8fd0.jpg</a>">
Another amazing song for a bride’s entry is the song “Tum se hi” from the movie Jab we met. It describes how important both of them feel about each other.</p>

<h1>Teri Ore</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417590/530a3f42-7852-11e6-9294-5bc2cd9fc9f9.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417590/530a3f42-7852-11e6-9294-5bc2cd9fc9f9.jpg</a>">
I think there cannot be a better song that would best describe the moment. As the bride moves towards her better half, the lyrics of the song match every step she takes or each moment she does, while moving forward.</p>

<h1>O Re piya</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18617466/3d618402-7ded-11e6-94e6-4fc865e880cc.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18617466/3d618402-7ded-11e6-94e6-4fc865e880cc.jpg</a>">
The song “o re piya” sung by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan is good enough to grab people’s attention as and when you enter the venue on your big day.</p>

<h1>Kabira Encore</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417691/a6a4f28a-7854-11e6-9b88-444fff453698.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18417691/a6a4f28a-7854-11e6-9b88-444fff453698.jpg</a>">
Kabira encore version is another wonderful song that can be played well when the bride enters the wedding hall. It makes the atmosphere so senti-menti that the people around start shedding tears looking at the bride.</p>

<h1>Latika’s theme song</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18617465/3d123bfe-7ded-11e6-9119-a3d8d6c156ce.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/18617465/3d123bfe-7ded-11e6-9119-a3d8d6c156ce.jpg</a>">
Sung by A.R. Rehman, from the movie Slum Dog Millionaire, this theme song is just a feeling that would definitely bring goose bumps on the skin of the listeners. The more you listen to this, the more you will feel it and love it.</p>

<p>So girls , on your big day, don’t let the DJs ruin your eye-catching entry by playing some cheap beats. Choose your own jingle for your special day!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Ways to Re-use Your Bridal Lehenga]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/05/7-ways-to-re-use-your-bridal-lehenga/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-05T21:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/05/7-ways-to-re-use-your-bridal-lehenga</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250508/6ecce898-73a1-11e6-918f-451afab578b6.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250508/6ecce898-73a1-11e6-918f-451afab578b6.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500">
When it comes to choosing the Bridal Lehenga, we just never mind the thousands of rupees as well as the long hours spent in finalizing the same. We take extra initiative to customize it according to our preference and make it more attractive in every way possible. But what happens of that precious piece of clothing, the bridal lehenga , after the wedding. Well if I am not wrong, then half of my readers will raise their hand if I say its wrapped up in a malmal ka kapda safely in the wardrobe. Well here are some great ideas to re use your bridal lehenga in a classy fashion again and again.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Lessen the volume and Cut it along.</h1>

<p>Though it may sound very harsh and painful but one can surely lessen down the motifs and heavy embellishments by simply cutting it off and toning it down in its look. With the extra kalis removed which was forcefully inserted at that time or event with the net out it will look more subtle and wearable.
<img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250132/b938d0c4-739f-11e6-8ae8-f779a4d6da8a.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250132/b938d0c4-739f-11e6-8ae8-f779a4d6da8a.jpg</a>"></p>

<h1>Switch the style to Anarkali</h1>

<p>With the help of a good tailor, its quite easy to transform your wedding attire to an embellished anarkali which looks less bridal in comparison to a bridal lehenga. The skirt and the blouse can be stitched together with a waist belt or the same can be stitched with a separate simpler blouse to get the desired effect.
<img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250242/46f88c24-73a0-11e6-878e-0abb97a8dcf3.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250242/46f88c24-73a0-11e6-878e-0abb97a8dcf3.jpg</a>"></p>

<h1>Long Kurtis with Lehengas</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250412/d8b718b0-73a0-11e6-847d-7d36d95ba8ab.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250412/d8b718b0-73a0-11e6-847d-7d36d95ba8ab.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600">
This is one of the most preferred styles that have hit the fashion world with a bang. And it is also a great way to reuse the bridal lehenga with a toned kurti and set the look. Even jackets with thin borders are also a good option to try along.</p>

<h1>Combining the bridal set with other attires</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250339/aaba739e-73a0-11e6-8b2f-a31b13861729.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250339/aaba739e-73a0-11e6-8b2f-a31b13861729.jpg</a>">
Usually the bridal lehenga teamed up with designer blouses and embellished dupatta forms the bridal set and altogether they provide the bridal feel. So the best way is to team the lehenga with a toned top, wear the blouse with a plain skirt and use the dupatta with a neutral shaded salwar kameez.</p>

<h1>Color Blocks</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250285/73bdf9e2-73a0-11e6-8379-7be272a1b291.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250285/73bdf9e2-73a0-11e6-8379-7be272a1b291.jpg</a>">
It is not always necessary to team up bridal lehenga with same colored blouses. Color blocking is quite in the fashion so if the idea is to attend some wedding function then pair up the embellished lehenga with a no work blouse of different color and just set the elegant look for the occasion.</p>

<h1>Drape it as a saree</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250339/aaba739e-73a0-11e6-8b2f-a31b13861729.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250339/aaba739e-73a0-11e6-8b2f-a31b13861729.jpg</a>">
There are many cases when the lehenga sets have a long flowing dupatta with loads of zari work on it. The best way to tone the dress down and still keep the charm is to drape the dupatta as a saree pallu and use a toned down blouse to maintain the classy look</p>

<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250508/6ecce898-73a1-11e6-918f-451afab578b6.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18250508/6ecce898-73a1-11e6-918f-451afab578b6.jpg</a>"></p>

<h1>Use as it is</h1>

<p>We all love our lehengas and honestly there are many who just don’t want to alter it. For them the best way to use it is by wearing it just as it is but with a simpler accessories, toned make up, and by letting the hair fall casually.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Destinations for Your Last Single Girls Trip]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/05/10-destinations-for-your-last-single-girls-trip/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-05T19:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/05/10-destinations-for-your-last-single-girls-trip</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239264/c88e218e-7361-11e6-8e2b-a9ef93478244.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239264/c88e218e-7361-11e6-8e2b-a9ef93478244.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600">
Ever been on an ‘only girls’ trip? If you haven’t done it or thought about it yet then go girl, do it now! Yes, here we are referring to an all-girls trip before you step in to your married life. When it comes to your last ‘single girls’ trip, it has to be something unique and epic! Here are 10 destinations for you that would let you have the time of your life.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Udaipur</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18238964/74dbdab0-735f-11e6-9a66-a01849176716.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18238964/74dbdab0-735f-11e6-9a66-a01849176716.jpg</a>">
Do forts, lakes and palaces are something that interests you? If so, here is the perfect destination for you and your girlies and that’s none other than Udaipur. This place is situated to the south of Rajasthan and coming here would make you feel as if you are here to take pleasure of the rich and cultural heritage of your motherland.</p>

<h1>Amboli</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239048/325a3c6c-7360-11e6-99a8-785bb37b40dc.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239048/325a3c6c-7360-11e6-99a8-785bb37b40dc.jpg</a>">
If you are a nature lover, you are definitely going to get mesmerized with the eye-catching beauty of Amboli, a beautiful hill station in South Maharashtra. The panoramic view of Amboli Falls and Shirgaonkar Point will make you fall in love with this place. Added to the fun, spicy Malvani food would provide you the remaining satisfaction.</p>

<h1>Rishikesh</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239104/8969b64a-7360-11e6-8184-1917d5516b77.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239104/8969b64a-7360-11e6-8184-1917d5516b77.jpg</a>">
Bring out the adrenaline junkie in you and be as adventurous as you can! Plan a road trip to Rishikesh and attend the Ganga aarti, taking place at Triven Ghat. Going Rishikesh and not doing river rafting would be regretful. Splash through the white waters of the place and give yourself a wave of thrilling fun. The treehouse café Little Buddha near Laxman Jhula is also worth a visit.</p>

<h1>Ladakh</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239194/2ad549f4-7361-11e6-8b14-d927e16ca65d.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239194/2ad549f4-7361-11e6-8b14-d927e16ca65d.jpg</a>">
Snow lovers would simply not resist going to Ladhakh. It is usually found that girls love snow all around, crystal clear lakes, all of it presenting nature at its best.</p>

<h1>Alleppey</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239198/33fdf26a-7361-11e6-90df-fc8c286f3ab1.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239198/33fdf26a-7361-11e6-90df-fc8c286f3ab1.jpg</a>">
Taking your best friends along and staying in a boathouse would be so much fun! The backwaters of Alleppey would let you have this fun with all the best girls of your life. Also, don’t forget to pay a visit to the Alleppey Beach.</p>

<h1>Nainital</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239229/7ce9e6be-7361-11e6-81de-534f8447f499.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239229/7ce9e6be-7361-11e6-81de-534f8447f499.jpg</a>">
Well, being a mini hill station of Uttarakhand, Nainital is not at all a bad option an all girls trip. The alluring Naini Lake and the mountains make this place a big hit among the travelers. The Kumaoni cuisine can also be tasted at its best when you visit this place.</p>

<h1>Ziro Valley, Arunachal Pradesh</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239113/968b815a-7360-11e6-8642-90103c7637f2.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239113/968b815a-7360-11e6-8642-90103c7637f2.jpg</a>">
Ziro Valley is counted amongst the most ‘worth watching’ places of Arunachal Pradesh. The Apatani Tribe and their rich and prosperous heritage can be a great source of knowledge about this place.</p>

<h1>Shimla</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239186/14a91f34-7361-11e6-93a3-f43aa76755a9.JPG">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239186/14a91f34-7361-11e6-93a3-f43aa76755a9.JPG</a>">
For the ladies, here is the safest hill station Shimla and along with its breathtaking beauty, don’t miss out the Toy Train.</p>

<h1>Varanasi</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239104/8969b64a-7360-11e6-8184-1917d5516b77.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239104/8969b64a-7360-11e6-8184-1917d5516b77.jpg</a>">
This divine city would arise the goddess in you and the morning boat ride is one of a kind.</p>

<h1>Sikkim</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239198/33fdf26a-7361-11e6-90df-fc8c286f3ab1.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18239198/33fdf26a-7361-11e6-90df-fc8c286f3ab1.jpg</a>">
The gorgeous valleys and the sky touching mountains accompanied by hot water springs are best of the combo that can be found in Sikkim, presenting the wow factor of north eastern India.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Do if You’re on Your Period on Your Wedding Day?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/03/period-on-your-wedding-day/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-03T19:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/09/03/period-on-your-wedding-day</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18057833/388b1bfa-6e2f-11e6-909b-e36c5d673d28.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18057833/388b1bfa-6e2f-11e6-909b-e36c5d673d28.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600">
Wedding Day is the most special day of every girl’s life. So, the special day of your life is about to arrive. Everything is planned, the perfect dress, the most romantic venue of the city, honeymoon destination, and what not? But oops! What’s happening? You suddenly realize your chums are here and you definitely did not invite them to your wedding. Well, the best way to avoid such a situation is to try and fit it into your marriage plans much before the time. If you happen to experience your period on wedding day, a few things can be done to avoid any kind of mishaps.
The first thing to be done is stay calm and composed. Keep a smile pasted to your face and enjoy the day. Here are some tips for you in case you happen to experience period on the most auspicious day of your life:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Rush to the doctor</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18058016/14777b54-6e30-11e6-872f-34f4ccc3da38.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18058016/14777b54-6e30-11e6-872f-34f4ccc3da38.jpg</a>" width="600" height="500">
In any case of uneasiness or a disease, all of us look for the doctor. Similarly, if you have these uninvited guests suddenly interrupting the special occasion of your life, doctor’s clinic is not far away! Start taking the pills two weeks before your period is due, it may delay your next period for your day. This might not be a foolproof solution though, but help’s for sure.</p>

<h1>Use a menstrual cup</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18058048/3c0b9786-6e30-11e6-96d6-e95ba80dca33.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18058048/3c0b9786-6e30-11e6-96d6-e95ba80dca33.jpg</a>">
They really do help: The menstrual cups can prove to be great help for the ‘aunt flo’ blunder that just took place. These cups can easily be inserted into the vagina and help cover the opening to the cervix. Tampons can also be used as a backup, otherwise pads are always your best friend during your menstrual cycle. These help prevent leakage. If you want to keep things tidy on your wedding night, the cup can also be inserted prior to sex.</p>

<h1>Make love on your wedding night anyways</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18057878/6d0618ee-6e2f-11e6-960c-e9cdb6fae890.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/18057878/6d0618ee-6e2f-11e6-960c-e9cdb6fae890.jpg</a>">
Due to extra sensitivity as well as lubrication, some women enjoy being intimate during their menstrual flow whereas, on the other hand, some find it more painful. Well, the whole thing entirely depends upon you and your better half. If your partner is ok with it, just go ahead and have an intercourse. Just make sure to take tiny precautions in order to avoid untidiness, like bring a towel along so that you can place it down to protect the bed.</p>

<p>In short, any of the brides can experience this mishap on the very special day of her life, but not to worry girls! There is always a solution to everything. Just don’t panic too much! Keep calm and tranquil, it’s your day girl! Enjoy it to the fullest and don’t forget to wear a smile all day long. This smile will add on to your glow on the wedding day. Discuss this with your friends and know each other’s experience in case such a thing ever happened to anyone of you.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
