<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Latest Posts on Junkjam | JunkJam Blog]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/categories/junkjam/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2016-07-26T20:38:38+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Famous Street Shops in Bangalore]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/26/5-famous-street-shops-in-banglore/"/>
    <updated>2016-07-26T19:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/26/5-famous-street-shops-in-banglore</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136045/b69cb962-5350-11e6-98c0-ec12e3b8df76.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136045/b69cb962-5350-11e6-98c0-ec12e3b8df76.jpg</a>" width="600" height="700">
Bangalore is a city that has n number of options for the perceptive bargain street shoppers. Be it colorful flower markets or the crowded second hand stores, there is something for everyone. The local street market of a city is something that can never be compared to anything else in the world. The joy of shopping gives an amazing shopping experience. The lively sounds, smells, and the wonderful sights of the city further make these shopping streets different from others. From clothes, accessories, to books, street food, medicines, flowers, and what not, Bangalore has a separate street market for everything that one would like to buy. Here is a list of 5 famous street shops in Bangalore where the shopaholics would love to go:</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Commercial Street</h1>

<p><img class="right <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136023/8bad626a-5350-11e6-94d4-303c018aa217.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136023/8bad626a-5350-11e6-94d4-303c018aa217.jpg</a>" width="500" height="500">
Commercial Street is one of the most popular shopping areas that has stores selling every style of clothing, accessories, jewellery, shoes, and much more. Every time you pay a visit to this street, you will find something new to shop for. All you need to do is bargain to your heart’s content. The more you bargain here, the less amount you will have to pay for the items that you purchase.</p>

<h1>Avenue Road</h1>

<p>The avenue road is an eternally crowded one way street that is famous for food carts, stationary shops, shops selling jewellery, and textiles. It is the home to such interesting things that no one can find anywhere else in the city. Here, second hand books are available at cheap rates and the ones who want to sell unused books are also welcomed. This makes it an ideal place for students as well as the book lovers due to the buying and selling of second hand books.
<img class="<a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136130/3b64417e-5351-11e6-9df7-f47ac1f48628.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136130/3b64417e-5351-11e6-9df7-f47ac1f48628.jpg</a>"></p>

<h1>Chickpet</h1>

<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136297/2593edc6-5352-11e6-847d-ed75721a53b7.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136297/2593edc6-5352-11e6-847d-ed75721a53b7.jpg</a>">
<img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136301/2836b3d8-5352-11e6-920c-bba3b91475b9.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136301/2836b3d8-5352-11e6-920c-bba3b91475b9.jpg</a>">
Chickpet is counted among the city’s oldest commercial districts and is famous for a wide variety of saris as well as wholesale dress materials that are available at reasonable prices. Also, you don’t need to compromise with the quality. Bangles at Balepet, jewellery at Raja market, and locally made musical instruments at Nagarthapet are also worth a purchase when you visit this place.
<img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136308/2cc06c78-5352-11e6-8cd2-d2f02494d065.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136308/2cc06c78-5352-11e6-8cd2-d2f02494d065.jpg</a>"></p>

<h1>Gandhi Bazaar</h1>

<p>Being city’s most vibrant streets, this market is known for trinkets, traditional religious items, textiles, silk saris, and local medicines. The best form of this shopping place can best be seen in the evenings and at the time of festivals. Offering lip smacking street food, a large number of people are gathered at the popular eateries, the most famous being Vidyarthi Bhavan.
<img class="<a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136480/40b20cd6-5353-11e6-9f81-2d7755273e49.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136480/40b20cd6-5353-11e6-9f81-2d7755273e49.jpg</a>"></p>

<h1>City Market</h1>

<p><img class="right <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136582/e2cf79c2-5353-11e6-81a6-9f2df47fb356.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136582/e2cf79c2-5353-11e6-81a6-9f2df47fb356.jpg</a>" width="500" height="500">
The city market is famous for colorful flowers, vegetables, and fresh fruits and several kilos of flowers are sold here every day. Vendors all over the city buy their stock from this market. The quality of flora, vegetables, and fruits make this place a must visit. If you get here early in the morning, you will be able to buy the best produce. The condition of the place is little messy but the fresh stock available here is a must to see and buy.
<img class="<a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136611/0af7b400-5354-11e6-98ab-de4a6d9144f3.jpeg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17136611/0af7b400-5354-11e6-98ab-de4a6d9144f3.jpeg</a>"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Fashion Accessories for Men]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/24/top-fashion-accessories-for-men/"/>
    <updated>2016-07-24T23:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/24/top-fashion-accessories-for-men</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17110837/7c7bebc0-52bc-11e6-881d-6f39d8bbc336.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/17110837/7c7bebc0-52bc-11e6-881d-6f39d8bbc336.jpg</a>" width="450" height="600" title="Fashion Accessories for Men" >
Most of the people will concur with the epigram &ldquo;women&rsquo;s fashion is much more diverse than men!!&rdquo;. But who says accessories are for women only? Here are top 10 accessories that can add flavour and color to any outfit to fit the preferences of any men out there.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>1. Watch</h2>

<p><img class="right <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17089993/b960e928-5249-11e6-8d5b-81279774db38.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17089993/b960e928-5249-11e6-8d5b-81279774db38.jpg</a>" width="250" height="200">
A wrist watch is the most conventional accessory a man can invest in. It exudes simplicity while adding style to your personality. it is one of the most acceptable men&rsquo;s accessory. Mechanical, chronograph, leather strap watches are the latest trends this season.</p>

<h2>2. Tie</h2>

<p>A tie is one accessory that adds life to any men&rsquo;s attire. Various mutants include bow-tie, necktie, ascots. A tie radiates class and confidence. Pair up your suit with multicolor, printed , textured, silk ties this summer.
<img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17089994/bb5c44d4-5249-11e6-933b-584c8de947e3.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17089994/bb5c44d4-5249-11e6-933b-584c8de947e3.jpg</a>" width="400" height="400"></p>

<h2>3. Pocket Squares</h2>

<p>Regardless of this recently added fashion statement pocket squares have become a perfect addition to men&rsquo;s wardrobe. How to pair them up?? well chose a totally contrast pocket square. no matchy-matchy!!GO for a colorful choice that isn&rsquo;t too in-your-face.
<img class="right <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17090004/ca3d60d2-5249-11e6-8a99-5aa692b481b3.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17090004/ca3d60d2-5249-11e6-8a99-5aa692b481b3.jpg</a>" width="300" height="200"></p>

<h2>4. Wallet</h2>

<p>Black and brown leather wallets for men are perennial. The Hobo Millie Clutch and Elephant wallets are gaining popularity these days. Totally cool isnt it?
<img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17090007/cde62ce6-5249-11e6-9f52-04feb9ea4fa2.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17090007/cde62ce6-5249-11e6-9f52-04feb9ea4fa2.jpg</a>"></p>

<h2>5. Money clip</h2>

<p>This accessory offers a simple and convenient approach to handle your cash. Its graceful and elegant style makes it a great alternative to carry your money. While other men are still confused as to what is better, a wallet or a money clip, you grab your painted m-clip, chrome or silver plated money clip to earn brownie points in impressing ladies out there!
<img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17089995/bdeff6f0-5249-11e6-9058-4ef2de814599.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17089995/bdeff6f0-5249-11e6-9058-4ef2de814599.jpg</a>" width="500" height="200"></p>

<h2>6. Card Holders</h2>

<p>Card holders can be a superb approach to speak to a level of professional skill. They also serve as a great way to gift a business associate. Stainless steel and custom fabric card holders are go-go this season.
<img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17090000/c29821dc-5249-11e6-87ac-53a347664d83.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17090000/c29821dc-5249-11e6-87ac-53a347664d83.jpg</a>" width="600" height="500"></p>

<h2>7. Jewellery for men</h2>

<p><img class="right <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17089998/c068dbfe-5249-11e6-843b-8982834315f5.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17089998/c068dbfe-5249-11e6-843b-8982834315f5.jpg</a>">
Yes unsual it seems,, but jewellery for men is gaining popularity now-a-days. Common jewellery for men is the wedding ring. THe most effective way for a man to carry jewellery is to be comfortable about it. Ear studs, copper bracelets, lapel pins, beaded necklace are some well executed jewellery intended for men.</p>

<h2>8. Belt</h2>

<p>Belt is a safe and easy pick accessory for men. It no longer serves as a tool for holding mens trouser but a great style statement. Wide buckles and a webbed, fabric version with a double-D buckle fastening works well for this summer.
<img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17090002/c430ffbe-5249-11e6-826f-77f4fee2771a.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17090002/c430ffbe-5249-11e6-826f-77f4fee2771a.jpg</a>" width="750" height="400"></p>

<h2>9. Sunglasses</h2>

<p>Sunglasses, aviators, shades are one of the accessory men wear on their face. They are a must have for glamorous, High Fashion look. Tortoiseshell frames and sleek metal are latest fashion trends..
<img class="right <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17090005/cbff5c18-5249-11e6-9fdb-d111dd013d44.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17090005/cbff5c18-5249-11e6-9fdb-d111dd013d44.jpg</a>"></p>

<h2>10. Cuff links</h2>

<p>Well you must first know what are cufflinks?? Cufflinks are tools for fastening shirt cuffs closed. They add variety and shape to men&rsquo;s outfit. Chain link and stud cufflinks are perfect for all your wedding functions and other formal occasions.
<img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17090003/c5e23d82-5249-11e6-8d98-5ec4b1c25279.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13364909/17090003/c5e23d82-5249-11e6-8d98-5ec4b1c25279.jpg</a>" width="700" height="500"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tibetan Market for Budget Shopping in Delhi]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/20/tibetan-market-for-budget-shopping-in-delhi/"/>
    <updated>2016-07-20T23:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/20/tibetan-market-for-budget-shopping-in-delhi</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16996255/1f8f8d00-4ece-11e6-94f0-30b4cb3b5cc8.jpeg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16996255/1f8f8d00-4ece-11e6-94f0-30b4cb3b5cc8.jpeg</a>" width="500" height="650" title="Tibetan Market New Delhi" >
What is the greatest highlight of Delhi shopping? Many may answer, that shopping in the cosmopolitan Delhi malls has revolutionized the shopping experience. But the hidden truth is different. Though the city malls are quite attractive but in comparison to the charm and attraction of the Delhi street markets, it’s nothing. The most convenient proof of the statement is the overcrowded; jam packed areas of the age old traditional markets of Delhi throughout the year.
One of such a traditional market is the Tibetan Market located on the western side of Janpath.  From designer clothing to stylish accessories, home décor to Tibetan artifacts, footwear to woolen clothes get it all in best quality and that too in throw back prices. Seems unbelievable? Well not, the market is one of the most preferred shopping destinations in the capital city.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Historical Truths</h1>

<p><img class="right  <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16996521/57465494-4ecf-11e6-9755-343d25be65a8.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16996521/57465494-4ecf-11e6-9755-343d25be65a8.jpg</a>">
Originally the place was designed to house in Tibetan refugees in 1960. But what initiated as a small locality dedicated to the fugitives soon got transferred into one of the popular shopping locations of the city. It is the rising fame of the market with its cheap price and quality products that it soon became a tourist spot in Delhi and became christened with the name, the Monastery market.
<img class="<a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16996295/4349bcb6-4ece-11e6-834e-701f23c28cec.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16996295/4349bcb6-4ece-11e6-834e-701f23c28cec.jpg</a>"></p>

<h1>What remains in Offer for you?</h1>

<p>Though Tibetan market has a host of products to offer, it is known a lot for its resplendent collection of woolen garments. Mostly these are homemade winter wears and they are sold at unbelievable low prices. Shawls, jackets and designer cloaks all remain available here. Apart from winter wears, the next best thing available here is the Tibetan artifacts which includes paintings, antiques, statues, incense , wooden lamps and classical jewellery. Leather products and footwear are also quite cheap here. The small Tibetan world also holds a wide collection of exquisite Lucky charms, Tibetan bric-a-brac , Om danglers, Tibetan souvenirs and many other exclusive products. In a nutshell, it’s Little Tibet away from Tibet.
<img class="<a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16996570/7db09720-4ecf-11e6-8e89-96f858d2deba.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16996570/7db09720-4ecf-11e6-8e89-96f858d2deba.jpg</a>"></p>

<h1>Food to Savor in Tibetan Market</h1>

<p>Shoppers usually are great foodies too. And even if they are not, shopping for stretched hours calls for re energizing with delicious food which gets fulfilled in the market with a wide collection of flavors from Tibet. Visit Wongdhen House or Zomsa and enjoy the wide variety of Tibetan foods like chowmein, momo, thupkas etc in its authentic flavor.
So what are you waiting for, get set go to explore the traditionally rich authentic Monastery market. The place is quite close to ISBT flyover and the nearest metro station is Kashmiri Gate. Even the Old Delhi Railway station is based closeby at a distance of 3kms with regular public buses plying towards the market area. The market usually remains open from 11 in the morning and stays buzzing till 8:30 to 9 in the evening. It is functional on all days of the week except Monday.
Undoubtedly, it is one of the cheapest and the best markets in the city and the must visit for all.
<img class="<a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16996600/9ee50246-4ecf-11e6-888a-a90d2332f200.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16996600/9ee50246-4ecf-11e6-888a-a90d2332f200.jpg</a>"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2 Best Places to Go Street Shopping in Mumbai]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/19/2-best-places-to-go-street-shopping-in-mumbai/"/>
    <updated>2016-07-19T23:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/19/2-best-places-to-go-street-shopping-in-mumbai</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16958979/837dee66-4e00-11e6-970a-fda168654bf9.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16958979/837dee66-4e00-11e6-970a-fda168654bf9.jpg</a>" width="500" height="650" title="Street Market Mumbai" >
Mumbai is the City of Dreams for many and certainly a shopper’s delight. Where there are hub of designer shops ranging from Gucci, Louis Vuitton, Burberry to Versache , there are also lot of street markets in Mumbai where you can shop at the cheapest rates. These street markets are very crowded as one can find variety of items here, ranging from first copy of branded clothes, vintage items, Chinese gadgets, books and finger licking street food. Mumbai Street markets are a blessing for all the college going girls as well as the struggling actresses who don’t have much money to buy branded dresses for their photo shoots or celebrity parties. Here I am listing 2 Best Places to Go Street Shopping in Mumbai</p>

<!-- more -->


<p><img class="<a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16959160/458c7db0-4e01-11e6-88ae-27ad32a0b177.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16959160/458c7db0-4e01-11e6-88ae-27ad32a0b177.jpg</a>"></p>

<h1>Colaba Causeway</h1>

<p>Located in the area of Southern Mumbai, Colaba Causeway is one of the best street markets in Mumbai. This market is a huge one which stretches over several meters and offers all kind of items. You name the item and you can find it here in this market, from artificial jewellery, handicrafts, leather items, sunglasses, stoles and scarves, antique items, books , fashionable clothes, books, bags, bangles to juttis. If you are looking for any personalized gift for a friend then you can also find vendors who can write messages on a single rice grain and engrave it into a locket or key chain. Even if the prices seem to be very reasonable but still you can bargain to a great extent and save your valuable money. Here you will not only find the local people of Mumbai but also foreigners shopping, as this market is only a few kilometers away from Taj Hotel and other iconic landmarks like Gateway of India. If you want to watch a movie then you can also go to one of the oldest Theatre, Regal Cinema, which is located near the market.
<img class="<a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16958980/840beffe-4e00-11e6-9476-f153a98d8c1d.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16958980/840beffe-4e00-11e6-9476-f153a98d8c1d.jpg</a>">
<img class="right <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16958978/836996aa-4e00-11e6-9c7d-0592edcaa868.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16958978/836996aa-4e00-11e6-9c7d-0592edcaa868.jpg</a>"></p>

<h1>Fashion Street</h1>

<p>Another amazing shopping area in Mumbai is the famous Fashion Street, which perfectly fits its name. Here, you will find all the latest fashion clothes, accessories, cosmetics, and much more at affordable prices. These also include first copies of popular brands. Situated in South Mumbai, this street is a cluster of about 385 street side clothing shops placed on MG Road near Azad Maidan, opposite to Bombay Gymkhana. Along with being a favorite shopping street of the locals as well as the visitors, it is also a popular tourist destination located opposite to VSNL office building at MG Road. As we know, the more you bargain, the better price you fetch for particular apparel, so another advantage of shopping here is that it is well known for bargaining. Not only this, but in order to show concern for environment, in January 2011, as a part of green drive of BMC in collaboration with Fashion Street Shop Owners’ Association, the market at Fashion Street banned the use of plastic bags and polybags, and started using paper bags, made by the training workshop of the National Association of the Blind.
<img class="<a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16959165/4bab41f4-4e01-11e6-9d83-407c45e521c5.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16959165/4bab41f4-4e01-11e6-9d83-407c45e521c5.jpg</a>">
<img class="<a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16959161/47682a26-4e01-11e6-8515-23d94f37e41f.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/16959161/47682a26-4e01-11e6-8515-23d94f37e41f.jpg</a>"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Freshest Pre-Fall 16 Collections Straight From the Runway!]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/16/the-freshest-pre-fall-2016-collections-straight-from-the-runway/"/>
    <updated>2016-07-16T13:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/16/the-freshest-pre-fall-2016-collections-straight-from-the-runway</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893405/4bdc7c74-4b54-11e6-8489-72c814ebbc59.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893405/4bdc7c74-4b54-11e6-8489-72c814ebbc59.jpg</a>" width="360" height="600" title="Pre Fall 2016" >
Keeping track of what is in-trend is quite a task and it can be really tough to stay updated with what is on the shop floor. To refresh and pepper your season with the latest collection, here are the freshest Pre-Fall’ 16 collections straight from the runway. The leopard prints and pastel hues are long-gone. It’s time to welcome the belted dresses, nerve-wrecking T-shirt look and denim shorts to stuff your wardrobe for the coming season.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893388/4b54bba4-4b54-11e6-8f93-01ad8b824da8.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893388/4b54bba4-4b54-11e6-8f93-01ad8b824da8.jpg</a>" width="500" height="650"></p>

<h1>Prep your look for the season:</h1>

<h2>1. Office Casuals</h2>

<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893389/4b581100-4b54-11e6-9585-d4d5ae1b9a77.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893389/4b581100-4b54-11e6-9585-d4d5ae1b9a77.jpg</a>" width="360" height="600">
<img class="right <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893392/4b5bb97c-4b54-11e6-9f06-4878565ec8cf.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893392/4b5bb97c-4b54-11e6-9f06-4878565ec8cf.jpg</a>" width="360" height="600">
When you’re an office-goer and you have the freedom to wear whatever you want, instead of a professional look you can also opt for an office-casual look. Patchwork jeans or vintage dresses can be a hit as well. We are not hinting at sweaty pants or revealing outfits but have you thought about off-shoulder tops or dresses?
<img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893391/4b590c9a-4b54-11e6-9350-b9f2c9ede222.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893391/4b590c9a-4b54-11e6-9350-b9f2c9ede222.jpg</a>">
The off-shoulder trend has fevered at an alarming pace and if you do not like to expose your arms, off-shoulders are at rescue for your arms. If you wish to wear the off-shoulder look at office you can pair the outfit with cigarette pants or pinstripe skirt, tie a bun and handle the corporate world in style.</p>

<h2>2. Party Popper</h2>

<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893393/4b5d1d4e-4b54-11e6-94dd-af07accee2c4.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893393/4b5d1d4e-4b54-11e6-94dd-af07accee2c4.jpg</a>" width="360" height="600">
<img class="right <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893404/4bdaeda0-4b54-11e6-8fc6-f8ba4ec90566.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893404/4bdaeda0-4b54-11e6-8fc6-f8ba4ec90566.jpg</a>" width="360" height="600">
The belted dresses are perhaps, the first choice for this Pre-Fall. These belted dresses are ultra-flattering on various body types and you can pull them off easily ‘because they’re guaranteed to start a legacy with cohorts admiring your style.
<img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893394/4b8fcdca-4b54-11e6-8f12-75e18ab2d4a3.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893394/4b8fcdca-4b54-11e6-8f12-75e18ab2d4a3.jpg</a>">
Select a dress that is breeze-friendly and isn’t too sticky considering the weather and to note the style, nothing would exhibit your glowing skin like these belted dresses with a tad bit lower hemline, that’s just about it.</p>

<h2>3. The T-Shirt Look</h2>

<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893396/4b950038-4b54-11e6-95fb-f837eb72939b.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893396/4b950038-4b54-11e6-95fb-f837eb72939b.jpg</a>" width="360" height="600">
<img class="right <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893397/4b975324-4b54-11e6-8fd4-1e27b266d20c.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893397/4b975324-4b54-11e6-8fd4-1e27b266d20c.jpg</a>" width="360" height="600">
Its the Pre-Fall season and all we wish to do is to Baywatch or perhaps, drink margaritas and wear T-shirts, jeans or shorts but if you are in a 9 to 5 job you can’t really live this dream, can you? Me neither. If you are an office goer, T-shirts can be worn just when you get the knack to pull-off the T-Shirt look.
<img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893395/4b93b9ee-4b54-11e6-8a96-469928486e88.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893395/4b93b9ee-4b54-11e6-8a96-469928486e88.jpg</a>">
A cropped T-shirt with a high-waist pencil skirt is a hit. Or a plain T-shirt with a midi-skirt can do wonders for you. Why don’t you pull off this T-shirt look? Stay comfortable yet corporate.</p>

<h2>4. Shorts-in-Style</h2>

<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893398/4b9a3ce2-4b54-11e6-8ef9-556d9973b4c9.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893398/4b9a3ce2-4b54-11e6-8ef9-556d9973b4c9.jpg</a>" width="360" height="600">
<img class="right <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893402/4bd06a6a-4b54-11e6-9074-8a032b647b57.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893402/4bd06a6a-4b54-11e6-9074-8a032b647b57.jpg</a>" width="360" height="300">
Well! Don&rsquo;t you want to pull out those denim shorts hanging in your closet and take to the road in the perfect street style? Yes, it’s August and you’re exactly thinking what we’re thinking. If you are bored to wear the cutoffs with a pretty tank or with a bodysuit, it’s finally time to tick-present on the denim shorts waiting to be worn.
<img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893399/4b9cbe90-4b54-11e6-9776-3dee109b2379.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893399/4b9cbe90-4b54-11e6-9776-3dee109b2379.jpg</a>">
Prep-up and play with the wardrobe essentials to pull-off a wonderful look. You can also wear denim shorts with gladiators, a belt bag and tank top or a crop top. It preps up the street style and looks just perfect.</p>

<h2>5. Mix-and-Match</h2>

<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893400/4bceedf2-4b54-11e6-9d4b-09fbe74319ba.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893400/4bceedf2-4b54-11e6-9d4b-09fbe74319ba.jpg</a>" width="360" height="600">
<img class="right <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893403/4bd3e0dc-4b54-11e6-9805-8a22543971cf.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893403/4bd3e0dc-4b54-11e6-9805-8a22543971cf.jpg</a>" width="360" height="600">
It&rsquo;s time to mix and match bright and shiny hues like lemon yellow, cherry red, emerald green as it pepper up the entire outfit and makes one look, attractive and pretty. Just in case you fear bright hues, you have no idea how the mix-and-match can swing your entire attire into an exceptionally striking one. What say?
<img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893401/4bd023f2-4b54-11e6-9463-c948426a0a4a.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893401/4bd023f2-4b54-11e6-9463-c948426a0a4a.jpg</a>">
Lemon yellow shirt dress prepped up with gold accessories or an emerald green with brown knee-length boots would surely steal many glances around.
<img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893390/4b58e2e2-4b54-11e6-9689-af80213e9e63.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16893390/4b58e2e2-4b54-11e6-9689-af80213e9e63.jpg</a>">
The Pre Fall &lsquo;16 collection is all about mixing and matching the bright hues and staying comfortable in whatever you wear. Because experimenting with style and trying out new looks is just so fashionista-type. Try out these looks and all eyes will be on you.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
