<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Latest Posts on Junkjam | JunkJam Blog - Street Market! Fashion! LifeStyle!]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/categories/junkjam/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2017-04-09T23:40:16+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are You in a Long Distance Relationships?? Here Are 6 Awesome Valentine Day Ideas for You.]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2017/02/12/6-awesome-valentine-day-ideas-for-ldr/"/>
    <updated>2017-02-12T19:36:03+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2017/02/12/6-awesome-valentine-day-ideas-for-ldr</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left  <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/22875106/ded768da-f1ef-11e6-95b0-08170d5f0585.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/22875106/ded768da-f1ef-11e6-95b0-08170d5f0585.jpg</a>" width="400" height="600">
With February 14 is so so close, you may be wondering how to celebrate Valentine’s Day when you’re in a long-distance relationship.</p>

<p>Hey! You’re certainly not alone — 14 million couples report being in a long-distance relationship, according to a study by Statistic Brain.</p>

<p>One have said that “One of the keys to a successful LDR is to maintain healthy levels of intimacy and closeness, especially during Valentine’s Day”
So, what should you give to your honey bee, to make her feel loved?  The answer to this question is presented here with some awesome ideas.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>1.   Start your Day with Facetime, Skype - Any Video Calling.</h2>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/22875100/dea88cb8-f1ef-11e6-8ea6-cb7ea4123836.png">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/22875100/dea88cb8-f1ef-11e6-8ea6-cb7ea4123836.png</a>" width="400" height="500"></p>

<h2>2.   Send him/her a small surprise gift.</h2>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/22875099/dea34208-f1ef-11e6-9d6d-d3fc905998b3.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/22875099/dea34208-f1ef-11e6-9d6d-d3fc905998b3.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500"></p>

<h2>3.   Send him/her Surprising Notes and tell how much you love in different ways.</h2>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/22875102/dea8923a-f1ef-11e6-8550-56a348a68de7.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/22875102/dea8923a-f1ef-11e6-8550-56a348a68de7.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500"></p>

<h2>4.   Make a collage, upload it on your social media and tag them with beautiful hash tags.</h2>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/22875101/dea88df8-f1ef-11e6-82c6-180d35f1681a.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/22875101/dea88df8-f1ef-11e6-82c6-180d35f1681a.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500"></p>

<h2>5.   Have an Online dinner date.</h2>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/22875105/deb00380-f1ef-11e6-927f-91ac33f1c32e.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/22875105/deb00380-f1ef-11e6-927f-91ac33f1c32e.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500"></p>

<h2>6.   Reach &amp; Surprise him/her at their place.</h2>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/22875103/deab0178-f1ef-11e6-92b3-5de0357809e5.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/22875103/deab0178-f1ef-11e6-92b3-5de0357809e5.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500"></p>

<p>Hope you will have a wonderful,loving &amp; adorable valentine day.. Love yaa.!!!!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Must Haves if Applying for a Foreign College]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2017/02/07/6-must-haves-if-applying-for-a-foreign-college/"/>
    <updated>2017-02-07T19:36:03+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2017/02/07/6-must-haves-if-applying-for-a-foreign-college</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22694596/da270524-ed6d-11e6-816a-b32e9d91c746.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/22694596/da270524-ed6d-11e6-816a-b32e9d91c746.jpg</a>" width="470" height="600">
If a study abroad programme seems appealing to you and you’ve applied or been selected and you are now super-duper excited about the abroad adventure. Well, congratulations! The next step is to prepare yourself for the trip. So make a probable questionnaire and kick start your preparation. Here we have complied 6 must have points in your to-do list while planning your trip.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Passport and Visa</h2>

<p>Without a passport, your abroad trip is impossible. If you already owned one, make sure that it’s not expired or won’t expire within 6 months of your intended return to the place you have opted for study. Also, check with other credentials related to the passport.</p>

<p>For newbies, it’s always advisable to apply for it before you plan a trip because the process may take a little time and also cuts the end-time hassle. One can also apply online, make payment and fix a schedule. It’s the easiest way to apply for a passport these days.</p>

<p>In addition to a passport, a traveller may need a visa to visit his/her dream country. Different countries have different visa requirements. In this regards, you will have to do some research and find out the required list. Or you can approach the nearest embassy as well. Like a passport, visa applications also takes several months to process so delay is non-advisable.</p>

<p>Apart from this, there are few countries, which allow the students to enter without a visa for 90 days. So, if your dream country comes under this umbrella than it’ll be an icing on the cake.</p>

<h2>Ensure You Have a Travel Insurance Plan</h2>

<p>While traveling abroad it is a must that you are covered by an accidental insurance plan.</p>

<p>What are Things that a Travel Insurance Covers?</p>

<ul>
<li>Coverage at the time of flight is delayed/cancelled</li>
<li>Lost luggage</li>
<li>Stolen personal belongings</li>
<li>Evacuation in the case of a health emergency or natural disaster</li>
</ul>


<p>Moreover, you can avail health insurance too from the Council of International Educational Exchange.</p>

<h2>Find a Plane Ticket at Cheapest Price: You’re Lucky</h2>

<p>Finding a plane ticket as per your budget and criteria is like an art of timing and luck. The fares are always unexpected and may vary depending on when you want to fly and to where you want to buy your tickets. There are various agencies though, you can compare the fares as well. Additionally, there are student travel agencies too who offer inexpensive tickets for students travelling abroad. You can approach them too.</p>

<h2>Research Your Destination</h2>

<p>Do some homework before flying to your destination. By knowing briefly about your soon-to-be home’s culture, language, history, economy, geography, you can ease your stay there.</p>

<h2>Settle with the Money</h2>

<p>Get an online account of you don’t have. It will be easier for you to use ATM/debit or credit cards to get cash in the local currency.</p>

<p>Moreover, never forget to inform your current bank that you are flying. Otherwise, you risk getting locked out of your account or they might flag it as a fraud.</p>

<p>Also, get some cash with you and don’t forget it the convert to the required currency. You can find the moneychangers at airport or metro stations.</p>

<h2>Finally Start Packing</h2>

<p>Now come to the last stage when you are done with all the documentations and financial requirements, start packing up. Kindly double check with your airlines to learn their luggage allowances to avoid fees. The less baggage you carry, the lesser are the chances of getting charged.</p>

<p>Finally, prepare yourself mentally, cross check everything that you have packed, especially the documents. Though you can never expect to be fully prepared upon arrival, we hope these tips will help you to plan your trip to your dream destination. Happy flight!!!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[OMG: 10 Insane Things Your Favourite Celebrities Believe!!!]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2017/01/15/omg-10-insane-things-your-favourite-celebrities-believe/"/>
    <updated>2017-01-15T12:47:35+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2017/01/15/omg-10-insane-things-your-favourite-celebrities-believe</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21961000/61034542-db23-11e6-9134-d49d9277a01c.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21961000/61034542-db23-11e6-9134-d49d9277a01c.jpg</a>">
Well we all love Bollywood’s Thumkas and jhatkas without NO doubts but we hear about their insane believes, it will straight forwardly put all us into persist snigger! Superstition is a senseless fear of God that NOT only show our much loved stars into disgust situations but also proof that Everyone is NOT perfect though as it sees..</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>So guys coming back to the track, let’s make your heart little more giggles and request our superstars to be little sensible in this approach.</p>

<h1>10 Shilpa Shetty</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960991/60b112ae-db23-11e6-9836-f02fa61cf7ea.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960991/60b112ae-db23-11e6-9836-f02fa61cf7ea.jpg</a>" title="Shilpa Shetty" ></p>

<p>Our number 10 celebrity is our favourite dhumkas girl. This superstar, super model and modern Entrepreneur that each girl want to be like has lot s more to stay herself practical to keep out of her laughing list.</p>

<p>As confessed by this beautiful diva herself, Shetty always wear “TWO” watches during cricket matches of IPL.  It is NOT all, the way she cross her legs when oppositions team bats is ACTUALLY insane.</p>

<p>Shilpa we love you and millions of your fans don’t want you to have such senseless fear or FAITH.</p>

<h1>9 Bipasha Basu</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960992/60b958ce-db23-11e6-96ce-5e3b06078e11.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960992/60b958ce-db23-11e6-96ce-5e3b06078e11.jpg</a>" title="Bipasha Basu" ></p>

<p>Always on the news for her fitness and over sensuous body, now this bollywood queen caught in our list with her over senseless thinking on the FEAR or faith over devil in particular. This Bengali sexy diva is always seen in horror movie but our reader will be chuckle after knowing her INSANE flicks for keeping lemon and green chillies in car every Saturday to keep her safe from evil eye.</p>

<p>Well bips, fearing from BHOOOOOOOT is not a cool idea.</p>

<h1>8 Katrina Kaif</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960993/60c3640e-db23-11e6-8cec-ed662be5242f.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960993/60c3640e-db23-11e6-8cec-ed662be5242f.jpg</a>" title="Katrina Kaif" ></p>

<p>Our bollywood Barbie doll is always in the mind for her sexy face and controversial love relationships. But this time she is stuck with our list for her superstitious belief of dargah of Sufi saint Khwaja Moinuddin Chisti in Ajmer before of movie release date.</p>

<p>Devotion is good kat but making it little pernickety and obligatory each time surely make you look insane.</p>

<h1>7 Deepika Padukone</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960994/60c5ee68-db23-11e6-8636-b73c68db6b88.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960994/60c5ee68-db23-11e6-8636-b73c68db6b88.jpg</a>" title="Deepika Padukone" ></p>

<p>After Katrina, Deepika is our next number to have insensible faith that sure said to be insane.  Going with the flow as Kat, she visits Siddhivinayak Temple in Prabhadevi.
Well visiting temple is NOT weird, but making it OBLIGATERY is INSANE.</p>

<h1>6 Ajay Devgn</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960995/60c97baa-db23-11e6-831a-226f32d33843.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960995/60c97baa-db23-11e6-831a-226f32d33843.jpg</a>" title="Ajay Devgn" ></p>

<p>Well guys DONT blame me if you ACTUALLY do the Dublicheaked with th google for this as it is 100% TRUE  or NOT that out KJos hubby has REMOVED “a” from his surname to have successful career!</p>

<p>I mean REALLY????</p>

<p>Mummy told us that hard work ke liye there is NO short “CUTS&hellip; “</p>

<p>This kind of INSANE things is NOT expected with you Mr. devgAn.. as you seems to be sensible in beginning.</p>

<h1>5 Sanjay Dutt</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960996/60ce3b22-db23-11e6-9962-da20209b3697.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960996/60ce3b22-db23-11e6-9962-da20209b3697.jpg</a>" title="Sanjay Dutt" ></p>

<p>Well I am sure that all of my readers must have watched Munna bhai Mbbs? Yes?
Have you remember our favourite Munna have do heart touching gandhigiri to remove that Pandit taboo for mangalic vivah..</p>

<p>Yes yes yes ..</p>

<p>So taking our number 5, our Munna Bhai has ACTUALLY broken our heart with his INSANE thing for choosing Number 45 45 each time and called as its good luck charm.</p>

<p>We loved you for what you done in the movie and NOW you are making us regret with this 4545 drama Munna..</p>

<p>Grow up Munna!!!</p>

<h1>4 Aamir Khan</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960997/60f10792-db23-11e6-8f8a-371a2acf3392.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960997/60f10792-db23-11e6-8f8a-371a2acf3392.jpg</a>" title="Aamir Khan" ></p>

<p>oOops Aamir is  ACTUALLY a heart breaking name to see in this list for sure. Having famous to be called as Mr. Perfectionist in Bollywood industry and looked up by millions of young minds, this INSANE thing is NOT so cool.</p>

<p>Our readers will be thrill to know that such a contemporary minded actor and liberated person who was recently loved for his PK movie who actually a slap for melo drama for superstitions is all just a reel play!</p>

<p>Our Mr. Perfectionist have a COMPULTION to release his movies on Christmas. List is quite long Taare Zameen Par, Ghajini, 3 Idiots, Dhoom 3 and PK.</p>

<p>Poor thing!!! PK was REEL not REAL.</p>

<h1>3 Kareena Kapoor Khan</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960998/60f63708-db23-11e6-8f28-43402f375d41.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960998/60f63708-db23-11e6-8f28-43402f375d41.jpg</a>" title="Kareena Kapoor Khan" ></p>

<p>Our bebo has taken 3rd positions in the race for her insane things in this list. You want to know how? She being the hottest and most followed on the bollywood theme lines, she is now in the laughing stalks for her obsession for NUMBER 3 on the car plates.</p>

<p>Bebo you have to be trend setters for all your co actors for NOT doing this INSANE harkate. We love you and these things are NOT #3</p>

<h1>2 Salman Khan</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960999/61003d5c-db23-11e6-88c9-ded759e37232.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21960999/61003d5c-db23-11e6-88c9-ded759e37232.jpg</a>" title="Salman Khan" ></p>

<p>He is hot and handsome, BUT surely this time he is NOT so COOL!</p>

<p>Our being human hero and Bigg boss super star, is also INSANE for trending up with superstition tradition with his sexy looking though, blue sapphire bracelet.</p>

<p>Change it salu, we know You Can!!!</p>

<h1>1 Shah Rukh Khan</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21961000/61034542-db23-11e6-9134-d49d9277a01c.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21961000/61034542-db23-11e6-9134-d49d9277a01c.jpg</a>" title="Shah Rukh Khan" >
KING Khan with NOT much doubt takes our TOP position in our list with his number 555 superstitious trend.</p>

<p>It is INSANE. IT is ILLOGICAL!!!</p>

<p>I hope you all love this INSANE list. DONT follow it and make a change!!!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Your Child Picking the Right Career Option?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/12/21/is-your-child-picking-the-right-career-option/"/>
    <updated>2016-12-21T07:45:27+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/12/21/is-your-child-picking-the-right-career-option</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375268/56872186-c752-11e6-8ceb-2216eee23654.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375268/56872186-c752-11e6-8ceb-2216eee23654.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500">
A simple effort of yours can make great change in terms of selecting the right career for your child!</p>

<p>Being a parent, has this question ever strike on your mind? Have you ever observed, towards what your little one is inclining more? In the daily hustle, parents often forget to notice those silly but important deeds of their child, which in a long run can be a big problem to tackle with. The skill of being a good parent Is not a rocket science. Yes, it can be obtained over the time. In today’s world, where academics, extra-curricular activities and distractions in the term of electronic gadgets, acquire children’s priority time, it is tough to communicate with them. However, a simple effort in this regard can make a great change.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>How to choose a right career is quite a common question floating in every students’ mind after completing the schooling. Since this is the peak time to find the right path and follow it enthusiastically, a student must be aware of his aptitude and preferences. One wrong decision might lead you to regret for lifetime. A well- structured career is an essential element to chase a successful life and here, parents can set the example as epitome of success, as they have already experienced the same phase.</p>

<p>In this article, we will give you an idea about how to help your child in choosing the right career path. Moreover, the DO’s and DON’T given here will help you in evaluate your parental role.</p>

<h2>Keep an Eye on these Imperatives:</h2>

<p>There are a few factors, which make the career selection process like a cakewalk. While determining a career for their children, parents should understand and ponder these factors. They include:</p>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375267/567c545e-c752-11e6-8c10-76e9c5ac7c9f.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375267/567c545e-c752-11e6-8c10-76e9c5ac7c9f.jpg</a>"></p>

<h3>Interest:</h3>

<p>Whatever you are doing, it should be of your interest. Without having an interest in a particular field, one can’t be successful in making this as his/her passion. Same goes to your child too. It is your duty as a parent to keep a frequent check of your child’s interest and choose a career accordingly.
<img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375266/567b37d6-c752-11e6-890d-bb5b43811011.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375266/567b37d6-c752-11e6-890d-bb5b43811011.jpg</a>"></p>

<h3>Ability:</h3>

<p>One’s ability determines his/her capabilities of doing something. It acts like a mirror of your child personality as well. By noting their ability of doing something, you can select a career exactly meant for your child.
<img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375265/567972e8-c752-11e6-9c3b-1d05801ffc63.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375265/567972e8-c752-11e6-9c3b-1d05801ffc63.jpg</a>"></p>

<h3>Research on the availability of course:</h3>

<p>The course related to a particular career should be available easily and it is, therefore, parents’ duty to do a thorough research on that before advising their child to opt it.
<img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375264/56789c2e-c752-11e6-9ced-32b230c57a39.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375264/56789c2e-c752-11e6-9ced-32b230c57a39.jpg</a>"></p>

<h3>Scope:</h3>

<p>Pay attention to the scope of a particular course, which tells us about what type of opportunities, will open up after doing that particular course or going for a career.
<img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375263/5675b1da-c752-11e6-83e4-cc55d58f47b7.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21375263/5675b1da-c752-11e6-83e4-cc55d58f47b7.jpg</a>"></p>

<h3>Remuneration:</h3>

<p>Though, all the time it’s not necessary, but in today’s scenario, remuneration or salary plays an important role. Remuneration should meet the child’s aspirations, so that they can excel a satisfied and comfortable life ahead.</p>

<h2>Do’s and Don’t</h2>

<h3>Do&rsquo;s</h3>

<ul>
<li>Evaluate your child’s aptitude, strengths and weaknesses.</li>
<li>Help your child in discovering his/her own passion.</li>
<li>Motivate your child in pursuing his/her passion.</li>
<li>Inform your child regarding all aspects of the career.</li>
<li>Help the child understand the work life in the chosen career by associating with professionals in the field.</li>
<li>Stop your child from falling prey to peer-pressure and herd mentality.</li>
<li>Gain your child’s confidence and motivate them to discuss their queries with you.</li>
<li>Seek professional help whenever required.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Dont&rsquo;s</h3>

<ul>
<li>Do not impose your wish on them</li>
<li>Do not burden the child with unreal expectations</li>
<li>Don’t be impatient when dealing with children</li>
<li>Career scope changes with time; do not try to impose the ideas or views that existed during your days</li>
<li>Do not misguide the child into choosing a career of your choice</li>
<li>Do not be on rush to answer a child’s question without the knowledge. It’s ok to take time, research or seek professional help</li>
<li>Protect your child from being influenced by others in the career selection process</li>
</ul>


<p>This way you can be an active partner of your child while selecting a career. Identify your child’s interest, skills and value and start playing your role.</p>

<p>Happy Parenting</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Navigate the Traps of Online Dating to Save Your Relationship?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/12/20/how-to-navigate-the-traps-of-online-dating-to-save-your-relationship/"/>
    <updated>2016-12-20T00:07:32+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/12/20/how-to-navigate-the-traps-of-online-dating-to-save-your-relationship</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324391/870c3a8c-c647-11e6-9118-abe61a3cd600.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324391/870c3a8c-c647-11e6-9118-abe61a3cd600.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600"></p>

<!-- more -->


<p>This surely is a tech savvy age and the rise of smartphones are all the rage. It has transformed our society wherein online dating has been ticking all the wrong boxes.
Men who are in relationships might be loyal to their women but nowadays, with this emerging trend of various online dating sites gaining popularity; men are drifting towards infidelity. These online dating sites provide a gamut of attractive facilities to woo men along with hundreds and thousands of eye-catching women waiting to get ticked. Men look for excitement in their lives and what better way than online dating sites? While being in a relationship, there are times when men look for other prospects for simply flirting and passing their time, these online dating sites are a boon for these men to talk with women they have never met or spoken with.</p>

<h2>How to deal with it -</h2>

<p>Do not turn a blind eye to it, if you get acquainted with the fact that your man is getting indulged in online dating sites and is showing his interest in it. It can act like a dagger piercing through the heart but do not ignore.</p>

<h2>Educate yourself and research about his interest –</h2>

<p>If he sends across messages that are steamy and passion then he surely seeks or attention just like an egoistic man would want to do and if he is sending intimate and comforting messages then he is craving for affection emotionally.</p>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324389/86f13aac-c647-11e6-9d6b-94a3f9fef1a1.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324389/86f13aac-c647-11e6-9d6b-94a3f9fef1a1.jpg</a>"></p>

<p>You don’t need to feel that you are not of value for him because online dating is considered as a sign of infidelity and such men at times lack the ability of communicating their needs or it might even be the reason of his self-image. You need to reach out to him and talk it out instead of thinking about anything else.</p>

<h2>Set your limits –</h2>

<p>When you get to know that your man is cheating on you, you need to set your limits there and then. Stop acting like an emotional freak and if you are serious for him; make it certain that he needs to make a choice. Don’t feel the pain of his entertainment and cut all ties of physical intimacy till the time he doesn’t get back to his senses.</p>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324390/86fe7244-c647-11e6-989f-b3c925bc419d.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324390/86fe7244-c647-11e6-989f-b3c925bc419d.jpg</a>"></p>

<p>Don’t burst like a volcano over him and try to be calm. Because he might take offence despite being wrong at his part. Also, don’t blame or argue, put out your heart on your sleeve and refrain from having any physical contact with him. He might comprehend the blunder he has made to his relationship.</p>

<h2>Focus back on your life –</h2>

<p>Your happiness is equally important and if you cannot control his infidelity, be kind to yourself. Do not indulge in sleepless nights and swollen eyes. Pamper yourself and ignore his behavior. There are times when your self-esteem gets broken when your man does such things.</p>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324388/86e47ef2-c647-11e6-87fe-e9e744e0fe2a.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/21324388/86e47ef2-c647-11e6-87fe-e9e744e0fe2a.jpg</a>"></p>

<p>Bubble-up and make sure you date yourself and spend as much time with yourself that it makes you feel happy. Take your life back and maintain the respect and self-esteem in the ego, no matter what. Everything else will fall back into place and if he is meant to be, he will come back to you.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
