<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Latest Posts on Delhi | JunkJam Blog]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/categories/delhi/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2016-08-13T17:52:15+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delhi College Fashion Trends]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/28/delhi-college-fashion-trends/"/>
    <updated>2016-07-28T19:30:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/28/delhi-college-fashion-trends</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17203889/be07ffac-54bf-11e6-8377-80ef1dffe9ba.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17203889/be07ffac-54bf-11e6-8377-80ef1dffe9ba.jpg</a>" width="600" height="600" title="Delhi College Fashion Trends" >
Along with the monsoons comes the new session of colleges which simply means a whole new life. All the new friendships, heart aches, class notes, mass bunk etc are waiting for you. Apart from all these things, one major thing that is gonna change is that you no longer have to wear the same uniform daily, college gives you the freedom to wear the trendiest outfits and break the code of regular uniform. As the college new session starts, here I am suggesting you 10 styles which are trending this season.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h1>Palazzos</h1>

<p><img class="right <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17203914/de738874-54bf-11e6-8d23-19ca5e2eb94a.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17203914/de738874-54bf-11e6-8d23-19ca5e2eb94a.jpg</a>" title="Palazzos" >
Palazzos are really trending and seems like everyone from women to young gals are in love with them. For summers, Palazzos are the best choice as they are flowy wide legged pants. You can wear plain palazzos or printed ones with any kind of top like long and short kurtas, halter neck, tuck in tops etc.</p>

<h5>Where to get: In Delhi you can easily get a palazzo from any street market like Sarojini Nagar, Janpath, Kamla Nagar Market</h5>

<h5>Price Range: Rs. 200 to Rs. 500</h5>

<h1>Scarves</h1>

<p><img class="center <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17204009/8829fb28-54c0-11e6-827d-4738e167d1f5.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17204009/8829fb28-54c0-11e6-827d-4738e167d1f5.jpg</a>" width="650" height="500" title="Scarves" >
Whether you are wearing a kurti, ethnic skirt or a top, you can easily accessorize it with a patterned scarf. There are various ways of carrying a scarf, if you don’t know how to tie a scarf then you can easily find many video tutorials online.  You can buy scarfs in different patterns like polka dots, striped ones, zig zag ones etc and create a new style every day to your college.</p>

<h5>Where to get: All the street markets of Delhi</h5>

<h5>Price Range: Rs. 35 to Rs. 150</h5>

<h1>Ripped Jeans</h1>

<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17203963/38b1959c-54c0-11e6-889b-32a56a9ff937.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17203963/38b1959c-54c0-11e6-889b-32a56a9ff937.jpg</a>" width="500" height="350" title="Ripped Jeans" >
Yeah and this one is really being loved by the college going gals as it gives them a rockstar like feel. No longer that boring normal jeans, make an exciting entry to your college on the first day wearing these highly fashionable ripped jeans. You can DIY any normal jeans into a rockstar ripped jeans.</p>

<h5>Where to get: Janpath</h5>

<h5>Price Range: Rs. 250 to Rs. 500</h5>

<h1>Kurtis</h1>

<p><img class="right <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17204139/5d921a5c-54c1-11e6-8d9e-674cf4aaf007.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17204139/5d921a5c-54c1-11e6-8d9e-674cf4aaf007.jpg</a>" width="500" height="700" title="Kurtis" >
Wear it with palazzos, leggings, ethnic skirts, jeans or anything else, Kurti is certainly the best choice for Summers. It’s light and comfortable to wear. And yeah you can also style it up with trendy scarves, Rajasthani jhola bags, cute little jhumkis and juttis or Kohlapuri chappals.</p>

<h5>Where to get: Janpath, Kamla Nagar Market, Palika Bazaar</h5>

<h5>Price Range: Rs. 250 to Rs. 500</h5>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17204152/70d46232-54c1-11e6-9540-a7d752da9c9a.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/20486720/17204152/70d46232-54c1-11e6-9540-a7d752da9c9a.jpg</a>" title="Fashion Accessories" ></p>

<h1>Fashion Accessories</h1>

<p>Yes, now you are in college and you can definitely flaunt your accessories without being called as “ye dekho school me jyda style mar rahi hai ladki”, rather you would be labeled as a fashionista. In Delhi you can have so many accessories like beaded neck pieces, scarves, sunglasses, metallic bangles etc at low price from various street markets.</p>

<h5>Where to get: All the Street Markets of Delhi</h5>

<h5>Price Range: Rs. 10 to Rs. 250</h5>

<p>So, follow these few Delhi college fashion trends and become a rockstar in your group.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
