<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Latest Posts on Relationship | JunkJam Blog - Street Market! Fashion! LifeStyle!]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/categories/relationship/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2017-02-08T05:16:29+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Questions Every Girl Wants to Ask Her Guy?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/15/questions-every-girl-wants-to-ask-her-guy/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-15T13:18:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/15/questions-every-girl-wants-to-ask-her-guy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif</a>" width="500" height="600">
Well, it is not as if the number of questions we often bombard you with is a low figure. Nevertheless, we have a few more.
There are certain questions, which are not so easy to ask, or are better avoided. However, in alignment with our traits,
we cannot feel at peace unless these questions are answered.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>No matter how cool we might seem as girlfriends, we remain troubled by these questions.
Therefore, boys, if you are reading this, please do help us clear away the clouds of curiosity hovering over our heads by answering these questions!</p>

<h1>1.Do you love me? Like, you really do?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378810/4b5135d4-920c-11e6-9819-b7f47d541d5c.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378810/4b5135d4-920c-11e6-9819-b7f47d541d5c.gif</a>">
You might have been very clear about your serious intentions. Yet, we feel the need to re-confirm if the answer has changed, is still the same, or is modified.
And of course, we love listening to the way you express your love.</p>

<h1>2.How much do you love me?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378794/4b17ec2a-920c-11e6-8e48-76543db03aea.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378794/4b17ec2a-920c-11e6-8e48-76543db03aea.gif</a>">
We aren’t expecting a very clichéd answer for this one, but rather an honest answer that quantitatively describes your love for us.
Then you can probably just add on those historic lines proclaiming how you can even fetch us stars from Heaven. :P</p>

<h1>3.‘Do you ever stalk me the way I stalk you?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif</a>">
Umm, maybe not as diligently as we do, but at least partially in the same manner that we do?
That’s really something we girls would want to know. We love knowing how much a person is curious about us.</p>

<h1>4.Does your best friend really like us?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378797/4b195eca-920c-11e6-8d2a-09695430c5d2.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378797/4b195eca-920c-11e6-8d2a-09695430c5d2.gif</a>">
If this question has not yet come up, be assured that it soon will. Although your best friend might be very nice to us,
we cannot help but contemplate on the question if she genuinely likes us or is being pretentious and doing it for the sake of friendship.</p>

<h1>5.‘How serious were you in your previous relationship?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378798/4b1af94c-920c-11e6-8787-0feccfb25de8.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378798/4b1af94c-920c-11e6-8787-0feccfb25de8.gif</a>">
This kind of a question may lead to an awkward silence. It is similar to the awkwardness we face when we contemplate asking you this.
The answer would not really affect our relationship, but we are curious. We would want to be a bit more knowledgeable about this.</p>

<h1>6.‘Did you ever imagine getting married to your ex?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378796/4b18c352-920c-11e6-8118-fd9083e9c858.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378796/4b18c352-920c-11e6-8118-fd9083e9c858.gif</a>">
If it were a straight forward NO, we definitely would want to know the answer. However, if it’s a yes, then maybe we should just go to the next question.</p>

<h1>7. ‘What do your friends think about me?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378811/4b51c6b6-920c-11e6-9198-180e93ff30d0.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378811/4b51c6b6-920c-11e6-9198-180e93ff30d0.gif</a>">
Whether the answer is negative or positive, we are ready to face anything and everything.
We just want to know about the kind of conversation you have with your friends while discussing us.</p>

<h1>8.‘Do you still miss something special about your past relationship?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378799/4b1fccc4-920c-11e6-8dd9-f1519d838bbb.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378799/4b1fccc4-920c-11e6-8dd9-f1519d838bbb.gif</a>">
At some point, we do accept your past and stay cool with it. Yet, we do love keeping ourselves informed about such things.</p>

<h1>9.What if your parents do not accept me?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378814/4b52a34c-920c-11e6-88c1-1175cd81b92b.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378814/4b52a34c-920c-11e6-88c1-1175cd81b92b.gif</a>">
We reassure you that we will try our best to make them like us.
However, suppose they don’t, what do we do then? Where does our relationship go from here?</p>

<h1>10.Why me at all?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378795/4b1756b6-920c-11e6-8677-5966d4dc2bf0.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378795/4b1756b6-920c-11e6-8677-5966d4dc2bf0.gif</a>">
Now this one calls for a super romantic reply. We girls would love hearing about your feelings during the initial meeting, and what prompted you to choose us.
It might be the hundredth time but it is hard to explain how it feels to hear the answer every single time!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Overcome a BAD Breakup]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/04/how-to-overcome-from-breakup/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-04T13:18:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/04/how-to-overcome-from-breakup</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif</a>">
Break ups can be very difficult to deal with and looking at how fast paced our lives are, it is difficult to make time for you and cope up with all the depression phase.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Needless to talk about how you have to deal with all the people around who if know about the break up, keep asking how you feeling and those who don’t know keep wondering
if there is something wrong you are going through mentally. However, we have got a few ways in which you can handle a break up without going through much of self- disappointment or depression.
Hope this tips help you and do the best for you</p>

<h1>Block him or unfriend him from all social media platforms.</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104511/8a2b50b4-8afa-11e6-9cc1-5252742b2490.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104511/8a2b50b4-8afa-11e6-9cc1-5252742b2490.gif</a>">
You might feel like a grownup that does not need to do all this but trust us, this helps BIG time! Off course you do not what his name popping up in your notifications. This might keep reminding you of him and plus getting updates about what he is up to while are trying to move on can worsen things up for you.</p>

<h1>Do not jump into the ‘let us just be friends’ stage too soon.</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104513/8a3137f4-8afa-11e6-95b4-262e04c3a847.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104513/8a3137f4-8afa-11e6-95b4-262e04c3a847.gif</a>">
It is advisable to give yourself sometime to figure things out and realize what needs to be changed and what does not. If he suggests this then tell him that you need some time to think about it. Usually one wish to be just friends while the other expects more out of it, and at such you a state, you might want to have things clear and no confusions involved.</p>

<h1>If you are ever tempted to drink, take a friend along.</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104510/8a288564-8afa-11e6-9ee7-b4d811ee0964.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104510/8a288564-8afa-11e6-9ee7-b4d811ee0964.gif</a>">
Drinking while you are alone and sad after a break up is very common.Although some find it a convenient way to deal with such traumatic situations, it is not really a solution to it. If you are tempted to go for a drink, take a trusted friend along who would make sure you don’t up making regrettable choices when you are drunk.</p>

<h1>Start up an intense work out regime.</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104512/8a2c681e-8afa-11e6-8e6c-81d934bc15db.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104512/8a2c681e-8afa-11e6-8e6c-81d934bc15db.gif</a>">
You might have come across options like these which people usually choose. The point is to boost your self-confidence and keep you focus on your own well-being. Moreover, doing something such as kickboxing is a great way of getting all the inner frustration out and doing something productive.</p>

<h1>Allow yourself to cry whenever you need to.</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif</a>">
This one can be a bit confusing but letting it all go and getting yourself out of the phase should be your motive.</p>

<p>Most importantly give time to do things that you like doing and being around people who love and care for you.
Before loving others, it is important to love ourselves, beginnings could be little difficult but once you start initiating things, you feel good about it. Remember the solution is always live up in the present than recalling the past. Your life is important.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Sweetest Ways to Tell Your Partner About Your Pregnancy]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/03/how-to-tell-him-about-your-pregnancy/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-03T13:18:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/03/how-to-tell-him-about-your-pregnancy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103253/6908ad66-8af3-11e6-91d1-6fff11b6948d.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103253/6908ad66-8af3-11e6-91d1-6fff11b6948d.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600">
Being in a long distance relationship it took us long time to plan a kid. Finally the good news arrived and I was pregnant by 2 month. The joy was to the cloud and back.
Even if you are sure and going to be new parents to be., here are some sweetest way to tell your partner the same, the tips are as follows:-</p>

<!--more-->


<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103252/69043c4a-8af3-11e6-9f8b-94abc6787cd6.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103252/69043c4a-8af3-11e6-9f8b-94abc6787cd6.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600"></p>

<h1>Cupcake delight</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103265/74fef99a-8af3-11e6-920c-a7f23ce2d3b2.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103265/74fef99a-8af3-11e6-920c-a7f23ce2d3b2.gif</a>">
The customized cup cakes could do all that wonders. A romantic and surprise cup cake for soon to be daddy will be a perfect one.</p>

<h1>Sweeter box of chocolates</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103324/d22f1b0e-8af3-11e6-8cf9-af577009b9c1.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103324/d22f1b0e-8af3-11e6-8cf9-af577009b9c1.gif</a>">
They are most easy thing to bake and spelling daddy on every piece of chocolate could be an good option to break the news.</p>

<h1>Jigsaw puzzle</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103487/b9ff3702-8af4-11e6-980d-58f1642709a3.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103487/b9ff3702-8af4-11e6-980d-58f1642709a3.gif</a>">
When you wish to give him that nail bitting moment and keep that fun of surprise on then jigsaw puzzle could be a perfect option for you.</p>

<h1>Coffee mug hidden message</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103527/fa6adfee-8af4-11e6-91bb-eb0400a56351.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103527/fa6adfee-8af4-11e6-91bb-eb0400a56351.jpg</a>">
Imagine that he has entered home after long time, in order to break the ice and start conversations coffee would be an ideal option. The best way to express your feelings is that the message in the interiors of the mug could express it better. Planning a coffee together could be the best one.</p>

<h1>Baby lottery</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103528/fa6c06b2-8af4-11e6-9acd-715e023c210e.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103528/fa6c06b2-8af4-11e6-9acd-715e023c210e.jpg</a>">
Times have gone where people only used scratch cards to win lottery or recharge, you can even use scratch card to announce your pregnancy.</p>

<h1>Announcing on customized t-shirt</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103530/faa56cea-8af4-11e6-9f18-f4146c0cfb84.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103530/faa56cea-8af4-11e6-9f18-f4146c0cfb84.jpg</a>">
Hip hurray we are going to be new parents to be, trust us fun will be different when he will wear a t-shirt. You could choose from variants of colors.</p>

<h1>Baby cake pops</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103529/fa912dd4-8af4-11e6-8ec1-6d45336494be.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103529/fa912dd4-8af4-11e6-8ec1-6d45336494be.gif</a>">
This time is right  to express your creativity to loved ones. You could order for baby cake pops and when he arrives surprise him with that.</p>

<h1>Small cute plate on dining table</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103526/fa6a651e-8af4-11e6-983c-830bcc351508.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103526/fa6a651e-8af4-11e6-983c-830bcc351508.jpg</a>">
A little spoon, dish and bowl with handwritten message will bring that big blushing smile.</p>

<h1>Baby photos everywhere</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103528/fa6c06b2-8af4-11e6-9acd-715e023c210e.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19103528/fa6c06b2-8af4-11e6-9acd-715e023c210e.jpg</a>">
Before he gets up from the bed, fill your bedroom with lot of photos. We are sure that cute baby photos will also melt his heart. Doing your own photoshoot with some cute dolls to surprise him will also work wonders.</p>

<h1>Take him for garden stroll</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19120993/84af3fcc-8b42-11e6-851b-63fbc6f8b7ae.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/19120993/84af3fcc-8b42-11e6-851b-63fbc6f8b7ae.jpg</a>">
There is nothing pure like nature and revealing heart out. Breaking the news of baby may require some peaceful environment; taking him to toddlers play area will give him that different joy all together.</p>

<p>Relationship grows better with a new arrival of new kid. Motherhood is all together different joy. We insist all of you to eat right and fresh.
Enjoy the present with all good moments. We are sure that these tips will surely bring in more joy than anything else. You could go boundless with creativity even if you are planning to do DIY.
“I love you” is always worth to say for giving him that perfect good feeling.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deal It Right for Perfect Dream Date!]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/03/first-date-tips/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-03T13:16:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/03/first-date-tips</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19019990/4b9ea3b6-88b9-11e6-818a-201fac58cebd.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19019990/4b9ea3b6-88b9-11e6-818a-201fac58cebd.gif</a>">
Dating online is no more a taboo. It has become a pretty normal way of finding dating partners. Not to miss out some relationships that turned into having a bright future.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Online dating can be a very tricky business. While it can work wonders for a few, it can even become troublesome for others. Under such circumstances, one must be self-informed about everything that goes around.
Not all online experiences turn out to be good ones and thus, here are a few tips which will help you connect to a partner suitable for you and also help you avoid making silly mistakes:</p>

<h1>Select a good site.</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19020016/39b50720-88ba-11e6-8e6a-7a36570515e0.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19020016/39b50720-88ba-11e6-8e6a-7a36570515e0.jpg</a>">
Even before you start dreaming about your to-be date; it is necessary to give enough time to select an appropriate site for online dating. While there are sites which allow you to make choice for yourself from a number of members using the same website, there are also sites that suggest dates to you based on your compatibility.
If you wish to have the freedom of choice and are ready to go through hundreds of accounts, then the prior one is what you should be looking for.</p>

<h1>Choose someone with similar interests.</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19020012/25cb172c-88ba-11e6-8221-7356013943f9.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19020012/25cb172c-88ba-11e6-8221-7356013943f9.jpg</a>">
If you are specific about what you are looking for, for example, of a particular community or work place or a defined age group or even in terms of preferred sexuality, there exist sites which work wholly based on that particular category.
This way it will be much more sorted, easier and faster. Also while choosing a partner; people like to usual go for someone with whom they share similar interest. This helps you to start a good conversation.</p>

<h1>Not being too choosy is the key.</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19020014/31813178-88ba-11e6-8acb-5611f4cd88d4.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19020014/31813178-88ba-11e6-8acb-5611f4cd88d4.jpg</a>">
It is a human tendency to make a list of have’s and have not’s when you start talking to each other or meet on the first date. You might have thoughts like ‘he doesn’t dress well’ or ‘she does not have good eyes’ or ‘he does not earn enough’.
However, when you are going for online dating, it is very important to have an open mind and not to be too much judgmental about everything. Letting your inner voice stay at peace and seeing what’s kept on the plate for you is a wise choice. You might as well turn out to like the person.</p>

<h1>Be honest.</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19019984/1b259cf8-88b9-11e6-88ad-4a78b058f81a.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19019984/1b259cf8-88b9-11e6-88ad-4a78b058f81a.gif</a>">
The truth can’t be denied that it is very tempting to exaggerate or stretch things while writing your bio. Nevertheless, lying can lead to a number of disappointments in the future. It is best to stay honest since the start and have nothing to hide about.
False revealing can make you lose a potential partner. Not pretending or trying to be someone or something you are not is the best option to go for.</p>

<p>Online dating has become a fade lately because of which it has become very important to beware aboutpeople who use these sites for their selfish needs or to trick people. One ‘must’ stand by rule is to keep it low at the start. Do not give too many details.
Rest is all that your personality and charms needs to manage.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
