<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Latest Posts Onrelationship | JunkJam | Fashion! LifeStyle! Market! Travel!]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/categories/relationship/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2020-04-17T17:50:40+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best 7 Role Plays to Try On]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/10/21/best-7-role-plays-to-try-on/"/>
    <updated>2018-10-21T15:52:48+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/10/21/best-7-role-plays-to-try-on</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a lazy" data-original="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/47265702-b6bd7a80-d549-11e8-8cee-7fbf9bab907c.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/47265702-b6bd7a80-d549-11e8-8cee-7fbf9bab907c.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left <a" data-original="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/47265702-b6bd7a80-d549-11e8-8cee-7fbf9bab907c.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/47265702-b6bd7a80-d549-11e8-8cee-7fbf9bab907c.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500" src="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/47265702-b6bd7a80-d549-11e8-8cee-7fbf9bab907c.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/47265702-b6bd7a80-d549-11e8-8cee-7fbf9bab907c.jpg</a>"></noscript>
It is being said, that the physical attraction takes around 3-6 months time to fade away.  After which, you would see what is the actual scenario, is it the personality of the person you fell for, or just the body. So, after your honeymoon period of romance and passion, the days have started to dry up. You have the same person, you want to make love , but don’t really know, how to re-ignite that fire. Some people, indulge in sex games, other people go to travel. But not all the time, we have that much of time, or money.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Have you ever heard of roleplays? Well, these are easy scenes, where you get to play some character and enact the entire scene. People love them, because, they feel like other person, and things for a change, begin to look as different. Only thing you would want here is a pertner, who would be open for this.</p>

<p>Therefore, 7 easy role plays for you, so that , you can try and feel a new sensation, well, at least for 7 times.</p>

<h4>1.  House owner and the tenant</h4>

<p>Consider, one of you as the house owner and the other one as the tenant. So, the house owner comes home to collect the rent, which hasn’t been transferred for the last 3 months now. As the house owner wants money and the tenant is out of cash, the tenant starts seducing the house owner, a fair deal according to the tenant. Since, the house owner had always been physically attracted to the tenant, after little hesitation, the house owner succumbs to the plan. Now, beauty of the scene is , anyone of you can be the house owner and the tenant. Only thing is, the tenant has to do more hard work( if you know, what it means).</p>

<h4>2.  Teacher and the student’s guardian</h4>

<p>You get the diary of your child/young sibling with the remarks, that you need to meet the teacher. You go to see the teacher but it is already late, and the teacher tells you , since you didn’t come on time, now your child/ sibling has to be marked failed. After a lot of request, the teacher agrees to see you at his/her place, because it is the time of closure of school. You go to the teacher’s place , with an intension to discuss, what can be done, but the teacher starts seducing you and doesn’t want to take no for an answer. You also, get drawn towards the teacher.</p>

<h4>3.  Patient and the fake Doctor</h4>

<p>Now, you have seen this person with your usual doctor, a lot of times, so, you automatically assumed the other person to be a doctor also. You had always exchanged few glances and smiles, but never really knew the person’s name or occupation. Once when you had gone to show some report of your family member, you don’t find your usual doctor there, but this person, who was also waiting for the doctor. You started talking to this person and then this person, fakes to be other doctor, and asks if you have a problem, because you are  also attracted to this person, you show off your back of the neck, or belly, or thighs ( depending which part is more sensitive), and this fake doctor starts seducing you.</p>

<h4>4.  With the partner’s roommate</h4>

<p>So, you are in a long distance relationship and all you know where does your partner stay, you have talked to your partner’s roommate a few times, and sometimes find the roomamate attractive or you have a hunch that the roommate is also attracted to you. You never moved further thinking about your relationship. Once day, you thought of visiting for 2 days to your partner’s place , a surprise visit. When you reach there, you get to know, that the partner has gone to some family event and will be home the next day. You want to go, but the roommate tells you it is only for a day and you can stay there. The roommate gets you drunk and starts to touch you inappropriate way and you give up.</p>

<h4>5.  Workout friend drops you home</h4>

<p>This guy/girl is someone you always see in the gym. The way this person exercise always turns you on and you had always been fantasizing this person. You had also caught this person looking at you and then both of you exchange smiles. One day, when you think of walking down to the store near your place, you find this person, honking at you , and asking if you need a lift. Even if you can walk to the home, you still take a lift, hoping you can invite this person, to your place. When you invite this person, after little reluctance this person agrees to come to your place. You want to offer water, and while offering you deliberately spill little water on your Gym friend, then you tell this person to take off the top and when this person does that, you take the towel, and slowly start wiping the water. Your gym friend is also turning on and is finding is hard to control…..rest is your way.</p>

<h4>6.  Your partner’s colleague</h4>

<p>You are having really bad relationship with you partner for a really long time now. But you go to the official parties with your partner and there is this one person, who you find attractive and soft spoken. The way of talking of this person gets you turned on. You also know, that this person might be attracted to you, because you have exchanged some flirtatious texts with each other, nothing really happened. So, one evening, when your partner is on leave, this person drops in to check in with your partner, since your partner has taken sick leave and is out for a trip with friends. When you tell that to this person, you become sad, and this person comes to console you, it starts with a hug, then a kiss on cheek, then a quick lip kiss, both of you realize it, but cant stop, you should lock your lips again and then you go the way you want.</p>

<h4>7.  The new intern in other office</h4>

<p>This new person is someone now you have started to see in the office next to you. Sometimes, you have seen each other in the office cafeteria, sometimes you have bumped into each other in the lift, but you never really got any chance to talk to each other. Whenever this person leaves, you always exchange a smile and also, till the time you see this person, you keep on exchanging short glances. One day, you happen to be out of your home and you find this person, just outside out home, next door, struggling. When asked, this person tells you that the phone is dead, and she/he came to visit a friend who lives here. So, this person had no option than to wait there. Since, you live alone, you invite that person inside. And offer tea or coffee, then both of you start talking and this person tells you about  his/her new appointment as an intern. Then while this intern wants to keep the cups and saucers in the kitchen , you try stopping this person, and hug this person tightly.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Your Love Language?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/26/whats-your-love-language/"/>
    <updated>2018-09-26T00:22:19+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/26/whats-your-love-language</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a lazy" data-original="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038010-93a8d200-c127-11e8-871f-964f38802105.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038010-93a8d200-c127-11e8-871f-964f38802105.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left <a" data-original="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038010-93a8d200-c127-11e8-871f-964f38802105.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038010-93a8d200-c127-11e8-871f-964f38802105.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500" src="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038010-93a8d200-c127-11e8-871f-964f38802105.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038010-93a8d200-c127-11e8-871f-964f38802105.jpg</a>"></noscript>
So, This is really a new way of talking, isn’t it! Dr. Gary Chapman coined the term love language to express how we express and receive love. So, it is not only based for romantic partner, but you can also identify what works for you at a usual basis. We have been hearing that a male’s and a female’s brain is different, but this is something where it is only about the type of love language that suits you.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>So, let us go through the five types of Love Languages , so that you can also identify which is a good fit for you .</p>

<h3>1. Quality Time</h3>

<p>Quality time is about spending time together enjoying each other’s company.
<img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038014-94416880-c127-11e8-9396-6790c848852b.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038014-94416880-c127-11e8-9396-6790c848852b.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038014-94416880-c127-11e8-9396-6790c848852b.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038014-94416880-c127-11e8-9396-6790c848852b.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600" src="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038014-94416880-c127-11e8-9396-6790c848852b.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038014-94416880-c127-11e8-9396-6790c848852b.jpg</a>"></noscript></p>

<h4>How to communicate:</h4>

<p>Put down your phone and other things that mostly distract you. Focus on uninterrupted interaction or discussion. One on one time is very critical. You must have heard something called as “Me Time”, there has to be an “Our Time” also.</p>

<h4>Actions to take:</h4>

<p>Create special moments together like scheduling and going for a walk together, doing or indulging in some activities with your spouse, going for a weekend getaways or even travelling somewhere close by.</p>

<h4>Things to avoid:</h4>

<p>Having distractions like Mobile apps, games, chatting with someone else, long stint without spending time with each other.</p>

<h3>2. Physical Touch</h3>

<p>Physical touch is showing love through hugging, cuddling, being intimate or simply putting a caring hand on someone’s shoulder. Sometimes, your partner might be more physically active than you. Even if you don’t like it, you should indulge or try to be in it happily, because that is one way of making your partner happy.
<img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038012-94416880-c127-11e8-860f-d2dc7abb96d9.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038012-94416880-c127-11e8-860f-d2dc7abb96d9.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038012-94416880-c127-11e8-860f-d2dc7abb96d9.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038012-94416880-c127-11e8-860f-d2dc7abb96d9.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600" src="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038012-94416880-c127-11e8-860f-d2dc7abb96d9.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038012-94416880-c127-11e8-860f-d2dc7abb96d9.jpg</a>"></noscript></p>

<h4>How to communicate:</h4>

<p>Non Verbal use of Body Language , which emphasizes love and care , for eg. Holding hands, hugging, moving your fingers along your partner’s hair.</p>

<h4>Actions to take:</h4>

<p>Showing physical affection regularly and make physical intimacy a thoughtful priority.</p>

<h4>Things to avoid:</h4>

<p>Physical neglect, a long stint without intimacy, receiving affection coldly</p>

<h3>3. Receiving Gifts</h3>

<p>Yes, this had to be featured in the list. When you gifted something to your crush from that gift shop or you received the gift, you saved that thing for so long, because it was dear to you. For few people, this becomes a really important step during their relationship.
<img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038010-93a8d200-c127-11e8-871f-964f38802105.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038010-93a8d200-c127-11e8-871f-964f38802105.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038010-93a8d200-c127-11e8-871f-964f38802105.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038010-93a8d200-c127-11e8-871f-964f38802105.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600" src="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038010-93a8d200-c127-11e8-871f-964f38802105.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038010-93a8d200-c127-11e8-871f-964f38802105.jpg</a>"></noscript></p>

<h4>How to communicate:</h4>

<p>Thoughtfulness, make your partner’s choice priority, speak purposefully.</p>

<h4>Actions to take:</h4>

<p>Give thoughtful gifts, small things matter in a big way, People in this category, don’t really are looking for expensive gifts, for them, it is the thought that counts.</p>

<h4>Things to avoid:</h4>

<p>Forgetting special occasions, unenthusiastic gift receiving.</p>

<h3>4. Acts of Service</h3>

<p>Ever experienced this during your relationship or someone other’s, that the partner would do something for the other counterpart, like cooking or cleaning or arranging the place or shopping on behalf of their partner. Well this is just the same thing.
<img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038009-93a8d200-c127-11e8-8110-20336f403674.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038009-93a8d200-c127-11e8-8110-20336f403674.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038009-93a8d200-c127-11e8-8110-20336f403674.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038009-93a8d200-c127-11e8-8110-20336f403674.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600" src="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038009-93a8d200-c127-11e8-8110-20336f403674.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038009-93a8d200-c127-11e8-8110-20336f403674.jpg</a>"></noscript></p>

<h4>How to communicate:</h4>

<p>Use action phrases like “ I’ll help…” , they want to know you are with them /partnered with them in small little errands.</p>

<h4>Actions to take:</h4>

<p>Do chores together, make them breakfast on bed, go out of your way to help alleviate their daily work load.</p>

<h4>Things to avoid:</h4>

<p>Making the requests of others a higher priority, lacking follow-through on tasks big and small.</p>

<h3>5. Words of Affirmation</h3>

<p>These are the positive words that you say to them personally or in front of people. These people love to be praised by someone they love. So, make sure, if you have one, who likes this, from time to time you need to tell him/her how lucky you are, or how much you love them, or how they have made a positive change in your personality.
<img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038015-94d9ff00-c127-11e8-8efb-1a4e59c58f58.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038015-94d9ff00-c127-11e8-8efb-1a4e59c58f58.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038015-94d9ff00-c127-11e8-8efb-1a4e59c58f58.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038015-94d9ff00-c127-11e8-8efb-1a4e59c58f58.jpg</a>" width="500" height="600" src="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038015-94d9ff00-c127-11e8-8efb-1a4e59c58f58.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/46038015-94d9ff00-c127-11e8-8efb-1a4e59c58f58.jpg</a>"></noscript></p>

<h4>How to communicate:</h4>

<p>Encourage, affirm, appreciate, empathize, listen actively</p>

<h4>Actions to take:</h4>

<p>Send an unexpected note, text or card. Encourage genuinely and often.</p>

<h4>Things to avoid:</h4>

<p>Non constructive criticism, not recognizing or appreciating efforts.</p>

<p>Typically people have one main love language and one secondary one. It is important to know these so you can ask for what you need and show your partners, friends and colleagues appreciation in the way they like to receive it.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Things That a Partner Expects From You, but Would Never Tell You]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/24/7-things-that-a-partner-expects-from-you-but-would-never-tell-you/"/>
    <updated>2018-09-24T23:15:22+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2018/09/24/7-things-that-a-partner-expects-from-you-but-would-never-tell-you</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a lazy" data-original="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45991539-fc01a000-c0a2-11e8-8292-a3675a4cf725.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45991539-fc01a000-c0a2-11e8-8292-a3675a4cf725.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500"/><noscript><img class="left <a" data-original="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45991539-fc01a000-c0a2-11e8-8292-a3675a4cf725.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45991539-fc01a000-c0a2-11e8-8292-a3675a4cf725.jpg</a>" width="400" height="500" src="href="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45991539-fc01a000-c0a2-11e8-8292-a3675a4cf725.jpg">https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1082157/45991539-fc01a000-c0a2-11e8-8292-a3675a4cf725.jpg</a>"></noscript>
There were days, when men used to control the household and women used to follow. Now, in majority of households, people start to follow equality between husbands and wives. Even after all these things, a woman usually has complains that her man is not fulfilling her demands without realizing that a man might also have few things to ask for. Psychologically speaking, men do not like ask things other than food and physical intimacy, but here are 7 things which they expect from their wives but won’t tell her. These results came out after a survey of 173 men aged 27-65yrs in relationship (marriage included).</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>1.  Admiration</h4>

<p>First thing to make it to the top is admiration. Admiration is the combination of love and respect. So, if you had been thinking , that your husband seeks only respect from you or only love, you are wrong. Especially, if you are in a public place, make sure that you show respect towards him. I am not saying he can be disrespectful. But a man takes a note of this , that how his wife is treating him in Public.</p>

<h4>2.  Supportive</h4>

<p>Another important factor is being supportive. A man would rarely say that he is having some problem or he needs you emotionally, but if you know him, you know, he wants that support. When he presents any idea to you, rather than declining it at the very first stage, take time to listen to the idea. It might be a chance that the idea presented is just not worth it, but when you are listening to the idea, just listen don’t just hear, to say NO at the end.</p>

<h4>3.  Intelligent</h4>

<p>In our country, the perception of intelligence is so wrong, that most of the people end up saying that they are not intelligent. In India, Marks in the examination are the only source which tell us who is intelligent. But that is not true. Intelligence is basically the skill to handle problems without getting annoyed. If you are not told how to do certain things, even then you can do it by trying, then that mean you are intelligent. So, handling a situation independently and nicely is a sign of good intelligence.</p>

<h4>4.  Family Oriented</h4>

<p>This is a big one. We know, that in India, we “have to” be family oriented. But when someone says family oriented, in India it just doesn’t mean only your children and partner. Family includes your parents as well and siblings. A woman who is more family oriented and has kept the family together is loved more. Now, with that statement, I am very sure, you might be thinking about Parvati Bhabhi and Tulsi Viraani, but even if you are a working woman, spending quality time with your entire family on festivals is something to be valued.</p>

<h4>5.  Mixing</h4>

<p>This nature is deeply appreciated by men. They value a woman who is of mixing nature. Ever seen that family member, whenever there is a festival, this person doesn’t talk to anyone, doesn’t like to spend time with other members and is always sulking. Don’t be like that person. No matter how much you dislike your relative, once if you smile by heart and try to mix, you would be appreciated. By mixing, I don’t mean, you need to ask them person or offending questions, I mean focusing only on the present event.</p>

<h4>6.  Independent</h4>

<p>You don’t’ have to be financially independent if you are not working. Being independent means, not depending on anybody. Let us say, the gas is over and you need to order a refill. You are waiting for your husband, because only he books the refill. Have you ever thought, for such small little things, how much are you dependent on your husband. Dependency is good, but codependency is better. A person working for long hours and gets to hear a list of such errands may make your man upset.</p>

<h4>7.  Open to experiment</h4>

<p>Now this is the point where it gets little bold. If you have a partner who wants to try new things whether it may be related to food or on bed, you may want to be open. Psychologically speaking, the more you try new things with your partner, the more you get attached to him.</p>

<p>So, these are the factors, which a man might not be very open to discuss with you but would always expect from you. But at the end, nothing else matters if the love is pure from both the ends.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Questions Every Girl Wants to Ask Her Guy?]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/15/questions-every-girl-wants-to-ask-her-guy/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-15T13:18:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/15/questions-every-girl-wants-to-ask-her-guy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif</a>" width="500" height="600"/><noscript><img class="left <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif</a>" width="500" height="600" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif</a>"></noscript>
Well, it is not as if the number of questions we often bombard you with is a low figure. Nevertheless, we have a few more.
There are certain questions, which are not so easy to ask, or are better avoided. However, in alignment with our traits,
we cannot feel at peace unless these questions are answered.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>No matter how cool we might seem as girlfriends, we remain troubled by these questions.
Therefore, boys, if you are reading this, please do help us clear away the clouds of curiosity hovering over our heads by answering these questions!</p>

<h1>1.Do you love me? Like, you really do?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378810/4b5135d4-920c-11e6-9819-b7f47d541d5c.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378810/4b5135d4-920c-11e6-9819-b7f47d541d5c.gif</a>"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378810/4b5135d4-920c-11e6-9819-b7f47d541d5c.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378810/4b5135d4-920c-11e6-9819-b7f47d541d5c.gif</a>" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378810/4b5135d4-920c-11e6-9819-b7f47d541d5c.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378810/4b5135d4-920c-11e6-9819-b7f47d541d5c.gif</a>"></noscript>
You might have been very clear about your serious intentions. Yet, we feel the need to re-confirm if the answer has changed, is still the same, or is modified.
And of course, we love listening to the way you express your love.</p>

<h1>2.How much do you love me?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378794/4b17ec2a-920c-11e6-8e48-76543db03aea.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378794/4b17ec2a-920c-11e6-8e48-76543db03aea.gif</a>"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378794/4b17ec2a-920c-11e6-8e48-76543db03aea.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378794/4b17ec2a-920c-11e6-8e48-76543db03aea.gif</a>" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378794/4b17ec2a-920c-11e6-8e48-76543db03aea.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378794/4b17ec2a-920c-11e6-8e48-76543db03aea.gif</a>"></noscript>
We aren’t expecting a very clichéd answer for this one, but rather an honest answer that quantitatively describes your love for us.
Then you can probably just add on those historic lines proclaiming how you can even fetch us stars from Heaven. :P</p>

<h1>3.‘Do you ever stalk me the way I stalk you?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif</a>"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif</a>" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378807/4b4d9c26-920c-11e6-97de-2fb444f62545.gif</a>"></noscript>
Umm, maybe not as diligently as we do, but at least partially in the same manner that we do?
That’s really something we girls would want to know. We love knowing how much a person is curious about us.</p>

<h1>4.Does your best friend really like us?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378797/4b195eca-920c-11e6-8d2a-09695430c5d2.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378797/4b195eca-920c-11e6-8d2a-09695430c5d2.gif</a>"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378797/4b195eca-920c-11e6-8d2a-09695430c5d2.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378797/4b195eca-920c-11e6-8d2a-09695430c5d2.gif</a>" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378797/4b195eca-920c-11e6-8d2a-09695430c5d2.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378797/4b195eca-920c-11e6-8d2a-09695430c5d2.gif</a>"></noscript>
If this question has not yet come up, be assured that it soon will. Although your best friend might be very nice to us,
we cannot help but contemplate on the question if she genuinely likes us or is being pretentious and doing it for the sake of friendship.</p>

<h1>5.‘How serious were you in your previous relationship?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378798/4b1af94c-920c-11e6-8787-0feccfb25de8.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378798/4b1af94c-920c-11e6-8787-0feccfb25de8.gif</a>"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378798/4b1af94c-920c-11e6-8787-0feccfb25de8.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378798/4b1af94c-920c-11e6-8787-0feccfb25de8.gif</a>" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378798/4b1af94c-920c-11e6-8787-0feccfb25de8.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378798/4b1af94c-920c-11e6-8787-0feccfb25de8.gif</a>"></noscript>
This kind of a question may lead to an awkward silence. It is similar to the awkwardness we face when we contemplate asking you this.
The answer would not really affect our relationship, but we are curious. We would want to be a bit more knowledgeable about this.</p>

<h1>6.‘Did you ever imagine getting married to your ex?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378796/4b18c352-920c-11e6-8118-fd9083e9c858.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378796/4b18c352-920c-11e6-8118-fd9083e9c858.gif</a>"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378796/4b18c352-920c-11e6-8118-fd9083e9c858.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378796/4b18c352-920c-11e6-8118-fd9083e9c858.gif</a>" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378796/4b18c352-920c-11e6-8118-fd9083e9c858.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378796/4b18c352-920c-11e6-8118-fd9083e9c858.gif</a>"></noscript>
If it were a straight forward NO, we definitely would want to know the answer. However, if it’s a yes, then maybe we should just go to the next question.</p>

<h1>7. ‘What do your friends think about me?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378811/4b51c6b6-920c-11e6-9198-180e93ff30d0.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378811/4b51c6b6-920c-11e6-9198-180e93ff30d0.gif</a>"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378811/4b51c6b6-920c-11e6-9198-180e93ff30d0.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378811/4b51c6b6-920c-11e6-9198-180e93ff30d0.gif</a>" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378811/4b51c6b6-920c-11e6-9198-180e93ff30d0.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378811/4b51c6b6-920c-11e6-9198-180e93ff30d0.gif</a>"></noscript>
Whether the answer is negative or positive, we are ready to face anything and everything.
We just want to know about the kind of conversation you have with your friends while discussing us.</p>

<h1>8.‘Do you still miss something special about your past relationship?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378799/4b1fccc4-920c-11e6-8dd9-f1519d838bbb.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378799/4b1fccc4-920c-11e6-8dd9-f1519d838bbb.gif</a>"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378799/4b1fccc4-920c-11e6-8dd9-f1519d838bbb.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378799/4b1fccc4-920c-11e6-8dd9-f1519d838bbb.gif</a>" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378799/4b1fccc4-920c-11e6-8dd9-f1519d838bbb.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378799/4b1fccc4-920c-11e6-8dd9-f1519d838bbb.gif</a>"></noscript>
At some point, we do accept your past and stay cool with it. Yet, we do love keeping ourselves informed about such things.</p>

<h1>9.What if your parents do not accept me?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378814/4b52a34c-920c-11e6-88c1-1175cd81b92b.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378814/4b52a34c-920c-11e6-88c1-1175cd81b92b.gif</a>"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378814/4b52a34c-920c-11e6-88c1-1175cd81b92b.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378814/4b52a34c-920c-11e6-88c1-1175cd81b92b.gif</a>" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378814/4b52a34c-920c-11e6-88c1-1175cd81b92b.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378814/4b52a34c-920c-11e6-88c1-1175cd81b92b.gif</a>"></noscript>
We reassure you that we will try our best to make them like us.
However, suppose they don’t, what do we do then? Where does our relationship go from here?</p>

<h1>10.Why me at all?’</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378795/4b1756b6-920c-11e6-8677-5966d4dc2bf0.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378795/4b1756b6-920c-11e6-8677-5966d4dc2bf0.gif</a>"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378795/4b1756b6-920c-11e6-8677-5966d4dc2bf0.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378795/4b1756b6-920c-11e6-8677-5966d4dc2bf0.gif</a>" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378795/4b1756b6-920c-11e6-8677-5966d4dc2bf0.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19378795/4b1756b6-920c-11e6-8677-5966d4dc2bf0.gif</a>"></noscript>
Now this one calls for a super romantic reply. We girls would love hearing about your feelings during the initial meeting, and what prompted you to choose us.
It might be the hundredth time but it is hard to explain how it feels to hear the answer every single time!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Overcome a BAD Breakup]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/04/how-to-overcome-from-breakup/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-04T13:18:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/10/04/how-to-overcome-from-breakup</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif</a>"/><noscript><img class="left <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif</a>" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif</a>"></noscript>
Break ups can be very difficult to deal with and looking at how fast paced our lives are, it is difficult to make time for you and cope up with all the depression phase.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Needless to talk about how you have to deal with all the people around who if know about the break up, keep asking how you feeling and those who don’t know keep wondering
if there is something wrong you are going through mentally. However, we have got a few ways in which you can handle a break up without going through much of self- disappointment or depression.
Hope this tips help you and do the best for you</p>

<h1>Block him or unfriend him from all social media platforms.</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104511/8a2b50b4-8afa-11e6-9cc1-5252742b2490.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104511/8a2b50b4-8afa-11e6-9cc1-5252742b2490.gif</a>"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104511/8a2b50b4-8afa-11e6-9cc1-5252742b2490.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104511/8a2b50b4-8afa-11e6-9cc1-5252742b2490.gif</a>" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104511/8a2b50b4-8afa-11e6-9cc1-5252742b2490.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104511/8a2b50b4-8afa-11e6-9cc1-5252742b2490.gif</a>"></noscript>
You might feel like a grownup that does not need to do all this but trust us, this helps BIG time! Off course you do not what his name popping up in your notifications. This might keep reminding you of him and plus getting updates about what he is up to while are trying to move on can worsen things up for you.</p>

<h1>Do not jump into the ‘let us just be friends’ stage too soon.</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104513/8a3137f4-8afa-11e6-95b4-262e04c3a847.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104513/8a3137f4-8afa-11e6-95b4-262e04c3a847.gif</a>"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104513/8a3137f4-8afa-11e6-95b4-262e04c3a847.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104513/8a3137f4-8afa-11e6-95b4-262e04c3a847.gif</a>" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104513/8a3137f4-8afa-11e6-95b4-262e04c3a847.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104513/8a3137f4-8afa-11e6-95b4-262e04c3a847.gif</a>"></noscript>
It is advisable to give yourself sometime to figure things out and realize what needs to be changed and what does not. If he suggests this then tell him that you need some time to think about it. Usually one wish to be just friends while the other expects more out of it, and at such you a state, you might want to have things clear and no confusions involved.</p>

<h1>If you are ever tempted to drink, take a friend along.</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104510/8a288564-8afa-11e6-9ee7-b4d811ee0964.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104510/8a288564-8afa-11e6-9ee7-b4d811ee0964.gif</a>"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104510/8a288564-8afa-11e6-9ee7-b4d811ee0964.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104510/8a288564-8afa-11e6-9ee7-b4d811ee0964.gif</a>" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104510/8a288564-8afa-11e6-9ee7-b4d811ee0964.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104510/8a288564-8afa-11e6-9ee7-b4d811ee0964.gif</a>"></noscript>
Drinking while you are alone and sad after a break up is very common.Although some find it a convenient way to deal with such traumatic situations, it is not really a solution to it. If you are tempted to go for a drink, take a trusted friend along who would make sure you don’t up making regrettable choices when you are drunk.</p>

<h1>Start up an intense work out regime.</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104512/8a2c681e-8afa-11e6-8e6c-81d934bc15db.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104512/8a2c681e-8afa-11e6-8e6c-81d934bc15db.gif</a>"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104512/8a2c681e-8afa-11e6-8e6c-81d934bc15db.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104512/8a2c681e-8afa-11e6-8e6c-81d934bc15db.gif</a>" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104512/8a2c681e-8afa-11e6-8e6c-81d934bc15db.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104512/8a2c681e-8afa-11e6-8e6c-81d934bc15db.gif</a>"></noscript>
You might have come across options like these which people usually choose. The point is to boost your self-confidence and keep you focus on your own well-being. Moreover, doing something such as kickboxing is a great way of getting all the inner frustration out and doing something productive.</p>

<h1>Allow yourself to cry whenever you need to.</h1>

<p><img class="center <a lazy" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif</a>"/><noscript><img class="center <a" data-original="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif</a>" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/21153184/19104514/8a579746-8afa-11e6-8881-f7a1c00d0160.gif</a>"></noscript>
This one can be a bit confusing but letting it all go and getting yourself out of the phase should be your motive.</p>

<p>Most importantly give time to do things that you like doing and being around people who love and care for you.
Before loving others, it is important to love ourselves, beginnings could be little difficult but once you start initiating things, you feel good about it. Remember the solution is always live up in the present than recalling the past. Your life is important.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
