<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Latest Posts on Kolkata | JunkJam Blog - Street Market! Fashion! LifeStyle!]]></title>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/categories/kolkata/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/"/>
  <updated>2016-10-25T00:11:40+05:30</updated>
  <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[JunkJam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[junkjam2015@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Market: The Famous Street Market in Kolkata]]></title>
    <link href="https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/15/famous-new-market-in-kolkata/"/>
    <updated>2016-07-15T23:05:49+05:30</updated>
    <id>https://blog.junkjam.in/2016/07/15/famous-new-market-in-kolkata</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16883036/a3765876-4adf-11e6-9615-53bc16f73f84.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16883036/a3765876-4adf-11e6-9615-53bc16f73f84.jpg</a>" width="500" height="650" title="New Market Kolkata" >
Kolkata is the city of joy, where we find many shopping markets to fulfill our shopping needs. This crowded city provides us with many markets like New Market, Gariahat market, Chandni Market etc. In this blog post, we are going to explore in detail about New Market in Kolkata. This market stands on Lindsey Street and was established as a rich arcade to fulfill the shopping requirements of the British-colonist population of the city. As soon as it was opened at the beginning of 1874, it started attracting people from all over India, who spent money in the exclusive shops of this market.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Once, British departed this country, New Market had become Indianised. However, its red-brick, ornate exterior still remains British-looking. Its compact clock tower, which rises from its eastern wall, makes us remember the British Empire era.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16883037/a37895a0-4adf-11e6-82f2-1f92beba48cd.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16883037/a37895a0-4adf-11e6-82f2-1f92beba48cd.jpg</a>"></p>

<p>Inside of New Market you will find a shopping market named S. S. Hawg Market which looks very tangled, however it contains a grid of narrow alleys which are bisecting one another and so many shops and stalls are arranged in neat blocks. You will always find this market busy and crowded and whenever you come at this place, you will find it architecturally chaotic. The boundaries of the market are complicated for defining since it has a basement also, likewise overcrowded with retailers, whose far end seems emerging in another building which contains many more floors of shops. Additionally, of course, the vendors scatter outside the main building and sell their products on the surrounding streets also._</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16883038/a378e212-4adf-11e6-9c3e-73154bdacf48.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16883038/a378e212-4adf-11e6-9c3e-73154bdacf48.jpg</a>"></p>

<p>We need not to say that you can but absolutely everything here you want. Be it grocery item, fruit and vegetable, meat, fish, toys, toiletries, cosmetics, wigs, sandals, shoes, flowers, electric appliances, kitchen utensils, crockery, crystal, silverware, jewelry, dresses, wallets, bags, scarves, shawls, or suitcases, you can find everything in this incredible street market of Kolkata. Even, you will see astrologer, money-changer and barber shops also in this market.
Well, if you are a bag lover and you are on the search for a handbag in this market, you will get completely confused and will be spoilt for choice, as you will find a million bags on sale here in this great street market.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16883039/a37d26a6-4adf-11e6-9b1d-89eca72cf309.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16883039/a37d26a6-4adf-11e6-9b1d-89eca72cf309.jpg</a>"></p>

<p>Entering New Market, you can see not only Indians but also the foreigners who visit this market for shopping regularly. Not only street products, you will find every brand’s outlet in this market, whether it is of dresses or of shoes.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16883040/a384da40-4adf-11e6-8ac5-53c7c00a4f02.jpg">https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1082157/16883040/a384da40-4adf-11e6-8ac5-53c7c00a4f02.jpg</a>"></p>

<p>New Market is not only tourist-friendly; but also the place of foodies as well. Undoubtedly, this place contains the modern shopping malls where you can find top-notch quality products anytime. In a nutshell, this is the place where you can spend your complete weekend, if you are shopaholic and foodie person.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
